[[{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government faces a ____ decision: Does it anger the USA or does it anger its European allies?", "Opt_1": "capable", "Opt_2": "tough", "Opt_3": "obvious", "Opt_4": "imaginary", "Answer": "tough", "Opt_1_def": "able", "Opt_2_def": "difficult, strong", "Opt_3_def": "clear, evident", "Opt_4_def": "not real; from the imagination"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If you ____ someone who is not qualified for the job, you cannot be surprised if they have problems.", "Opt_1": "intervene", "Opt_2": "appoint", "Opt_3": "review", "Opt_4": "assure", "Answer": "appoint", "Opt_1_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)", "Opt_2_def": "to give a job to someone", "Opt_3_def": "to check over (and make changes)", "Opt_4_def": "to make sure; to say that something will certainly happen"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The director was not prepared to even listen to ideas ____ to his own.", "Opt_1": "growth", "Opt_2": "contrary", "Opt_3": "range", "Opt_4": "assignment", "Answer": "contrary", "Opt_1_def": "development, increase", "Opt_2_def": "opposite", "Opt_3_def": "extent, distance between two points", "Opt_4_def": "a task; the giving of a task"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "This alone makes the book a worthwhile read for students whose received knowledge about Africans is often little more than a stereotype of ____ victims.", "Opt_1": "slight", "Opt_2": "passive", "Opt_3": "supplementary", "Opt_4": "uniform", "Answer": "passive", "Opt_1_def": "small", "Opt_2_def": "not active; unresponsive", "Opt_3_def": "extra; additional", "Opt_4_def": "having the same qualities"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "If the student is determined to be independent of their parents, the student must be a ____ of Indiana since at least December 31 of the previous year.", "Opt_1": "province", "Opt_2": "research", "Opt_3": "resident", "Opt_4": "incentive", "Answer": "resident", "Opt_1_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_2_def": "study; the finding of information", "Opt_3_def": "a person who lives in a place", "Opt_4_def": "reason to do something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Rules do not usually stimulate creativity or passion; rather they ____ conformity and make us fear change.", "Opt_1": "demand", "Opt_2": "society", "Opt_3": "portion", "Opt_4": "stereotype", "Answer": "demand", "Opt_1_def": "a need or desire for", "Opt_2_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country", "Opt_3_def": "part, amount", "Opt_4_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "After several years of work, the project team was not able to gather the political support needed to maintain funding for the integrated ____ program.", "Opt_1": "proportion", "Opt_2": "service", "Opt_3": "compensation", "Opt_4": "trend", "Answer": "service", "Opt_1_def": "amount; number; percentage", "Opt_2_def": "work done for others; help", "Opt_3_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_4_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The ____ for her frequent absences will be a poor grade in the final exam.", "Opt_1": "penalty", "Opt_2": "administration", "Opt_3": "outcome", "Opt_4": "incentive", "Answer": "penalty", "Opt_1_def": "negative consequence; punishment", "Opt_2_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school", "Opt_3_def": "result", "Opt_4_def": "reason to do something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "She was unable to ____ her sadness when she only came third in the music competition.", "Opt_1": "dispose", "Opt_2": "harm", "Opt_3": "prevail", "Opt_4": "conceal", "Answer": "conceal", "Opt_1_def": "to get rid of", "Opt_2_def": "to damage or injure", "Opt_3_def": "to succeed; to overcome", "Opt_4_def": "to hide"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Oddly, however, the book is almost completely ____ in fictional representations of invalids.", "Opt_1": "deficient", "Opt_2": "logical", "Opt_3": "numerous", "Opt_4": "artificial", "Answer": "deficient", "Opt_1_def": "poor, lacking in quantity or quality", "Opt_2_def": "making sense", "Opt_3_def": "very many", "Opt_4_def": "not real or natural"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "When used correctly and consistently, condoms are an effective ____ of preventing pregnancy.", "Opt_1": "ability", "Opt_2": "source", "Opt_3": "effect", "Opt_4": "means", "Answer": "means", "Opt_1_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well", "Opt_2_def": "where something begins, where you can find something", "Opt_3_def": "result", "Opt_4_def": "way"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The ____ of most big cities around the main train station is often a dangerous place to be at night.", "Opt_1": "district", "Opt_2": "interior", "Opt_3": "sample", "Opt_4": "criterion", "Answer": "district", "Opt_1_def": "region of a city", "Opt_2_def": "inside", "Opt_3_def": "example; a smaller number of a larger collection", "Opt_4_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "In this article I will discuss the possible use of ____ speech recognition (ASR) for training students to improve their accents in a foreign language.", "Opt_1": "automatic", "Opt_2": "commercial", "Opt_3": "typical", "Opt_4": "loose", "Answer": "automatic", "Opt_1_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually", "Opt_2_def": "to do with business", "Opt_3_def": "usual", "Opt_4_def": "not firm or finished"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Some scientists claim that we cannot ____ global warming on the basis of a just few years of hot weather.", "Opt_1": "prosper", "Opt_2": "arise", "Opt_3": "infer", "Opt_4": "stress", "Answer": "infer", "Opt_1_def": "to do well; to become rich", "Opt_2_def": "to happen", "Opt_3_def": "to come to a conclusion about something", "Opt_4_def": "to emphasize; to say what is important"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It is not in employers' interest to get rid of cheap illegal immigrants - only to ____ them of any rights.", "Opt_1": "expel", "Opt_2": "deprive", "Opt_3": "allege", "Opt_4": "extend", "Answer": "deprive", "Opt_1_def": "to drive or push out", "Opt_2_def": "to take away (the opportunity)", "Opt_3_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_4_def": "to make longer in time or space"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Van Haarlem also said the team had ____ a large fragment of what may have been a ceramic baboon statue.", "Opt_1": "found", "Opt_2": "rotate", "Opt_3": "overlap", "Opt_4": "indicate", "Answer": "found", "Opt_1_def": "to begin (often an organization)", "Opt_2_def": "to turn or move (around)", "Opt_3_def": "to have in common; to cover part of", "Opt_4_def": "to show or convey"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Library and information science students must be taught how to ____ the resources that will allow them to anticipate the future and avoid becoming irrelevant as information professionals.", "Opt_1": "detect", "Opt_2": "trade", "Opt_3": "harm", "Opt_4": "exploit", "Answer": "exploit", "Opt_1_def": "to see, find or notice", "Opt_2_def": "to exchange products or services", "Opt_3_def": "to damage or injure", "Opt_4_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The typewriter is more or less ____ now that we have computers and keyboards.", "Opt_1": "obsolete", "Opt_2": "optional", "Opt_3": "immense", "Opt_4": "entire", "Answer": "obsolete", "Opt_1_def": "not used or needed any more; out of date", "Opt_2_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want", "Opt_3_def": "very large", "Opt_4_def": "whole, all"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "You will ____ students of their ability to think for themselves if you never set them challenging questions.", "Opt_1": "drain", "Opt_2": "fare", "Opt_3": "allocate", "Opt_4": "threaten", "Answer": "drain", "Opt_1_def": "to take away; to get rid of", "Opt_2_def": "to do or succeed", "Opt_3_def": "to give to (to promise to give)", "Opt_4_def": "to warn or show signs of danger"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "She is yet to ____ basic verb grammar. She often says He do .. instead of He does ...", "Opt_1": "donate", "Opt_2": "master", "Opt_3": "indicate", "Opt_4": "restore", "Answer": "master", "Opt_1_def": "to give (usually money)", "Opt_2_def": "to (gain) control", "Opt_3_def": "to show or convey", "Opt_4_def": "to put back, create again"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The June 1992 Gender Equity Study found a significant ____ in salaries between men and women.", "Opt_1": "incident", "Opt_2": "gap", "Opt_3": "ratio", "Opt_4": "income", "Answer": "gap", "Opt_1_def": "happening; event", "Opt_2_def": "space, opening or time between", "Opt_3_def": "mathematical relationship between two amount", "Opt_4_def": "money earned"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "As a result of the rise in the price of oil, the government has decided not to ____ the proposed tax increase.", "Opt_1": "consent", "Opt_2": "implement", "Opt_3": "dismiss", "Opt_4": "dominate", "Answer": "implement", "Opt_1_def": "to agree", "Opt_2_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)", "Opt_3_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant", "Opt_4_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "My teacher has the ____ of telling us the homework in the last minute of the lesson. It's not good.", "Opt_1": "habit", "Opt_2": "episode", "Opt_3": "interior", "Opt_4": "facilities", "Answer": "habit", "Opt_1_def": "something you do regularly", "Opt_2_def": "period of time", "Opt_3_def": "inside", "Opt_4_def": "buildings and other places that can be used by people"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It takes a lot of ____ to cook a meal for 20 guests.", "Opt_1": "skill", "Opt_2": "benefit", "Opt_3": "hypothesis", "Opt_4": "ability", "Answer": "skill", "Opt_1_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)", "Opt_2_def": "advantage", "Opt_3_def": "idea or prediction", "Opt_4_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "If the student contacts you before or after the experiment with a ____ excuse, you can cancel the appointment without penalty.", "Opt_1": "substantial", "Opt_2": "valid", "Opt_3": "ordinary", "Opt_4": "exact", "Answer": "valid", "Opt_1_def": "large", "Opt_2_def": "correct", "Opt_3_def": "usual, typical, every day", "Opt_4_def": "precise, opposite of approximate"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "However, no one criterion will be the ____ reason for lack of admission to the program.", "Opt_1": "accurate", "Opt_2": "cautious", "Opt_3": "brief", "Opt_4": "sole", "Answer": "sole", "Opt_1_def": "exact, containing no mistakes", "Opt_2_def": "careful", "Opt_3_def": "short", "Opt_4_def": "only"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Too much stress can ____ problems with mental and physical health, particularly over a prolonged period of time.", "Opt_1": "communicate", "Opt_2": "annotate", "Opt_3": "cover", "Opt_4": "trigger", "Answer": "trigger", "Opt_1_def": "to convey information", "Opt_2_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing", "Opt_3_def": "to do; to complete", "Opt_4_def": "to (cause to) start"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "She said sorry to the teacher and ____ avoided a detention.", "Opt_1": "universally", "Opt_2": "moreover", "Opt_3": "thereby", "Opt_4": "indirectly", "Answer": "thereby", "Opt_1_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_2_def": "also .., what is more ..", "Opt_3_def": "by doing this", "Opt_4_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Not everyone is ____ enough to have internet access at home.", "Opt_1": "deficient", "Opt_2": "fortunate", "Opt_3": "artificial", "Opt_4": "essential", "Answer": "fortunate", "Opt_1_def": "poor, lacking in quantity or quality", "Opt_2_def": "lucky", "Opt_3_def": "not real or natural", "Opt_4_def": "very important"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Do you have a ____ pencil? I forgot to bring mine.", "Opt_1": "accurate", "Opt_2": "ambitious", "Opt_3": "homogeneous", "Opt_4": "spare", "Answer": "spare", "Opt_1_def": "exact, containing no mistakes", "Opt_2_def": "having high goals (especially in a career; challenging", "Opt_3_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics", "Opt_4_def": "not needed"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Since that time two major surveys were conducted with an attempt to define the ____ of the problem.", "Opt_1": "privilege", "Opt_2": "argument", "Opt_3": "innovation", "Opt_4": "scope", "Answer": "scope", "Opt_1_def": "a right (to do something)", "Opt_2_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)", "Opt_3_def": "new object or idea", "Opt_4_def": "extent, range"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The third stage of the writing process is when you ____ your work. This means that you make any necessary changes to its structure or content.", "Opt_1": "refer", "Opt_2": "extend", "Opt_3": "descend", "Opt_4": "revise", "Answer": "revise", "Opt_1_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean", "Opt_2_def": "to make longer in time or space", "Opt_3_def": "to go down", "Opt_4_def": "to change (in order to improve)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The company has the ____ to dismiss employees without giving a reason during the first 6 months of their employment.", "Opt_1": "diagram", "Opt_2": "decision", "Opt_3": "liberty", "Opt_4": "ratio", "Answer": "liberty", "Opt_1_def": "a type of picture or chart", "Opt_2_def": "intention to do something, choice", "Opt_3_def": "freedom", "Opt_4_def": "mathematical relationship between two amount"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "She began to notice that being overlooked by her supervisor was not a ____ problem.", "Opt_1": "odd", "Opt_2": "temporary", "Opt_3": "significant", "Opt_4": "complex", "Answer": "temporary", "Opt_1_def": "strange, unusual", "Opt_2_def": "for a short or limited time", "Opt_3_def": "important, large", "Opt_4_def": "difficult, complicated"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The teacher gave me a ____ about the need to be in class on time with all my materials.", "Opt_1": "resource", "Opt_2": "lecture", "Opt_3": "occasion", "Opt_4": "figure", "Answer": "lecture", "Opt_1_def": "a source of information or material", "Opt_2_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "time (opportunity)", "Opt_4_def": "number"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "They felt this was an unreliable forecast ____ to poor data and that the harvest could in fact increase.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Doctors these days are not ____ to advising patients about poor lifestyle choices such as smoking or lack of exercise.", "Opt_1": "abundant", "Opt_2": "obvious", "Opt_3": "averse", "Opt_4": "political", "Answer": "averse", "Opt_1_def": "existing in large quantities", "Opt_2_def": "clear, evident", "Opt_3_def": "against", "Opt_4_def": "to do government and politics"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "For the second meeting of the Forum, we have arranged a debate between two legal professionals who must struggle with the death ____ regularly.", "Opt_1": "reply", "Opt_2": "penalty", "Opt_3": "assent", "Opt_4": "duty", "Answer": "penalty", "Opt_1_def": "an answer", "Opt_2_def": "negative consequence; punishment", "Opt_3_def": "agreement", "Opt_4_def": "responsibility, or job that you are required to do"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "All new systems to the data center will need to undergo a security scan or audit ____ to installation.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The teachers ____ that the school administration is secretly planning to increase working hours.", "Opt_1": "discuss", "Opt_2": "descend", "Opt_3": "allege", "Opt_4": "utilize", "Answer": "allege", "Opt_1_def": "to talk about", "Opt_2_def": "to go down", "Opt_3_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_4_def": "to use"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "You may need to ____ to the terms and scope of the permission (i.e., duration, purpose, etc.).", "Opt_1": "suspend", "Opt_2": "refer", "Opt_3": "alter", "Opt_4": "trust", "Answer": "refer", "Opt_1_def": "to stop (often for a short time only)", "Opt_2_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean", "Opt_3_def": "to change", "Opt_4_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The many demonstrators on the streets of the capital city were a clear ____ of the government's unpopularity.", "Opt_1": "community", "Opt_2": "detriment", "Opt_3": "statement", "Opt_4": "symptom", "Answer": "symptom", "Opt_1_def": "a group of people", "Opt_2_def": "disadvantage", "Opt_3_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)", "Opt_4_def": "sign (often of a disease or other problem)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The management is hoping that its new improved product will ____ increased profits.", "Opt_1": "attempt", "Opt_2": "yield", "Opt_3": "fulfill", "Opt_4": "correspond", "Answer": "yield", "Opt_1_def": "to try", "Opt_2_def": "to produce", "Opt_3_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)", "Opt_4_def": "to be related to"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The ____ between the United States and Mexico represents one of the greatest divisions of wealth on Earth.", "Opt_1": "boundary", "Opt_2": "theory", "Opt_3": "sum", "Opt_4": "criterion", "Answer": "boundary", "Opt_1_def": "limit, extent", "Opt_2_def": "idea or hypothesis", "Opt_3_def": "an amount of money, total", "Opt_4_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The temperature curve shows that the increase was not steady with time; a fact which could ____ be expected and is also not observed on other continents.", "Opt_1": "conversely", "Opt_2": "largely", "Opt_3": "gradually", "Opt_4": "hardly", "Answer": "hardly", "Opt_1_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand", "Opt_2_def": "mostly", "Opt_3_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_4_def": "not very much"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "There are six categories to ____ from, each containing five answers in ascending order of difficulty.", "Opt_1": "regulate", "Opt_2": "select", "Opt_3": "yield", "Opt_4": "attain", "Answer": "select", "Opt_1_def": "to control", "Opt_2_def": "to choose", "Opt_3_def": "to produce", "Opt_4_def": "to get, achieve"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It is essential to ____ her difficulties at school in the context of her chaotic home life.", "Opt_1": "consider", "Opt_2": "prevent", "Opt_3": "label", "Opt_4": "base", "Answer": "consider", "Opt_1_def": "to think", "Opt_2_def": "to stop from doing or happening", "Opt_3_def": "to give a name to someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "How many planet/planet collisions do you ____ will come from the M31 incident - or do you think we will be smoothly assimilated?", "Opt_1": "verify", "Opt_2": "assemble", "Opt_3": "obtain", "Opt_4": "presume", "Answer": "presume", "Opt_1_def": "to prove or claim the truth", "Opt_2_def": "to get, put or bring together", "Opt_3_def": "to get", "Opt_4_def": "to believe, assume"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Many people think that the government ____ to reduce teenage pregnancy will not be successful.", "Opt_1": "decision", "Opt_2": "record", "Opt_3": "magnitude", "Opt_4": "scheme", "Answer": "scheme", "Opt_1_def": "intention to do something, choice", "Opt_2_def": "evidence; documentation", "Opt_3_def": "size; amount", "Opt_4_def": "plan. idea, project"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "He seems to be lacking the ____ to improve his rather poor grades.", "Opt_1": "impulse", "Opt_2": "standard", "Opt_3": "behalf", "Opt_4": "duration", "Answer": "impulse", "Opt_1_def": "reason or motivation to do something", "Opt_2_def": "quality", "Opt_3_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of", "Opt_4_def": "period of time"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government must not hesitate in taking ____ actions against communism and all its supporters.", "Opt_1": "subsequent", "Opt_2": "harsh", "Opt_3": "essential", "Opt_4": "scarce", "Answer": "harsh", "Opt_1_def": "next, following", "Opt_2_def": "hard, unfair", "Opt_3_def": "very important", "Opt_4_def": "rare, not abundant"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Now that you have revised your work, the next stage of the writing process is to ____ it for errors of grammar or spelling.", "Opt_1": "underlie", "Opt_2": "edit", "Opt_3": "elect", "Opt_4": "isolate", "Answer": "edit", "Opt_1_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something", "Opt_2_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing", "Opt_3_def": "to choose by voting", "Opt_4_def": "to separate something or someone from others"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "If you saved a file to a library PC running Windows prior to a crash or being logged out, you should be able to ____ it.", "Opt_1": "possess", "Opt_2": "recover", "Opt_3": "append", "Opt_4": "owe", "Answer": "recover", "Opt_1_def": "to have or own", "Opt_2_def": "to get back", "Opt_3_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)", "Opt_4_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Your final course grade will ____ on your grades in the 3 trimester exams.", "Opt_1": "reward", "Opt_2": "retreat", "Opt_3": "fulfill", "Opt_4": "depend", "Answer": "depend", "Opt_1_def": "to give something (e.g. a prize) for good work or behaviour", "Opt_2_def": "to go back", "Opt_3_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)", "Opt_4_def": "be influenced (by)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "There is a sharp contrast between Japan's ____ rigid hierarchy of national and private universities with the United States, which has a wider variety of institutions.", "Opt_1": "fairly", "Opt_2": "thereby", "Opt_3": "universally", "Opt_4": "definitely", "Answer": "fairly", "Opt_1_def": "quite, somewhat", "Opt_2_def": "by doing this", "Opt_3_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_4_def": "certainly; without doubt"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "In my opinion the government should ____ more to prevent young people drinking and driving.", "Opt_1": "connect", "Opt_2": "attract", "Opt_3": "undertake", "Opt_4": "praise", "Answer": "undertake", "Opt_1_def": "to bring or put together", "Opt_2_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like", "Opt_3_def": "to (plan to) do", "Opt_4_def": "to express approval about something someone has done"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The data center will ____ researchers through the application of mathematics and computer science to biological problems.", "Opt_1": "observe", "Opt_2": "advise", "Opt_3": "assist", "Opt_4": "risk", "Answer": "assist", "Opt_1_def": "to watch carefully", "Opt_2_def": "to say what someone should do; to give advice", "Opt_3_def": "to help", "Opt_4_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The police have not been able to establish a ____ for the brutal killing.", "Opt_1": "location", "Opt_2": "research", "Opt_3": "amount", "Opt_4": "motive", "Answer": "motive", "Opt_1_def": "place, where something or someone is", "Opt_2_def": "study; the finding of information", "Opt_3_def": "how much there is of something", "Opt_4_def": "reason"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "In this article I will discuss the possible use of ____ speech recognition (ASR) for training students to improve their accents in a foreign language.", "Opt_1": "prompt", "Opt_2": "fortunate", "Opt_3": "relevant", "Opt_4": "automatic", "Answer": "automatic", "Opt_1_def": "quick; on or before time", "Opt_2_def": "lucky", "Opt_3_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration", "Opt_4_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The goals are to answer some of the most urgent questions to ____ significantly our scientific knowledge about Mars.", "Opt_1": "advance", "Opt_2": "investigate", "Opt_3": "isolate", "Opt_4": "devise", "Answer": "advance", "Opt_1_def": "to go or move forward; to get better", "Opt_2_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened", "Opt_3_def": "to separate something or someone from others", "Opt_4_def": "to create or think up"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Children ____ in classes where their teachers care about each of them as individuals.", "Opt_1": "displace", "Opt_2": "dismiss", "Opt_3": "persist", "Opt_4": "prosper", "Answer": "prosper", "Opt_1_def": "to push out or take the place of something or someone", "Opt_2_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant", "Opt_3_def": "to continue (often in the face of difficulty)", "Opt_4_def": "to do well; to become rich"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If you are trying to understand the instructions of a new piece of ____ like a camera, it helps to have a diagram to look at.", "Opt_1": "quality", "Opt_2": "income", "Opt_3": "stage", "Opt_4": "equipment", "Answer": "equipment", "Opt_1_def": "worth or value", "Opt_2_def": "money earned", "Opt_3_def": "period of time, part of a process", "Opt_4_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "If you discover that you have the wrong textbook, you must ____ the source from which you purchased the book and make arrangements to exchange the book.", "Opt_1": "contact", "Opt_2": "rotate", "Opt_3": "increase", "Opt_4": "block", "Answer": "contact", "Opt_1_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)", "Opt_2_def": "to turn or move (around)", "Opt_3_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_4_def": "to not allow; to stop or prevent"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "We believe that individuals who respect and support a diverse ____ society will prosper as leaders in schools, universities, businesses, and human service.", "Opt_1": "global", "Opt_2": "utter", "Opt_3": "firm", "Opt_4": "precise", "Answer": "global", "Opt_1_def": "world", "Opt_2_def": "complete, total", "Opt_3_def": "strong, cannot be changed", "Opt_4_def": "exact"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It is essential to ____ her difficulties at school in the context of her chaotic home life.", "Opt_1": "attempt", "Opt_2": "increase", "Opt_3": "consider", "Opt_4": "accumulate", "Answer": "consider", "Opt_1_def": "to try", "Opt_2_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_3_def": "to think", "Opt_4_def": "to grow; to gather together"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Since the human body is not an ____ that can be disposed of at will, the results of research should be made available to the whole scientific community.", "Opt_1": "event", "Opt_2": "object", "Opt_3": "profession", "Opt_4": "belief", "Answer": "object", "Opt_1_def": "a happening", "Opt_2_def": "thing", "Opt_3_def": "job; occupation", "Opt_4_def": "what you think; what you believe in"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It is an insult in some countries to ____ an offer of the local food.", "Opt_1": "tolerate", "Opt_2": "propose", "Opt_3": "reject", "Opt_4": "disperse", "Answer": "reject", "Opt_1_def": "to allow to happen; to bear", "Opt_2_def": "to suggest", "Opt_3_def": "to refuse", "Opt_4_def": "to spread out; to move apart"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "There is very little difference in the quality of learning received by distance ____ students and regular students, according to a study.", "Opt_1": "detriment", "Opt_2": "ratio", "Opt_3": "education", "Opt_4": "scale", "Answer": "education", "Opt_1_def": "disadvantage", "Opt_2_def": "mathematical relationship between two amount", "Opt_3_def": "schooling", "Opt_4_def": "extent"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Doctors often fail in their attempt to ____ patients to stop smoking. The habit is too addictive.", "Opt_1": "contact", "Opt_2": "comprehend", "Opt_3": "verify", "Opt_4": "persuade", "Answer": "persuade", "Opt_1_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)", "Opt_2_def": "to understand", "Opt_3_def": "to prove or claim the truth", "Opt_4_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "She has continued ____ me with her hard work and positive attitude.", "Opt_1": "communicate", "Opt_2": "derive", "Opt_3": "impress", "Opt_4": "contact", "Answer": "impress", "Opt_1_def": "to convey information", "Opt_2_def": "to come from or get from", "Opt_3_def": "to create a favourable reaction", "Opt_4_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Monroe is a well-known ____ of the mechanical theory of education, with its cult of standardization, intelligence tests, etc.", "Opt_1": "exponent", "Opt_2": "district", "Opt_3": "issue", "Opt_4": "contrary", "Answer": "exponent", "Opt_1_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion", "Opt_2_def": "region of a city", "Opt_3_def": "a matter or problem", "Opt_4_def": "opposite"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Lack of sufficient revenue often prohibits sound management activities that are ____ to the company's long-term health and stability.", "Opt_1": "final", "Opt_2": "confident", "Opt_3": "basic", "Opt_4": "necessary", "Answer": "necessary", "Opt_1_def": "last", "Opt_2_def": "sure that something will happen", "Opt_3_def": "first or easy", "Opt_4_def": "needed; very important"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It was not the goal of this book to ____ whether America can win the war, or whether it must lose it.", "Opt_1": "intervene", "Opt_2": "discuss", "Opt_3": "produce", "Opt_4": "prove", "Answer": "discuss", "Opt_1_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)", "Opt_2_def": "to talk about", "Opt_3_def": "to make or create", "Opt_4_def": "to show to be true"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The Court did not find it necessary to hear the testimony of the two forensic experts and did not ____ the possibility of ordering a further investigation.", "Opt_1": "achieve", "Opt_2": "violate", "Opt_3": "consider", "Opt_4": "accomplish", "Answer": "consider", "Opt_1_def": "to gain or get something (often academic success)", "Opt_2_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_3_def": "to think", "Opt_4_def": "to do or achieve"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Hacking's book suffers from a serious defect, ____ he does not understand the nature of hypnosis.", "Opt_1": "absolutely", "Opt_2": "seldom", "Opt_3": "somewhat", "Opt_4": "namely", "Answer": "namely", "Opt_1_def": "completely; 100%", "Opt_2_def": "rare", "Opt_3_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_4_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Later in the year they plan to ____ up to 4000,00 more solar panels in a student village to be built for the university.", "Opt_1": "review", "Opt_2": "install", "Opt_3": "join", "Opt_4": "align", "Answer": "install", "Opt_1_def": "to check over (and make changes)", "Opt_2_def": "to put in (often a machine or new system)", "Opt_3_def": "to become a member (of an organization; to get together with others", "Opt_4_def": "to bring into line with; to make similar"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The Health Department is advertising on TV to ____ the message about the importance of healthy eating and exercise.", "Opt_1": "overlap", "Opt_2": "suggest", "Opt_3": "trigger", "Opt_4": "spread", "Answer": "spread", "Opt_1_def": "to have in common; to cover part of", "Opt_2_def": "to say an idea; to recommend", "Opt_3_def": "to (cause to) start", "Opt_4_def": "to move (over a wider area)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Excellent writing with just one or two ____ mistakes!", "Opt_1": "trivial", "Opt_2": "certain", "Opt_3": "royal", "Opt_4": "sane", "Answer": "trivial", "Opt_1_def": "not important", "Opt_2_def": "sure", "Opt_3_def": "of kings and queens", "Opt_4_def": "reasonable; not mad"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Some doctors have the ____ to use language that their patients do not understand.", "Opt_1": "plenty", "Opt_2": "bias", "Opt_3": "potential", "Opt_4": "propensity", "Answer": "propensity", "Opt_1_def": "many, lots of", "Opt_2_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice", "Opt_3_def": "good possibility", "Opt_4_def": "tendency; desire"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The school have employed some guards to make the campus more ____ against unannounced visitors.", "Opt_1": "secure", "Opt_2": "rapid", "Opt_3": "compulsory", "Opt_4": "commercial", "Answer": "secure", "Opt_1_def": "safe", "Opt_2_def": "quick", "Opt_3_def": "required, must be done", "Opt_4_def": "to do with business"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The U.S. firms selling steel in India must compete ____ the firms from not merely India but Europe, Japan, Korea and China as well.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Having access to the laptop does seem to have substantially increased the overall feeling of having ____ resources to do the job.", "Opt_1": "stable", "Opt_2": "adequate", "Opt_3": "military", "Opt_4": "diverse", "Answer": "adequate", "Opt_1_def": "not changing; not easy to change", "Opt_2_def": "good enough; ok", "Opt_3_def": "to do with army", "Opt_4_def": "many and different"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "US companies have too often viewed the social sector as a dumping ground for their spare cash, ____ equipment, and tired executives.", "Opt_1": "available", "Opt_2": "rational", "Opt_3": "obsolete", "Opt_4": "chief", "Answer": "obsolete", "Opt_1_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_2_def": "base on reason, not on emotion or instinct", "Opt_3_def": "not used or needed any more; out of date", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The last week of the tennis tournament will ____ the first week of the Olympic Games.", "Opt_1": "occur", "Opt_2": "emphasize", "Opt_3": "investigate", "Opt_4": "overlap", "Answer": "overlap", "Opt_1_def": "to happen; take place", "Opt_2_def": "to stress, to say something strongly", "Opt_3_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened", "Opt_4_def": "to have in common; to cover part of"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "In addition to paying for the required tuition and fees, you will need to ____ a variety of materials to complete this class.", "Opt_1": "suppress", "Opt_2": "procure", "Opt_3": "prepare", "Opt_4": "interact", "Answer": "procure", "Opt_1_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen", "Opt_2_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_3_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)", "Opt_4_def": "to react, to affect and be affected"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Some students find it difficult to ____ to a new school in a new country.", "Opt_1": "collaborate", "Opt_2": "reject", "Opt_3": "adapt", "Opt_4": "assemble", "Answer": "adapt", "Opt_1_def": "to work together", "Opt_2_def": "to refuse", "Opt_3_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)", "Opt_4_def": "to get, put or bring together"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The purpose of this tutorial is to give you an idea of the ____ of events leading up to graduation.", "Opt_1": "treatment", "Opt_2": "supply", "Opt_3": "technique", "Opt_4": "sequence", "Answer": "sequence", "Opt_1_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)", "Opt_2_def": "provision, store", "Opt_3_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "the order in which things are arranged or happen"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The company's problems did not ____ until the price of oil increased.", "Opt_1": "appear", "Opt_2": "praise", "Opt_3": "master", "Opt_4": "commence", "Answer": "commence", "Opt_1_def": "to come, be seen", "Opt_2_def": "to express approval about something someone has done", "Opt_3_def": "to (gain) control", "Opt_4_def": "to start"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The primary ____ of the Management Information Systems Department is to prepare students for exciting and challenging careers in the information technology.", "Opt_1": "interpretation", "Opt_2": "attribute", "Opt_3": "institution", "Opt_4": "objective", "Answer": "objective", "Opt_1_def": "explanation; assessment", "Opt_2_def": "characteristic; property", "Opt_3_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom", "Opt_4_def": "aim or goal"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is not usual that students ____ with their teachers whether they must do homework or not.", "Opt_1": "advocate", "Opt_2": "negotiate", "Opt_3": "decline", "Opt_4": "convert", "Answer": "negotiate", "Opt_1_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)", "Opt_3_def": "to go down or get worse", "Opt_4_def": "to change from one thing to another"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "To launch the project, a special event will ____ at Stanford University's Center for Design Research at 11am today.", "Opt_1": "risk", "Opt_2": "deserve", "Opt_3": "commence", "Opt_4": "contribute", "Answer": "commence", "Opt_1_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure", "Opt_2_def": "to have the right to something", "Opt_3_def": "to start", "Opt_4_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Students who are awarded an International Student Scholarship must ____ the following requirements each semester in order to continue receiving this award.", "Opt_1": "classify", "Opt_2": "fulfill", "Opt_3": "react", "Opt_4": "assess", "Answer": "fulfill", "Opt_1_def": "to put into a category or class", "Opt_2_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)", "Opt_3_def": "to respond", "Opt_4_def": "to judge or test"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It is not the government's ____ to tell its citizens how to live.", "Opt_1": "extract", "Opt_2": "crisis", "Opt_3": "role", "Opt_4": "cause", "Answer": "role", "Opt_1_def": "to remove; to take out and use", "Opt_2_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe", "Opt_3_def": "job or function", "Opt_4_def": "the reason why something happens"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Students must demonstrate ____ of a competent reading knowledge of a language other than modern English.", "Opt_1": "industry", "Opt_2": "evidence", "Opt_3": "apparatus", "Opt_4": "insight", "Answer": "evidence", "Opt_1_def": "area of business ( often manufacturing )", "Opt_2_def": "proof, signs", "Opt_3_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job", "Opt_4_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "They are currently involved in a battle ____ Occidental Petroleum to save their land and their way of life.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "She is having serious problems in her mathematics class. She cannot even ____ two numbers using a calculator.", "Opt_1": "accomplish", "Opt_2": "multiply", "Opt_3": "preserve", "Opt_4": "owe", "Answer": "multiply", "Opt_1_def": "to do or achieve", "Opt_2_def": "to increase greatly", "Opt_3_def": "forward,\" said Michele Gougeon.", "Opt_4_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Some beach systems showed significant ____ of sand in the period from 1964.", "Opt_1": "loss", "Opt_2": "statement", "Opt_3": "trace", "Opt_4": "demand", "Answer": "loss", "Opt_1_def": "removal or reduction", "Opt_2_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)", "Opt_3_def": "sign; indication; evidence", "Opt_4_def": "a need or desire for"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The school made a mistake when buying new computers. They are not ____ with the printers we have.", "Opt_1": "compatible", "Opt_2": "chief", "Opt_3": "mental", "Opt_4": "official", "Answer": "compatible", "Opt_1_def": "able to work with someone or something else", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "of the brain or mind", "Opt_4_def": "approved by an authority"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "There is land ____ the ice in Antarctica, but water ____ it at the North Pole.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Our teacher showed us an ____ of The Simpsons in ESL class yesterday.", "Opt_1": "debt", "Opt_2": "debate", "Opt_3": "episode", "Opt_4": "challenge", "Answer": "episode", "Opt_1_def": "something owed to another person (often money)", "Opt_2_def": "formal discussion", "Opt_3_def": "period of time", "Opt_4_def": "difficult situation; problem"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The percentage of online adults who say they ____ ever or never search for health information has dropped to 39 percent.", "Opt_1": "especially", "Opt_2": "generally", "Opt_3": "indirectly", "Opt_4": "hardly", "Answer": "hardly", "Opt_1_def": "particularly", "Opt_2_def": "usually", "Opt_3_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate", "Opt_4_def": "not very much"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It is predicted that Off-campus study programs will ____ due to the problematic financial situation.", "Opt_1": "shrink", "Opt_2": "migrate", "Opt_3": "overcome", "Opt_4": "exhaust", "Answer": "shrink", "Opt_1_def": "to get smaller", "Opt_2_def": "to go to another place", "Opt_3_def": "to conquer, defeat", "Opt_4_def": "to use up"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Colorado State University scientists have found a way to ____ improve the quality of laser light at extremely short wavelengths.", "Opt_1": "dramatically", "Opt_2": "overly", "Opt_3": "gradually", "Opt_4": "seldom", "Answer": "dramatically", "Opt_1_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_2_def": "too", "Opt_3_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_4_def": "rare"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "When the USA expelled two Russian diplomats, the Russian ____ was to do the same.", "Opt_1": "income", "Opt_2": "concern", "Opt_3": "range", "Opt_4": "reply", "Answer": "reply", "Opt_1_def": "money earned", "Opt_2_def": "worry, fear", "Opt_3_def": "extent, distance between two points", "Opt_4_def": "an answer"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "In 1986, 23 percent of parents said obedience was the most important ____ they expected from their children.", "Opt_1": "trait", "Opt_2": "period", "Opt_3": "disaster", "Opt_4": "desire", "Answer": "trait", "Opt_1_def": "characteristic; aspect", "Opt_2_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)", "Opt_3_def": "a huge problem or failure", "Opt_4_def": "a want or wish for something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Terrorists control large areas of the country outside of the ____ towns.", "Opt_1": "similar", "Opt_2": "main", "Opt_3": "effective", "Opt_4": "ideal", "Answer": "main", "Opt_1_def": "like, almost the same as", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "good, working well", "Opt_4_def": "best, optimal"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It should be obvious that the consumption habits of the wealthy countries are the ____ cause of environmental problems.", "Opt_1": "prime", "Opt_2": "absent", "Opt_3": "dynamic", "Opt_4": "compulsory", "Answer": "prime", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "being not there; missing", "Opt_3_def": "changing; growing; energetic", "Opt_4_def": "required, must be done"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The school has a ratio of ____ one teacher for every fifteen students.", "Opt_1": "approximately", "Opt_2": "thereby", "Opt_3": "rather", "Opt_4": "dramatically", "Answer": "approximately", "Opt_1_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_2_def": "by doing this", "Opt_3_def": "instead", "Opt_4_def": "very strongly, significantly"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "He rightly concludes that the end of the Cold War failed to ____ significant changes in the Horn of Africa or to improve the mutual security of states.", "Opt_1": "declare", "Opt_2": "subsidize", "Opt_3": "presume", "Opt_4": "induce", "Answer": "induce", "Opt_1_def": "to state", "Opt_2_def": "to support financially", "Opt_3_def": "to believe, assume", "Opt_4_def": "to make happen; to force"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Thus, while we do not wish to speculate on future developments, we need to consider the ____ and potential effects of the decision.", "Opt_1": "actual", "Opt_2": "main", "Opt_3": "consistent", "Opt_4": "obsolete", "Answer": "actual", "Opt_1_def": "real", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same", "Opt_4_def": "not used or needed any more; out of date"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It is not usual that students ____ with their teachers whether they must do homework or not.", "Opt_1": "advance", "Opt_2": "explain", "Opt_3": "negotiate", "Opt_4": "implement", "Answer": "negotiate", "Opt_1_def": "to go or move forward; to get better", "Opt_2_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)", "Opt_4_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It is impossible to ____ any Yuan play in its original style because the music is lost and its social context has changed.", "Opt_1": "revive", "Opt_2": "suggest", "Opt_3": "elect", "Opt_4": "manipulate", "Answer": "revive", "Opt_1_def": "to bring back (to life)", "Opt_2_def": "to say an idea; to recommend", "Opt_3_def": "to choose by voting", "Opt_4_def": "to (use and) change"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Government ministers laid flowers at the ____ of the terrorist explosion.", "Opt_1": "insight", "Opt_2": "sequence", "Opt_3": "privilege", "Opt_4": "site", "Answer": "site", "Opt_1_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)", "Opt_2_def": "the order in which things are arranged or happen", "Opt_3_def": "a right (to do something)", "Opt_4_def": "place"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The first effort to produce a revised policy started during the mid-1980s and failed to ____ in a new agreement.", "Opt_1": "persist", "Opt_2": "enter", "Opt_3": "culminate", "Opt_4": "displace", "Answer": "culminate", "Opt_1_def": "to continue (often in the face of difficulty)", "Opt_2_def": "to go in or put in", "Opt_3_def": "to end", "Opt_4_def": "to push out or take the place of something or someone"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "An error will ____ if this software is not installed on the user's machine.", "Opt_1": "inspect", "Opt_2": "contribute", "Opt_3": "suffer", "Opt_4": "occur", "Answer": "occur", "Opt_1_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_2_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in", "Opt_3_def": "to experience something bad or painful", "Opt_4_def": "to happen; take place"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Many students who ____ a grade lower than they want, do so because they fail to annotate their texts.", "Opt_1": "emphasize", "Opt_2": "receive", "Opt_3": "prevail", "Opt_4": "express", "Answer": "receive", "Opt_1_def": "to stress, to say something strongly", "Opt_2_def": "to get", "Opt_3_def": "to succeed; to overcome", "Opt_4_def": "to say or mean"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "We all have to tolerate differences of opinion in the political world and, in ____ to do that, we have to understand that there are real reasons for these differences.", "Opt_1": "community", "Opt_2": "format", "Opt_3": "duty", "Opt_4": "order", "Answer": "order", "Opt_1_def": "a group of people", "Opt_2_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting", "Opt_3_def": "responsibility, or job that you are required to do", "Opt_4_def": "sequence, place"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "We need to ____ on the important issues.", "Opt_1": "exhaust", "Opt_2": "focus", "Opt_3": "announce", "Opt_4": "compile", "Answer": "focus", "Opt_1_def": "to use up", "Opt_2_def": "to direct attention (on an issue)", "Opt_3_def": "to state (often in an official way)", "Opt_4_def": "to put together (often in a list"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government decided to increase its ____ to the countries of eastern Africa.", "Opt_1": "goal", "Opt_2": "guarantee", "Opt_3": "aid", "Opt_4": "deed", "Answer": "aid", "Opt_1_def": "aim or intention", "Opt_2_def": "to promise or assure that something will or will not happen", "Opt_3_def": "help (often financial help)", "Opt_4_def": "an action"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The ____ of child deaths in the nineteenth century is one which could hardly fail to interest any serious scholar of the period.", "Opt_1": "interval", "Opt_2": "disaster", "Opt_3": "topic", "Opt_4": "sample", "Answer": "topic", "Opt_1_def": "a period of time", "Opt_2_def": "a huge problem or failure", "Opt_3_def": "area of interest or discussion", "Opt_4_def": "example; a smaller number of a larger collection"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government has failed to reduce unemployment ____ all its efforts over the last 5 years.", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "prior", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "before"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The business tried to ____ its employees to work harder by offering an extra day's holiday to the best salesperson.", "Opt_1": "motivate", "Opt_2": "mention", "Opt_3": "contribute", "Opt_4": "consult", "Answer": "motivate", "Opt_1_def": "to get someone interested enough to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to say; state", "Opt_3_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in", "Opt_4_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "In my opinion the government's ____ for banning smoking is very weak. Surely they don't expect people to agree!", "Opt_1": "argument", "Opt_2": "error", "Opt_3": "potential", "Opt_4": "dispute", "Answer": "argument", "Opt_1_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)", "Opt_2_def": "a mistake", "Opt_3_def": "good possibility", "Opt_4_def": "argument; conflict"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It has no alternative but to ____ to more sources and additional help from all those who are keen to support Palestinian education.", "Opt_1": "continue", "Opt_2": "appeal", "Opt_3": "confine", "Opt_4": "revise", "Answer": "appeal", "Opt_1_def": "to carry on, not stop", "Opt_2_def": "to complain against an official judgment; to make a strong request", "Opt_3_def": "to limit", "Opt_4_def": "to change (in order to improve)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "She was raised by a family that did not appreciate the significance of racial differences and the importance of developing a ____ racial identity.", "Opt_1": "poor", "Opt_2": "commercial", "Opt_3": "positive", "Opt_4": "novel", "Answer": "positive", "Opt_1_def": "bad, unsatisfactory", "Opt_2_def": "to do with business", "Opt_3_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_4_def": "new"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Therefore, it is important to ____ low birth weight infants according to their weight for their gestational age.", "Opt_1": "reform", "Opt_2": "procure", "Opt_3": "classify", "Opt_4": "afford", "Answer": "classify", "Opt_1_def": "to change and improve", "Opt_2_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_3_def": "to put into a category or class", "Opt_4_def": "to be able to pay for something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The xenon atoms need to accelerate to a ____ of 30 km/s.", "Opt_1": "victory", "Opt_2": "speed", "Opt_3": "goal", "Opt_4": "majority", "Answer": "speed", "Opt_1_def": "win", "Opt_2_def": "how quickly something moves or changes", "Opt_3_def": "aim or intention", "Opt_4_def": "more than 50%"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The ____ of the government's willingness to pay kidnappers to release hostages is that now there are more kidnappings and more hostages.", "Opt_1": "experiment", "Opt_2": "margin", "Opt_3": "decision", "Opt_4": "outcome", "Answer": "outcome", "Opt_1_def": "test", "Opt_2_def": "amount; distance", "Opt_3_def": "intention to do something, choice", "Opt_4_def": "result"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Quaranta envisions a future when computer simulations like this will be used to ____ a tumor's clinical progression.", "Opt_1": "predict", "Opt_2": "deny", "Opt_3": "tolerate", "Opt_4": "append", "Answer": "predict", "Opt_1_def": "to say what will happen in the future", "Opt_2_def": "to refuse ( responsibility for doing or saying something); to say that something is not correct", "Opt_3_def": "to allow to happen; to bear", "Opt_4_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "There are strict laws that ____ the trade in rainforest wood.", "Opt_1": "request", "Opt_2": "enlarge", "Opt_3": "contemplate", "Opt_4": "govern", "Answer": "govern", "Opt_1_def": "to ask politely", "Opt_2_def": "to make larger", "Opt_3_def": "to think about; to consider", "Opt_4_def": "to control or influence"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "We will continue to see new immigrants coming to our city, and we will need to ____ their access into the medical care system.", "Opt_1": "evidence", "Opt_2": "resident", "Opt_3": "guarantee", "Opt_4": "deal", "Answer": "guarantee", "Opt_1_def": "proof, signs", "Opt_2_def": "a person who lives in a place", "Opt_3_def": "to promise or assure that something will or will not happen", "Opt_4_def": "agreement"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "I was headed into new ____ not in what I was teaching but in how I was to teach it.", "Opt_1": "course", "Opt_2": "territory", "Opt_3": "dimension", "Opt_4": "responsibility", "Answer": "territory", "Opt_1_def": "a subject or period of study", "Opt_2_def": "land; area (of interest)", "Opt_3_def": "importance; amount", "Opt_4_def": "job, duty to do something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government has taken the ____ decision to consult the public before passing the proposed law.", "Opt_1": "ordinary", "Opt_2": "necessary", "Opt_3": "wise", "Opt_4": "distinct", "Answer": "wise", "Opt_1_def": "usual, typical, every day", "Opt_2_def": "needed; very important", "Opt_3_def": "intelligent; sensible", "Opt_4_def": "clear and strong"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The school had similar exam results to last year, with the ____ion ____ that mathematics scores were a little higher.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "If two students are always talking in class, then the teacher will often ____ them and make them sit in opposite parts of the room.", "Opt_1": "pursue", "Opt_2": "lessen", "Opt_3": "cover", "Opt_4": "separate", "Answer": "separate", "Opt_1_def": "to follow (or do)", "Opt_2_def": "to reduce", "Opt_3_def": "to do; to complete", "Opt_4_def": "to pull or put apart"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government does not plan to admit any more immigrants unless they can ____ that their life is in danger in their own country.", "Opt_1": "disrupt", "Opt_2": "prove", "Opt_3": "insert", "Opt_4": "stress", "Answer": "prove", "Opt_1_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage", "Opt_2_def": "to show to be true", "Opt_3_def": "to put in", "Opt_4_def": "to emphasize; to say what is important"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If you do not ____ the rules of the classroom, you will be sent to the headmaster.", "Opt_1": "obey", "Opt_2": "manufacture", "Opt_3": "import", "Opt_4": "associate", "Answer": "obey", "Opt_1_def": "to do as commanded or expected", "Opt_2_def": "to produce (with machines)", "Opt_3_def": "to bring in (to a country)", "Opt_4_def": "to link to; to make a connection to"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "We got some very ____ results in our science experiment. I think the thermometer was not working correctly.", "Opt_1": "serious", "Opt_2": "compatible", "Opt_3": "abnormal", "Opt_4": "confident", "Answer": "abnormal", "Opt_1_def": "severe, large", "Opt_2_def": "able to work with someone or something else", "Opt_3_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_4_def": "sure that something will happen"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Many businesses offer ____ working hours. Employees can arrive early and leave early or arrive late and leave late.", "Opt_1": "flexible", "Opt_2": "crucial", "Opt_3": "vague", "Opt_4": "abundant", "Answer": "flexible", "Opt_1_def": "can be changed or bent", "Opt_2_def": "extremely important", "Opt_3_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_4_def": "existing in large quantities"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Even with support, because of his health and limits on the hours he could work, he was unable to ____ the duties of the typical teaching job.", "Opt_1": "fulfill", "Opt_2": "classify", "Opt_3": "react", "Opt_4": "succeed", "Answer": "fulfill", "Opt_1_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)", "Opt_2_def": "to put into a category or class", "Opt_3_def": "to respond", "Opt_4_def": "to do well"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Psychologist Peter Wason discovered that we have enormous difficulty understanding certain sentences that ____ common sense.", "Opt_1": "contradict", "Opt_2": "subsidize", "Opt_3": "devise", "Opt_4": "cease", "Answer": "contradict", "Opt_1_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong", "Opt_2_def": "to support financially", "Opt_3_def": "to create or think up", "Opt_4_def": "to stop"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "She has gained ____ good grades since she has started attending school more regularly.", "Opt_1": "moreover", "Opt_2": "therefore", "Opt_3": "occasionally", "Opt_4": "predominantly", "Answer": "predominantly", "Opt_1_def": "also .., what is more ..", "Opt_2_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_3_def": "sometimes", "Opt_4_def": "mostly"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Archaeologists found some Roman coins ____ the town wall.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "She was raised by a family that did not ____ the significance of racial differences and the importance of developing a positive racial identity.", "Opt_1": "assimilate", "Opt_2": "fail", "Opt_3": "abandon", "Opt_4": "appreciate", "Answer": "appreciate", "Opt_1_def": "to take in", "Opt_2_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly", "Opt_3_def": "to leave or give up", "Opt_4_def": "to understand (the value of someone or something)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It is scheduled to begin at 3:30 p.m. A decision to cancel or ____ the match will be made later in the day, if necessary.", "Opt_1": "distort", "Opt_2": "distinguish", "Opt_3": "postpone", "Opt_4": "reflect", "Answer": "postpone", "Opt_1_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)", "Opt_2_def": "to make clear the differences between two things", "Opt_3_def": "to put back in time", "Opt_4_def": "to think or consider"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Do not ____ the serious error of believing you can pass the course without doing the coursework.", "Opt_1": "block", "Opt_2": "contradict", "Opt_3": "regard", "Opt_4": "commit", "Answer": "commit", "Opt_1_def": "to not allow; to stop or prevent", "Opt_2_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong", "Opt_3_def": "to think or have an opinion about something or someone", "Opt_4_def": "to do (often an offense)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The practice test materials will become available just ____ to the class.", "Opt_1": "among", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "in, between", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is an insult in some countries to ____ an offer of the local food.", "Opt_1": "reject", "Opt_2": "express", "Opt_3": "eliminate", "Opt_4": "discover", "Answer": "reject", "Opt_1_def": "to refuse", "Opt_2_def": "to say or mean", "Opt_3_def": "to dispose of", "Opt_4_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Students need to ____ with the department offering the master's degree to ensure the correct credential courses are taken.", "Opt_1": "inquire", "Opt_2": "coordinate", "Opt_3": "assure", "Opt_4": "drain", "Answer": "inquire", "Opt_1_def": "to ask", "Opt_2_def": "to bring things or people together so that they work well", "Opt_3_def": "to make sure; to say that something will certainly happen", "Opt_4_def": "to take away; to get rid of"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "I ____ one thing I cannot do is review the film as I wished it had been made.", "Opt_1": "suppose", "Opt_2": "solve", "Opt_3": "inform", "Opt_4": "strain", "Answer": "suppose", "Opt_1_def": "to think, imagine", "Opt_2_def": "to find an answer", "Opt_3_def": "to say, give information", "Opt_4_def": "to put under stress or make difficult"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "There was not a big difference in the negative description of Saddam Hussein among the three newspapers, and these descriptions did not ____ much space.", "Opt_1": "proceed", "Opt_2": "neglect", "Opt_3": "prevent", "Opt_4": "occupy", "Answer": "occupy", "Opt_1_def": "to go forward (and do ..)", "Opt_2_def": "to not think about or care for", "Opt_3_def": "to stop from doing or happening", "Opt_4_def": "to up space or time"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "He came to the conclusion that Mexico's constitutions did not last because they ____ did not conform to Mexico's customs and traditions.", "Opt_1": "indirectly", "Opt_2": "nevertheless", "Opt_3": "simply", "Opt_4": "somewhat", "Answer": "simply", "Opt_1_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate", "Opt_2_def": "however (although / despite that)", "Opt_3_def": "completely; just; only", "Opt_4_def": "quite, rather"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "And ____ failing to reduce unemployment, the government has also increased the tax on food.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "However, continuous and systematic research on the ____ did not emerge until after World War II.", "Opt_1": "guarantee", "Opt_2": "disaster", "Opt_3": "tool", "Opt_4": "implication", "Answer": "disaster", "Opt_1_def": "to promise or assure that something will or will not happen", "Opt_2_def": "a huge problem or failure", "Opt_3_def": "something used to do a job", "Opt_4_def": "result or consequence"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "There have been ____ attempts to build an intelligent robot, but so far no-one has been successful.", "Opt_1": "strict", "Opt_2": "global", "Opt_3": "poor", "Opt_4": "numerous", "Answer": "numerous", "Opt_1_def": "hard, not changeable", "Opt_2_def": "world", "Opt_3_def": "bad, unsatisfactory", "Opt_4_def": "very many"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The only disappointing part of the book is a portion of the third chapter, which is devoted to an interesting but much too ____ discussion of FDR's foreign policy.", "Opt_1": "brief", "Opt_2": "significant", "Opt_3": "suitable", "Opt_4": "mobile", "Answer": "brief", "Opt_1_def": "short", "Opt_2_def": "important, large", "Opt_3_def": "good for a particular job or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "moving; able to move"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Because there was the threat of losing funding if they failed to participate, there was a strong ____ to do so.", "Opt_1": "volume", "Opt_2": "incentive", "Opt_3": "mixture", "Opt_4": "education", "Answer": "incentive", "Opt_1_def": "amount", "Opt_2_def": "reason to do something", "Opt_3_def": "combination", "Opt_4_def": "schooling"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Dr. Pruitt said that he was very confident that all aspects of the law, as well as any other concerns, would be closely looked at prior to any ____ being made.", "Opt_1": "license", "Opt_2": "deal", "Opt_3": "sum", "Opt_4": "guarantee", "Answer": "deal", "Opt_1_def": "permission to do something (often an official document)", "Opt_2_def": "agreement", "Opt_3_def": "an amount of money, total", "Opt_4_def": "to promise or assure that something will or will not happen"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "There is no mechanism in the master plan to ____ whether or not we are doing what we are supposed to do.", "Opt_1": "offer", "Opt_2": "accumulate", "Opt_3": "assess", "Opt_4": "settle", "Answer": "assess", "Opt_1_def": "to ask if someone would like something (e.g. food or help)", "Opt_2_def": "to grow; to gather together", "Opt_3_def": "to judge or test", "Opt_4_def": "to solve a problem or dispute"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The government is finding it difficult to break the ____ of poverty and poor school performance.", "Opt_1": "evidence", "Opt_2": "incident", "Opt_3": "route", "Opt_4": "cycle", "Answer": "cycle", "Opt_1_def": "proof, signs", "Opt_2_def": "happening; event", "Opt_3_def": "the way to get to a place or a thing", "Opt_4_def": "a complete series of events or processes"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The owner of the organization has the ____ to make decisions.", "Opt_1": "authority", "Opt_2": "amount", "Opt_3": "victory", "Opt_4": "command", "Answer": "authority", "Opt_1_def": "control (right to control)", "Opt_2_def": "how much there is of something", "Opt_3_def": "win", "Opt_4_def": "control"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The wishes of parents must not always ____ the recommendations of the teachers about the course choices of the child.", "Opt_1": "manifest", "Opt_2": "respect", "Opt_3": "override", "Opt_4": "fear", "Answer": "override", "Opt_1_def": "show", "Opt_2_def": "to think positively about someone; to tolerate or avoid interfering with something", "Opt_3_def": "to take precedence over; to disregard", "Opt_4_def": "to be concerned or frightened about"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "A serious problem of nuclear power is where and how to ____ of the radioactive waste.", "Opt_1": "dispose", "Opt_2": "preserve", "Opt_3": "inquire", "Opt_4": "control", "Answer": "dispose", "Opt_1_def": "to get rid of", "Opt_2_def": "forward,\" said Michele Gougeon.", "Opt_3_def": "to ask", "Opt_4_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Use this form when you need to ____ accidentally deleted files from the network.", "Opt_1": "induce", "Opt_2": "restore", "Opt_3": "abandon", "Opt_4": "magnify", "Answer": "restore", "Opt_1_def": "to make happen; to force", "Opt_2_def": "to put back, create again", "Opt_3_def": "to leave or give up", "Opt_4_def": "to make or show larger"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "After the deadline, you will need to negotiate an extension with the TA ____ such cases, before taking it up with the professor.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "You have not made a clear enough ____ between the causes and effects of the disaster.", "Opt_1": "sample", "Opt_2": "contrast", "Opt_3": "disaster", "Opt_4": "asset", "Answer": "contrast", "Opt_1_def": "example; a smaller number of a larger collection", "Opt_2_def": "difference", "Opt_3_def": "a huge problem or failure", "Opt_4_def": "advantage"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Some people think it was no ____ that there was a terror alarm two days before the election.", "Opt_1": "fragment", "Opt_2": "coincidence", "Opt_3": "interpretation", "Opt_4": "record", "Answer": "coincidence", "Opt_1_def": "part of something", "Opt_2_def": "an uncommon happening of two things", "Opt_3_def": "explanation; assessment", "Opt_4_def": "evidence; documentation"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Honesty is not an ____ that most people associate with occupations such as politician or used-car salesman.", "Opt_1": "privilege", "Opt_2": "relationship", "Opt_3": "attribute", "Opt_4": "area", "Answer": "attribute", "Opt_1_def": "a right (to do something)", "Opt_2_def": "the way to things are connected", "Opt_3_def": "characteristic; property", "Opt_4_def": "field, sphere"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Since we can't ____ it directly, we need to infer it from the things we can ____.", "Opt_1": "confront", "Opt_2": "observe", "Opt_3": "dismiss", "Opt_4": "pursue", "Answer": "observe", "Opt_1_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)", "Opt_2_def": "to watch carefully", "Opt_3_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant", "Opt_4_def": "to follow (or do)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Spending months at a time in orbit, the scientists will be able to observe changes on the earth ____ them from day to day.", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "beneath", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "below", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "We view his behavior as very serious and we hope this ban will serve as an example.If you ____ the rules about downloading internet files, you will not be allowed to use the computer lab.", "Opt_1": "specify", "Opt_2": "exploit", "Opt_3": "violate", "Opt_4": "assimilate", "Answer": "violate", "Opt_1_def": "to state exactly", "Opt_2_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)", "Opt_3_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_4_def": "to take in"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Only seniors have the ____ of using this room. You will have to wait until you are in grade 12.", "Opt_1": "objection", "Opt_2": "privilege", "Opt_3": "dimension", "Opt_4": "range", "Answer": "privilege", "Opt_1_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval", "Opt_2_def": "a right (to do something)", "Opt_3_def": "importance; amount", "Opt_4_def": "extent, distance between two points"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Your grades will continue to ____ unless you start working harder.", "Opt_1": "prefer", "Opt_2": "modify", "Opt_3": "deteriorate", "Opt_4": "solve", "Answer": "deteriorate", "Opt_1_def": "to like better", "Opt_2_def": "to change", "Opt_3_def": "to get worse", "Opt_4_def": "to find an answer"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Please note that section 5 is the most important, and ____ it should constitute the majority of your journal entry.", "Opt_1": "largely", "Opt_2": "hence", "Opt_3": "universally", "Opt_4": "furthermore", "Answer": "hence", "Opt_1_def": "mostly", "Opt_2_def": "so, therefore", "Opt_3_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_4_def": "also, in addition"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Two thousand years from now, an archaeologist will find little ____ of the millions of web pages that have been updated in the last hour.", "Opt_1": "context", "Opt_2": "coincidence", "Opt_3": "trace", "Opt_4": "phenomenon", "Answer": "trace", "Opt_1_def": "the place or situation in which something is found", "Opt_2_def": "an uncommon happening of two things", "Opt_3_def": "sign; indication; evidence", "Opt_4_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Most students agree that teachers need ____ them on how much they have learned.", "Opt_1": "assess", "Opt_2": "insert", "Opt_3": "respect", "Opt_4": "encourage", "Answer": "assess", "Opt_1_def": "to judge or test", "Opt_2_def": "to put in", "Opt_3_def": "to think positively about someone; to tolerate or avoid interfering with something", "Opt_4_def": "to move someone to do something by positive talk; support or help"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The additional time is necessary to enable him to make a ____ decision on an Alaska natural gas transportation system.", "Opt_1": "sound", "Opt_2": "severe", "Opt_3": "abstract", "Opt_4": "ordinary", "Answer": "sound", "Opt_1_def": "good; strong", "Opt_2_def": "serious, harsh", "Opt_3_def": "not specific or concrete", "Opt_4_def": "usual, typical, every day"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "After the deadline, you will need to negotiate an extension with the TA ____ such cases, before taking it up with the professor.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The thesis is unoriginal and lacks insight into the ____ issues.", "Opt_1": "physical", "Opt_2": "spontaneous", "Opt_3": "fundamental", "Opt_4": "key", "Answer": "key", "Opt_1_def": "of the body", "Opt_2_def": "happening without warning or planning", "Opt_3_def": "very important", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "All campus party noise must ____ by 12:00 Midnight.", "Opt_1": "consult", "Opt_2": "include", "Opt_3": "cease", "Opt_4": "claim", "Answer": "cease", "Opt_1_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)", "Opt_2_def": "to put in; to have in", "Opt_3_def": "to stop", "Opt_4_def": "to state to be true"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Parents have ____ over their children until the children leave home.", "Opt_1": "schedule", "Opt_2": "structure", "Opt_3": "authority", "Opt_4": "portion", "Answer": "authority", "Opt_1_def": "timetable", "Opt_2_def": "the way something is made or organized", "Opt_3_def": "control (right to control)", "Opt_4_def": "part, amount"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "In this article, a novel way of teaching chemistry is presented that uses ____ music and chemical lyrics to educate.", "Opt_1": "contemporary", "Opt_2": "vast", "Opt_3": "scarce", "Opt_4": "profound", "Answer": "contemporary", "Opt_1_def": "of this time, happening now", "Opt_2_def": "very large", "Opt_3_def": "rare, not abundant", "Opt_4_def": "deep; great; serious"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "You need to ____ your work a little more closely for silly spelling or punctuation errors.", "Opt_1": "signify", "Opt_2": "join", "Opt_3": "inspect", "Opt_4": "appreciate", "Answer": "inspect", "Opt_1_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_2_def": "to become a member (of an organization; to get together with others", "Opt_3_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_4_def": "to understand (the value of someone or something)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Therefore, it is important to ____ low birth weight infants according to their weight for their gestational age.", "Opt_1": "classify", "Opt_2": "append", "Opt_3": "manufacture", "Opt_4": "frustrate", "Answer": "classify", "Opt_1_def": "to put into a category or class", "Opt_2_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)", "Opt_3_def": "to produce (with machines)", "Opt_4_def": "to stop or prevent"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Even more extraordinary, every child ____ one was more than willing to state his or her name to the stranger.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "A feeling prevailed that there were no rules at all on a campus that, only a few years earlier, prided itself on the implementation of ____ regulations.", "Opt_1": "strict", "Opt_2": "superior", "Opt_3": "accurate", "Opt_4": "odd", "Answer": "strict", "Opt_1_def": "hard, not changeable", "Opt_2_def": "better", "Opt_3_def": "exact, containing no mistakes", "Opt_4_def": "strange, unusual"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government has decided to revise it proposals to increase ____ tax after massive demonstrations on the streets of the capital city.", "Opt_1": "income", "Opt_2": "fallacy", "Opt_3": "incident", "Opt_4": "proportion", "Answer": "income", "Opt_1_def": "money earned", "Opt_2_def": "mistake; false belief", "Opt_3_def": "happening; event", "Opt_4_def": "amount; number; percentage"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "When a ____ court heard the case, it found the policy did not violate students' free-speech rights.", "Opt_1": "influence", "Opt_2": "hypothesis", "Opt_3": "district", "Opt_4": "entity", "Answer": "district", "Opt_1_def": "effect", "Opt_2_def": "idea or prediction", "Opt_3_def": "region of a city", "Opt_4_def": "thing; body; organization"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Unfortunately, hunger is no ____ problem in the United States, where the disparity between the affluent and the indigent is considerable.", "Opt_1": "compatible", "Opt_2": "minor", "Opt_3": "trivial", "Opt_4": "adjacent", "Answer": "minor", "Opt_1_def": "able to work with someone or something else", "Opt_2_def": "small, not important", "Opt_3_def": "not important", "Opt_4_def": "next to"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "DeRosa's success is a genuine example of how the right ____ and excellent faculty really can cause a scholarly transformation.", "Opt_1": "stage", "Opt_2": "finance", "Opt_3": "environment", "Opt_4": "opportunity", "Answer": "environment", "Opt_1_def": "period of time, part of a process", "Opt_2_def": "to do with money and payment", "Opt_3_def": "the world around us", "Opt_4_def": "chance"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "I do not ____ about your right to an opinion, but I do ____ about your inability to see the truth when it is explained to you.", "Opt_1": "protest", "Opt_2": "allocate", "Opt_3": "collapse", "Opt_4": "descend", "Answer": "protest", "Opt_1_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_2_def": "to give to (to promise to give)", "Opt_3_def": "to fall down completely and heavily; to fail", "Opt_4_def": "to go down"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "There are ____ ways that you can improve your English. Probably the best is to do plenty of reading.", "Opt_1": "overall", "Opt_2": "various", "Opt_3": "absent", "Opt_4": "conscious", "Answer": "various", "Opt_1_def": "general", "Opt_2_def": "several, of different kinds", "Opt_3_def": "being not there; missing", "Opt_4_def": "aware, knowing"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "In many cases what was once an ____ is now taken for granted. Remarkable inventions, once assimilated into daily life, become routine.", "Opt_1": "source", "Opt_2": "role", "Opt_3": "innovation", "Opt_4": "atmosphere", "Answer": "innovation", "Opt_1_def": "where something begins, where you can find something", "Opt_2_def": "job or function", "Opt_3_def": "new object or idea", "Opt_4_def": "mood among people or groups"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Teenage alcohol ____ is an enormous problem in some UK cities.", "Opt_1": "restrict", "Opt_2": "inhibit", "Opt_3": "encounter", "Opt_4": "abuse", "Answer": "abuse", "Opt_1_def": "to limit", "Opt_2_def": "to prevent or stop", "Opt_3_def": "to meet or experience", "Opt_4_def": "to treat someone or something badly"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "If you ____ from the course by February 12, the course will be deleted from your enrollment record.", "Opt_1": "withdraw", "Opt_2": "proceed", "Opt_3": "complicate", "Opt_4": "exhaust", "Answer": "withdraw", "Opt_1_def": "to go back or take away", "Opt_2_def": "to go forward (and do ..)", "Opt_3_def": "to make things more complex or difficult", "Opt_4_def": "to use up"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "A ____ of this cement three tenthousandths of an inch thick over one square inch will support a weight of 7000 pounds.", "Opt_1": "exercise", "Opt_2": "priority", "Opt_3": "layer", "Opt_4": "plenty", "Answer": "layer", "Opt_1_def": "a piece of work, activity", "Opt_2_def": "first and most important task", "Opt_3_def": "level", "Opt_4_def": "many, lots of"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Illegal immigration is not the ____ reason so many poor young blacks are on the streets and why some turn to gangs, guns and drug dealing.", "Opt_1": "perpetual", "Opt_2": "prime", "Opt_3": "necessary", "Opt_4": "inevitable", "Answer": "prime", "Opt_1_def": "continuing for ever; never disappearing", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "needed; very important", "Opt_4_def": "cannot be changed or avoided; obvious"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "This forecast showed much less ____ than expected by the district's officials and residents.", "Opt_1": "struggle", "Opt_2": "context", "Opt_3": "survey", "Opt_4": "growth", "Answer": "growth", "Opt_1_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome", "Opt_2_def": "the place or situation in which something is found", "Opt_3_def": "questionnaire; information gained by questioning people or data", "Opt_4_def": "development, increase"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The communication medium is a computer, phone line, and modem; the student must have ____ to the necessary equipment.", "Opt_1": "access", "Opt_2": "potential", "Opt_3": "attribute", "Opt_4": "condition", "Answer": "access", "Opt_1_def": "the right to enter or use", "Opt_2_def": "good possibility", "Opt_3_def": "characteristic; property", "Opt_4_def": "state"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Visit our web page Phases of the Moon for a more detailed explanation and a clear ____ that shows the phases of our moon.", "Opt_1": "liberty", "Opt_2": "diagram", "Opt_3": "income", "Opt_4": "delay", "Answer": "diagram", "Opt_1_def": "freedom", "Opt_2_def": "a type of picture or chart", "Opt_3_def": "money earned", "Opt_4_def": "lateness"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "There are ____ laws that govern the trade in rainforest wood.", "Opt_1": "strict", "Opt_2": "final", "Opt_3": "obvious", "Opt_4": "cautious", "Answer": "strict", "Opt_1_def": "hard, not changeable", "Opt_2_def": "last", "Opt_3_def": "clear, evident", "Opt_4_def": "careful"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It is a ____ that Japanese girls are quiet. You should hear them on the bus on a school trip!", "Opt_1": "role", "Opt_2": "volume", "Opt_3": "stereotype", "Opt_4": "mixture", "Answer": "stereotype", "Opt_1_def": "job or function", "Opt_2_def": "amount", "Opt_3_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)", "Opt_4_def": "combination"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The last ____ of the flooded village was evacuated by a helicopter.", "Opt_1": "record", "Opt_2": "plenty", "Opt_3": "resident", "Opt_4": "anomaly", "Answer": "resident", "Opt_1_def": "evidence; documentation", "Opt_2_def": "many, lots of", "Opt_3_def": "a person who lives in a place", "Opt_4_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If you submit your application in person, there will be a ____ of up to 48 hours following receipt of your application before you can enroll for classes.", "Opt_1": "resident", "Opt_2": "condition", "Opt_3": "procedure", "Opt_4": "delay", "Answer": "delay", "Opt_1_def": "a person who lives in a place", "Opt_2_def": "state", "Opt_3_def": "the way to do something", "Opt_4_def": "lateness"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It is ____ that you hand in the essay on time. If you don't, you will fail the course.", "Opt_1": "neutral", "Opt_2": "crucial", "Opt_3": "abnormal", "Opt_4": "valuable", "Answer": "crucial", "Opt_1_def": "neither for nor against; neither positive nor negative", "Opt_2_def": "extremely important", "Opt_3_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_4_def": "worth a lot of money; important"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The court concluded that schools could not ____ disabled students whose disability causes their disruptive conduct.", "Opt_1": "recur", "Opt_2": "expel", "Opt_3": "derive", "Opt_4": "broadcast", "Answer": "expel", "Opt_1_def": "to happen again", "Opt_2_def": "to drive or push out", "Opt_3_def": "to come from or get from", "Opt_4_def": "to tell or transmit (often by means of a television programme)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Students needed to devote ____ time to recognizing the three basic tenses (past, present, and future) and using the appropriate tense in their own writing.", "Opt_1": "intrinsic", "Opt_2": "considerable", "Opt_3": "concise", "Opt_4": "relevant", "Answer": "considerable", "Opt_1_def": "belonging to; inherent in", "Opt_2_def": "very big; very much", "Opt_3_def": "short, not detailed", "Opt_4_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Using a new ____ to trap and measure single particles with lasers, an international group of researchers have demonstrated that Brownian motion of a single particle behaves differently than Einstein theorized one century ago.", "Opt_1": "item", "Opt_2": "technique", "Opt_3": "phenomenon", "Opt_4": "deed", "Answer": "technique", "Opt_1_def": "thing, element", "Opt_2_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)", "Opt_4_def": "an action"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "My science teacher returned my homework and told me to do it again. She said I had to use the ____ format for lab reports.", "Opt_1": "skill", "Opt_2": "fault", "Opt_3": "standard", "Opt_4": "habit", "Answer": "standard", "Opt_1_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)", "Opt_2_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem", "Opt_3_def": "quality", "Opt_4_def": "something you do regularly"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "You will need to ____ the images and present them as a narrative or the story of destruction in New Orleans after Katrina.", "Opt_1": "achieve", "Opt_2": "integrate", "Opt_3": "protect", "Opt_4": "annotate", "Answer": "annotate", "Opt_1_def": "to gain or get something (often academic success)", "Opt_2_def": "to fit into a new situation", "Opt_3_def": "to keep something out of danger", "Opt_4_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government's proposals will have a ____ effect on the education of every child in the country.", "Opt_1": "faint", "Opt_2": "commercial", "Opt_3": "profound", "Opt_4": "aware", "Answer": "profound", "Opt_1_def": "not strong", "Opt_2_def": "to do with business", "Opt_3_def": "deep; great; serious", "Opt_4_def": "knowing"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Though Sima and Codreanu both attempted to prevent the murder, it ____ took place, and produced harsh consequences.", "Opt_1": "nevertheless", "Opt_2": "especially", "Opt_3": "barely", "Opt_4": "extremely", "Answer": "nevertheless", "Opt_1_def": "however (although / despite that)", "Opt_2_def": "particularly", "Opt_3_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_4_def": "very"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "You will not be able to request a ____ name unless you provide the following information.", "Opt_1": "role", "Opt_2": "power", "Opt_3": "domain", "Opt_4": "stereotype", "Answer": "domain", "Opt_1_def": "job or function", "Opt_2_def": "the right or authority to do something", "Opt_3_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_4_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Do not ____ the period after an abbreviation such as in. (for inch), which could be confused with the word in.", "Opt_1": "praise", "Opt_2": "omit", "Opt_3": "belong", "Opt_4": "retire", "Answer": "omit", "Opt_1_def": "to express approval about something someone has done", "Opt_2_def": "to leave something out or not do something", "Opt_3_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone", "Opt_4_def": "to stop working"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Most educational institutions have a required ____ for citations and references.", "Opt_1": "profession", "Opt_2": "outcome", "Opt_3": "format", "Opt_4": "assignment", "Answer": "format", "Opt_1_def": "job; occupation", "Opt_2_def": "result", "Opt_3_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting", "Opt_4_def": "a task; the giving of a task"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Germany had to ____ a harsh peace treaty after being defeated in the first world war.", "Opt_1": "launch", "Opt_2": "ban", "Opt_3": "accept", "Opt_4": "attain", "Answer": "accept", "Opt_1_def": "to begin", "Opt_2_def": "to prohibit or forbid", "Opt_3_def": "to agree (to have)", "Opt_4_def": "to get, achieve"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government had to acknowledge that it had not succeeded in its plans to ____ child poverty.", "Opt_1": "risk", "Opt_2": "base", "Opt_3": "presume", "Opt_4": "reduce", "Answer": "reduce", "Opt_1_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure", "Opt_2_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something", "Opt_3_def": "to believe, assume", "Opt_4_def": "to make smaller or shorter"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Mobile phones have made it ____ to contact someone anytime and anywhere.", "Opt_1": "inevitable", "Opt_2": "feasible", "Opt_3": "subjective", "Opt_4": "pure", "Answer": "feasible", "Opt_1_def": "cannot be changed or avoided; obvious", "Opt_2_def": "possible", "Opt_3_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling", "Opt_4_def": "complete, 100%"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The company's ____ was to increase sales by 20%. Due to the high cost of oil in the past year, it was not successful.", "Opt_1": "effect", "Opt_2": "intention", "Opt_3": "rate", "Opt_4": "power", "Answer": "intention", "Opt_1_def": "result", "Opt_2_def": "plan, aim", "Opt_3_def": "quantity; proportion; speed", "Opt_4_def": "the right or authority to do something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The government has taken the wise decision to ____ the public before passing the proposed law.", "Opt_1": "prefer", "Opt_2": "dictate", "Opt_3": "refer", "Opt_4": "consult", "Answer": "consult", "Opt_1_def": "to like better", "Opt_2_def": "to tell someone what to do", "Opt_3_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean", "Opt_4_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "She came to school yesterday ____ feeling very unwell.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If your ____ is temporary and is impacting only attendance, make sure you follow up with your professors and contact the Dean of Students Office.", "Opt_1": "journey", "Opt_2": "condition", "Opt_3": "episode", "Opt_4": "component", "Answer": "condition", "Opt_1_def": "a long trip to a different place", "Opt_2_def": "state", "Opt_3_def": "period of time", "Opt_4_def": "part of; an element of"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The internet has made it possible for a community of people with ____ interests to get together online, even if they don't live close to each other.", "Opt_1": "reasonable", "Opt_2": "consistent", "Opt_3": "similar", "Opt_4": "superior", "Answer": "similar", "Opt_1_def": "acceptable, quite good", "Opt_2_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same", "Opt_3_def": "like, almost the same as", "Opt_4_def": "better"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "This is the completely rational response of a country that has no hope of defeating the United States in battle but ____ wants to insure that it isn't attacked.", "Opt_1": "naturally", "Opt_2": "absolutely", "Opt_3": "simply", "Opt_4": "nevertheless", "Answer": "nevertheless", "Opt_1_def": "of course, obviously", "Opt_2_def": "completely; 100%", "Opt_3_def": "completely; just; only", "Opt_4_def": "however (although / despite that)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Two thousand years from now, an archaeologist will find little ____ of the millions of web pages that have been updated in the last hour.", "Opt_1": "result", "Opt_2": "outcome", "Opt_3": "trace", "Opt_4": "episode", "Answer": "trace", "Opt_1_def": "outcome, effect", "Opt_2_def": "result", "Opt_3_def": "sign; indication; evidence", "Opt_4_def": "period of time"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Gladwin County decided to ____ the sale of dogs from its animal shelter in order to give citizens the chance to review the county's earlier decision.", "Opt_1": "retire", "Opt_2": "suspend", "Opt_3": "cease", "Opt_4": "expose", "Answer": "suspend", "Opt_1_def": "to stop working", "Opt_2_def": "to stop (often for a short time only)", "Opt_3_def": "to stop", "Opt_4_def": "to uncover, reveal"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It is less widely recognized, moreover, that growth and globalization also threaten to ____ environmental damage.", "Opt_1": "conform", "Opt_2": "cease", "Opt_3": "collaborate", "Opt_4": "accelerate", "Answer": "accelerate", "Opt_1_def": "to do what is required", "Opt_2_def": "to stop", "Opt_3_def": "to work together", "Opt_4_def": "to get or make faster"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Most governments ____ to negotiate with kidnappers.", "Opt_1": "refuse", "Opt_2": "convey", "Opt_3": "solve", "Opt_4": "seek", "Answer": "refuse", "Opt_1_def": "to not do something that someone wants you to do", "Opt_2_def": "to pass on to another person (often by speaking)", "Opt_3_def": "to find an answer", "Opt_4_def": "to look for or want"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Plagiarism is easy to ____ but often hard to define. This is partly because the legal rules differ sharply from the ethical ones.", "Opt_1": "realize", "Opt_2": "protect", "Opt_3": "condemn", "Opt_4": "distribute", "Answer": "condemn", "Opt_1_def": "to come to know or understand", "Opt_2_def": "to keep something out of danger", "Opt_3_def": "to express strong disapproval", "Opt_4_def": "to give out"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Financial ____ is the term we use to describe a variety of funds available to help students and their families finance the cost of a Berry College education.", "Opt_1": "aid", "Opt_2": "rank", "Opt_3": "struggle", "Opt_4": "volume", "Answer": "aid", "Opt_1_def": "help (often financial help)", "Opt_2_def": "position (in a list or hierarchy)", "Opt_3_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome", "Opt_4_def": "amount"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The school is constructing a new science block ____ the sports field.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "prior", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "before"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The court concluded that schools could not ____ disabled students whose disability causes their disruptive conduct.", "Opt_1": "expel", "Opt_2": "speculate", "Opt_3": "oppose", "Opt_4": "determine", "Answer": "expel", "Opt_1_def": "to drive or push out", "Opt_2_def": "to think and talk about (often future events)", "Opt_3_def": "to be against or fight against something", "Opt_4_def": "to find out; to establish or identify; state"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It is a particular privilege to welcome several San Francisco State University alumni who ____ all that we commemorate today.", "Opt_1": "suppose", "Opt_2": "embody", "Opt_3": "notice", "Opt_4": "combine", "Answer": "embody", "Opt_1_def": "to think, imagine", "Opt_2_def": "to be a good example of ..", "Opt_3_def": "to see or realize", "Opt_4_def": "to put or go together"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The professor meets with each student for a half-hour private tutorial ____ three times during the semester.", "Opt_1": "simultaneously", "Opt_2": "absolutely", "Opt_3": "naturally", "Opt_4": "approximately", "Answer": "approximately", "Opt_1_def": "at the same time", "Opt_2_def": "completely; 100%", "Opt_3_def": "of course, obviously", "Opt_4_def": "about; not exactly"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Some people ____ the USA of starting the war in Iraq in order to gain control of its oilfields.", "Opt_1": "enforce", "Opt_2": "precede", "Opt_3": "differentiate", "Opt_4": "accuse", "Answer": "accuse", "Opt_1_def": "to make something happen (particularly a law or regulation)", "Opt_2_def": "to go or be before someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to make different; to see the difference", "Opt_4_def": "to blame"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "A student whose total absences in a course, excused or unexcused, exceed ten per trimester is ____ to fail the course.", "Opt_1": "liable", "Opt_2": "several", "Opt_3": "outstanding", "Opt_4": "valuable", "Answer": "liable", "Opt_1_def": "likely to happen; at risk of happening", "Opt_2_def": "many (about 6 or seven)", "Opt_3_def": "excellent", "Opt_4_def": "worth a lot of money; important"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The most basic ____ to develop is observational drawing skills.", "Opt_1": "technique", "Opt_2": "belief", "Opt_3": "majority", "Opt_4": "entity", "Answer": "technique", "Opt_1_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "what you think; what you believe in", "Opt_3_def": "more than 50%", "Opt_4_def": "thing; body; organization"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Miller, long a ____ of Switzerland, broke with the school of traditional psychoanalysis over the issue.", "Opt_1": "limit", "Opt_2": "principle", "Opt_3": "loss", "Opt_4": "resident", "Answer": "resident", "Opt_1_def": "extent, boundary", "Opt_2_def": "rule", "Opt_3_def": "removal or reduction", "Opt_4_def": "a person who lives in a place"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "My ____ this term is to improve my mathematics and science grades.", "Opt_1": "factor", "Opt_2": "administration", "Opt_3": "impact", "Opt_4": "goal", "Answer": "goal", "Opt_1_def": "an aspect to be considered", "Opt_2_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school", "Opt_3_def": "effect", "Opt_4_def": "aim or intention"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Repeat this procedure until only a small amount of ____ is released when it is vented.", "Opt_1": "pressure", "Opt_2": "sum", "Opt_3": "magnitude", "Opt_4": "defect", "Answer": "pressure", "Opt_1_def": "force; influence; stress", "Opt_2_def": "an amount of money, total", "Opt_3_def": "size; amount", "Opt_4_def": "problem; mistake"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "What do western Louisville and the Appalachian region have in common ____ being two of the poorest areas in Kentucky?", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "prior", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "before"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The new ____ should help to reduce the number of problems resulting from adjustment to semester length.", "Opt_1": "procedure", "Opt_2": "sum", "Opt_3": "attack", "Opt_4": "technique", "Answer": "procedure", "Opt_1_def": "the way to do something", "Opt_2_def": "an amount of money, total", "Opt_3_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage", "Opt_4_def": "a method of doing something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The prime minister is today expected to ____ the date of the next election.", "Opt_1": "improve", "Opt_2": "ban", "Opt_3": "announce", "Opt_4": "protect", "Answer": "announce", "Opt_1_def": "to get better", "Opt_2_def": "to prohibit or forbid", "Opt_3_def": "to state (often in an official way)", "Opt_4_def": "to keep something out of danger"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The technology to ____ carbon monoxide into liquid fuel has been around a long time.", "Opt_1": "convert", "Opt_2": "manipulate", "Opt_3": "obtain", "Opt_4": "culminate", "Answer": "convert", "Opt_1_def": "to change from one thing to another", "Opt_2_def": "to (use and) change", "Opt_3_def": "to get", "Opt_4_def": "to end"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The ____ position of the school has improved since the government reduced its tax requirements.", "Opt_1": "economic", "Opt_2": "obvious", "Opt_3": "legal", "Opt_4": "strict", "Answer": "economic", "Opt_1_def": "financial; to do with money", "Opt_2_def": "clear, evident", "Opt_3_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)", "Opt_4_def": "hard, not changeable"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "In our society, which is far from ____ in its beliefs and values, reaching consensus on any issue is significantly difficult.", "Opt_1": "outstanding", "Opt_2": "uniform", "Opt_3": "stable", "Opt_4": "major", "Answer": "uniform", "Opt_1_def": "excellent", "Opt_2_def": "having the same qualities", "Opt_3_def": "not changing; not easy to change", "Opt_4_def": "important, large"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The course introduces students to the structure and function of cities and ways planners ____ urban problems.", "Opt_1": "solve", "Opt_2": "trade", "Opt_3": "prevail", "Opt_4": "proceed", "Answer": "solve", "Opt_1_def": "to find an answer", "Opt_2_def": "to exchange products or services", "Opt_3_def": "to succeed; to overcome", "Opt_4_def": "to go forward (and do ..)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "You will ____ many difficulties but if you persist in your efforts, you will succeed.", "Opt_1": "degenerate", "Opt_2": "encounter", "Opt_3": "remain", "Opt_4": "infer", "Answer": "encounter", "Opt_1_def": "to get worse", "Opt_2_def": "to meet or experience", "Opt_3_def": "to stay; still exist", "Opt_4_def": "to come to a conclusion about something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "At no point in our deliberations are numbers employed in a way that would trigger an ____ decision to offer or deny admission.", "Opt_1": "intense", "Opt_2": "valuable", "Opt_3": "automatic", "Opt_4": "instant", "Answer": "automatic", "Opt_1_def": "strong, extreme", "Opt_2_def": "worth a lot of money; important", "Opt_3_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually", "Opt_4_def": "immediate"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Many a ____ that was once believed by everyone later proves to be false - e.g. that the sun goes around the earth.", "Opt_1": "forecast", "Opt_2": "career", "Opt_3": "theory", "Opt_4": "sphere", "Answer": "theory", "Opt_1_def": "prediction", "Opt_2_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_3_def": "idea or hypothesis", "Opt_4_def": "area of interest"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "In this class, we will ____ the controversy about the risks generated by the war on terror.", "Opt_1": "trigger", "Opt_2": "examine", "Opt_3": "approach", "Opt_4": "compete", "Answer": "examine", "Opt_1_def": "to (cause to) start", "Opt_2_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_3_def": "to near; to get closer", "Opt_4_def": "to try and win against someone or something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "This position is the ____ chance to learn about the many different areas of marketing and business operations in a hands-on environment.", "Opt_1": "strict", "Opt_2": "mental", "Opt_3": "ultimate", "Opt_4": "deficient", "Answer": "ultimate", "Opt_1_def": "hard, not changeable", "Opt_2_def": "of the brain or mind", "Opt_3_def": "final or most important", "Opt_4_def": "poor, lacking in quantity or quality"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "We must reverse the ____ of a growing incidence of campus hate crimes.", "Opt_1": "symptom", "Opt_2": "friction", "Opt_3": "criterion", "Opt_4": "trend", "Answer": "trend", "Opt_1_def": "sign (often of a disease or other problem)", "Opt_2_def": "problems or arguments between two people or groups", "Opt_3_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something", "Opt_4_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Do I have to be a member of the Society to ____ a paper?", "Opt_1": "conceal", "Opt_2": "allege", "Opt_3": "omit", "Opt_4": "submit", "Answer": "submit", "Opt_1_def": "to hide", "Opt_2_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_3_def": "to leave something out or not do something", "Opt_4_def": "to give; to send"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The school does a lot to ____ new families, with information meetings, translation services, etc.", "Opt_1": "restore", "Opt_2": "spread", "Opt_3": "anticipate", "Opt_4": "integrate", "Answer": "integrate", "Opt_1_def": "to put back, create again", "Opt_2_def": "to move (over a wider area)", "Opt_3_def": "to expect", "Opt_4_def": "to fit into a new situation"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The powerful hold that the empire of Egypt had on Palestine at this time would not have permitted the rise of a significant ____ such as Israel.", "Opt_1": "asset", "Opt_2": "ignorance", "Opt_3": "entity", "Opt_4": "decision", "Answer": "entity", "Opt_1_def": "advantage", "Opt_2_def": "lack of knowledge", "Opt_3_def": "thing; body; organization", "Opt_4_def": "intention to do something, choice"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Therefore, if a calf has not received an ____ amount of quality colostrum, the calf may not be able to resist disease.", "Opt_1": "poor", "Opt_2": "appropriate", "Opt_3": "adequate", "Opt_4": "strict", "Answer": "adequate", "Opt_1_def": "bad, unsatisfactory", "Opt_2_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable", "Opt_3_def": "good enough; ok", "Opt_4_def": "hard, not changeable"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "When he left home he planned to ____ from Christianity to Buddhism, but then he decided he didn't believe in any god.", "Opt_1": "convert", "Opt_2": "involve", "Opt_3": "retreat", "Opt_4": "assemble", "Answer": "convert", "Opt_1_def": "to change from one thing to another", "Opt_2_def": "to include or mean", "Opt_3_def": "to go back", "Opt_4_def": "to get, put or bring together"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Over the course of the period there is a steady ____ in the status of the painter, sculptor, and architect and a growing sympathy expressed for the visual arts.", "Opt_1": "drawback", "Opt_2": "topic", "Opt_3": "status", "Opt_4": "rise", "Answer": "rise", "Opt_1_def": "disadvantage, problem", "Opt_2_def": "area of interest or discussion", "Opt_3_def": "position, standing", "Opt_4_def": "to go up"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Very few companies can ____ cars of the quality of German makes such as BMW or Mercedes.", "Opt_1": "distinguish", "Opt_2": "isolate", "Opt_3": "control", "Opt_4": "manufacture", "Answer": "manufacture", "Opt_1_def": "to make clear the differences between two things", "Opt_2_def": "to separate something or someone from others", "Opt_3_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone", "Opt_4_def": "to produce (with machines)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Marat used his ____ ideas to arouse the people, and set himself apart.", "Opt_1": "current", "Opt_2": "neutral", "Opt_3": "radical", "Opt_4": "distinct", "Answer": "radical", "Opt_1_def": "happening now", "Opt_2_def": "neither for nor against; neither positive nor negative", "Opt_3_def": "extreme, strong", "Opt_4_def": "clear and strong"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Dr. Pruitt said that he was very ____ that all aspects of the law, as well as any other concerns, would be closely looked at prior to any deal being made.", "Opt_1": "technical", "Opt_2": "arbitrary", "Opt_3": "profound", "Opt_4": "confident", "Answer": "confident", "Opt_1_def": "to do with machines or the way things work", "Opt_2_def": "not planned or thought-out; not considering the wishes of others", "Opt_3_def": "deep; great; serious", "Opt_4_def": "sure that something will happen"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The new factory near the school will ____ parts for mobile phones.", "Opt_1": "form", "Opt_2": "manufacture", "Opt_3": "adhere", "Opt_4": "reform", "Answer": "manufacture", "Opt_1_def": "to make (into a shape)", "Opt_2_def": "to produce (with machines)", "Opt_3_def": "to keep to; to follow", "Opt_4_def": "to change and improve"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "A significant ____ of the continent is characterized by water scarcity.", "Opt_1": "obligation", "Opt_2": "role", "Opt_3": "proportion", "Opt_4": "entity", "Answer": "proportion", "Opt_1_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_2_def": "job or function", "Opt_3_def": "amount; number; percentage", "Opt_4_def": "thing; body; organization"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "This ____ ignorance was caused by the insufficient amount of media coverage on topic.", "Opt_1": "widespread", "Opt_2": "sole", "Opt_3": "liable", "Opt_4": "faint", "Answer": "widespread", "Opt_1_def": "common", "Opt_2_def": "only", "Opt_3_def": "likely to happen; at risk of happening", "Opt_4_def": "not strong"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Attendance will not constitute a specific percentage of your final grade, but if you miss more than two classes you will ____ fail this course.", "Opt_1": "furthermore", "Opt_2": "virtually", "Opt_3": "definitely", "Opt_4": "simply", "Answer": "definitely", "Opt_1_def": "also, in addition", "Opt_2_def": "almost", "Opt_3_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_4_def": "completely; just; only"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The ____ authority in the country is the President.", "Opt_1": "ultimate", "Opt_2": "regular", "Opt_3": "satisfactory", "Opt_4": "competent", "Answer": "ultimate", "Opt_1_def": "final or most important", "Opt_2_def": "predictable, following a pattern; normal", "Opt_3_def": "enough;OK", "Opt_4_def": "good at something (often a job)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The Bush administration will not back down on pursuing new sanctions against Iran over its nuclear program ____ questions about their effectiveness.", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Well done. The result of all your ____ is an fine grade in your ESL test.", "Opt_1": "labour", "Opt_2": "treatment", "Opt_3": "diagnosis", "Opt_4": "committee", "Answer": "labour", "Opt_1_def": "work", "Opt_2_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)", "Opt_3_def": "assessment of a situation (particularly of a problem)", "Opt_4_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Our results did not enable us to ____ whether SMR or MOEE had reached minimum values.", "Opt_1": "install", "Opt_2": "eliminate", "Opt_3": "determine", "Opt_4": "add", "Answer": "determine", "Opt_1_def": "to put in (often a machine or new system)", "Opt_2_def": "to dispose of", "Opt_3_def": "to find out; to establish or identify; state", "Opt_4_def": "to include; to give or say extra"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Doctors advise people to ____ the number of eggs they eat to 2-3 per week.", "Opt_1": "restrict", "Opt_2": "inspect", "Opt_3": "transfer", "Opt_4": "embody", "Answer": "restrict", "Opt_1_def": "to limit", "Opt_2_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_3_def": "to move to a different place or job", "Opt_4_def": "to be a good example of .."}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Students engaging in scheduled curricular work have ____ over other students.", "Opt_1": "limit", "Opt_2": "institution", "Opt_3": "priority", "Opt_4": "motive", "Answer": "priority", "Opt_1_def": "extent, boundary", "Opt_2_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom", "Opt_3_def": "first and most important task", "Opt_4_def": "reason"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "For my next step I would propose to the students certain distinctions that might at first glance seem to be completely ____ or valueless.", "Opt_1": "urban", "Opt_2": "secure", "Opt_3": "arbitrary", "Opt_4": "global", "Answer": "arbitrary", "Opt_1_def": "of the town or city", "Opt_2_def": "safe", "Opt_3_def": "not planned or thought-out; not considering the wishes of others", "Opt_4_def": "world"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The department may admit students of superior promise but ____ preparation, provided that such students correct their deficiencies.", "Opt_1": "severe", "Opt_2": "annual", "Opt_3": "deficient", "Opt_4": "several", "Answer": "deficient", "Opt_1_def": "serious, harsh", "Opt_2_def": "yearly", "Opt_3_def": "poor, lacking in quantity or quality", "Opt_4_def": "many (about 6 or seven)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "I'm sorry but the school has no ____ to educate children with severe learning problems.", "Opt_1": "friction", "Opt_2": "doubt", "Opt_3": "ability", "Opt_4": "boundary", "Answer": "ability", "Opt_1_def": "problems or arguments between two people or groups", "Opt_2_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)", "Opt_3_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well", "Opt_4_def": "limit, extent"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "At the end of the lesson please put the ____ back in the storeroom.", "Opt_1": "result", "Opt_2": "truth", "Opt_3": "priority", "Opt_4": "apparatus", "Answer": "apparatus", "Opt_1_def": "outcome, effect", "Opt_2_def": "actual reason or fact", "Opt_3_def": "first and most important task", "Opt_4_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Prices have risen by ____ 4% over the last 10 years.", "Opt_1": "approximately", "Opt_2": "gradually", "Opt_3": "dramatically", "Opt_4": "fairly", "Answer": "approximately", "Opt_1_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_2_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_3_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_4_def": "quite, somewhat"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Doctors ____ make mistakes which can have serious or even fatal consequences for their patients.", "Opt_1": "recently", "Opt_2": "largely", "Opt_3": "simultaneously", "Opt_4": "occasionally", "Answer": "occasionally", "Opt_1_def": "in the near past", "Opt_2_def": "mostly", "Opt_3_def": "at the same time", "Opt_4_def": "sometimes"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Many students who ____ a grade lower than they want, do so because they fail to annotate their texts.", "Opt_1": "contain", "Opt_2": "receive", "Opt_3": "replace", "Opt_4": "attain", "Answer": "receive", "Opt_1_def": "to have in it; to hold inside", "Opt_2_def": "to get", "Opt_3_def": "to put in or take the place of ..", "Opt_4_def": "to get, achieve"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The PBL ____ is rather time-consuming and requires the teacher to invest a lot of effort over an extended period of time.", "Opt_1": "component", "Opt_2": "survey", "Opt_3": "trend", "Opt_4": "method", "Answer": "method", "Opt_1_def": "part of; an element of", "Opt_2_def": "questionnaire; information gained by questioning people or data", "Opt_3_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "a way of doing something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Water is a useful and necessary thing, but it is not a ____ until someone builds a fence around the water source.", "Opt_1": "environment", "Opt_2": "commodity", "Opt_3": "sector", "Opt_4": "atmosphere", "Answer": "commodity", "Opt_1_def": "the world around us", "Opt_2_def": "a product; something you can buy", "Opt_3_def": "part; area", "Opt_4_def": "mood among people or groups"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The pharmacy does not have access to your medical record, thus is unable to ____ insurance information from the health forms.", "Opt_1": "obtain", "Opt_2": "interfere", "Opt_3": "advise", "Opt_4": "occupy", "Answer": "obtain", "Opt_1_def": "to get", "Opt_2_def": "to prevent; to harm", "Opt_3_def": "to say what someone should do; to give advice", "Opt_4_def": "to up space or time"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Remember that you ____ me \ufffd\ufffd20.", "Opt_1": "improve", "Opt_2": "owe", "Opt_3": "distribute", "Opt_4": "shrink", "Answer": "owe", "Opt_1_def": "to get better", "Opt_2_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)", "Opt_3_def": "to give out", "Opt_4_def": "to get smaller"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Stubbornness is a trait that is sometimes ____ and sometimes negative.", "Opt_1": "positive", "Opt_2": "novel", "Opt_3": "secure", "Opt_4": "artificial", "Answer": "positive", "Opt_1_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_2_def": "new", "Opt_3_def": "safe", "Opt_4_def": "not real or natural"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The ____ made no comment on the reasons for asking the student to leave the school.", "Opt_1": "abnormal", "Opt_2": "principal", "Opt_3": "utter", "Opt_4": "confident", "Answer": "principal", "Opt_1_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "complete, total", "Opt_4_def": "sure that something will happen"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Don't ____ me in your plan - I want nothing to do with it.", "Opt_1": "warn", "Opt_2": "realize", "Opt_3": "involve", "Opt_4": "prohibit", "Answer": "involve", "Opt_1_def": "to notify (of possible danger)", "Opt_2_def": "to come to know or understand", "Opt_3_def": "to include or mean", "Opt_4_def": "to ban, disallow"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The first of the allegations came from a woman who, in the opinion of the Committee, was not a ____ witness.", "Opt_1": "credible", "Opt_2": "reliable", "Opt_3": "cautious", "Opt_4": "brief", "Answer": "credible", "Opt_1_def": "believable", "Opt_2_def": "can be trusted, does not let you down \r\n", "Opt_3_def": "careful", "Opt_4_def": "short"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The school has a ____ of approximately one teacher for every fifteen students.", "Opt_1": "pressure", "Opt_2": "version", "Opt_3": "rise", "Opt_4": "ratio", "Answer": "ratio", "Opt_1_def": "force; influence; stress", "Opt_2_def": "form", "Opt_3_def": "to go up", "Opt_4_def": "mathematical relationship between two amount"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "How do we ____ the essential and perpetual problem of dealing with our own waste?", "Opt_1": "offend", "Opt_2": "approach", "Opt_3": "adapt", "Opt_4": "differentiate", "Answer": "approach", "Opt_1_def": "to go against; to upset", "Opt_2_def": "to near; to get closer", "Opt_3_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)", "Opt_4_def": "to make different; to see the difference"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The grade will be amended but the former grade will remain on the record with an ____ notation.", "Opt_1": "fortunate", "Opt_2": "effective", "Opt_3": "appropriate", "Opt_4": "random", "Answer": "appropriate", "Opt_1_def": "lucky", "Opt_2_def": "good, working well", "Opt_3_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable", "Opt_4_def": "by chance; without any sequence"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Many economists ____ the rise in prices with the government's decision to tax imports.", "Opt_1": "culminate", "Opt_2": "associate", "Opt_3": "arise", "Opt_4": "attend", "Answer": "associate", "Opt_1_def": "to end", "Opt_2_def": "to link to; to make a connection to", "Opt_3_def": "to happen", "Opt_4_def": "to go to, to be present at"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If your exam is closed book, you will want to prepare an ____ that will assist you in studying until the day of the exam.", "Opt_1": "region", "Opt_2": "instinct", "Opt_3": "outline", "Opt_4": "code", "Answer": "outline", "Opt_1_def": "part of a place", "Opt_2_def": "natural feeling or reaction", "Opt_3_def": "plan or summary", "Opt_4_def": "a set of rules"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Though Sima and Codreanu both attempted to prevent the murder, it ____ took place, and produced harsh consequences.", "Opt_1": "indirectly", "Opt_2": "overly", "Opt_3": "generally", "Opt_4": "nevertheless", "Answer": "nevertheless", "Opt_1_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate", "Opt_2_def": "too", "Opt_3_def": "usually", "Opt_4_def": "however (although / despite that)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The number of students at the school with learning difficulties has begun to ____ in the last few years.", "Opt_1": "deteriorate", "Opt_2": "decline", "Opt_3": "explain", "Opt_4": "gather", "Answer": "decline", "Opt_1_def": "to get worse", "Opt_2_def": "to go down or get worse", "Opt_3_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to bring or get together"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It is an advantage for a politician to be able to give a clear but ____ statement of what he or she believes in.", "Opt_1": "concise", "Opt_2": "original", "Opt_3": "major", "Opt_4": "visual", "Answer": "concise", "Opt_1_def": "short, not detailed", "Opt_2_def": "the first of its kind", "Opt_3_def": "important, large", "Opt_4_def": "to do with sight and seeing"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "If you can't do your homework, you should ask your parents to ____ you.", "Opt_1": "inhibit", "Opt_2": "assist", "Opt_3": "qualify", "Opt_4": "commit", "Answer": "assist", "Opt_1_def": "to prevent or stop", "Opt_2_def": "to help", "Opt_3_def": "to become eligible", "Opt_4_def": "to do (often an offense)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The forecast was for travel ____ to increase by 1 percent to 2 percent compared to last year.", "Opt_1": "duty", "Opt_2": "volume", "Opt_3": "policy", "Opt_4": "ignorance", "Answer": "volume", "Opt_1_def": "responsibility, or job that you are required to do", "Opt_2_def": "amount", "Opt_3_def": "formal rules", "Opt_4_def": "lack of knowledge"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government broadcast a warning about the dangers of terrorist ____ in the capital city.", "Opt_1": "attack", "Opt_2": "range", "Opt_3": "symptom", "Opt_4": "stereotype", "Answer": "attack", "Opt_1_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage", "Opt_2_def": "extent, distance between two points", "Opt_3_def": "sign (often of a disease or other problem)", "Opt_4_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The ____ fits well with the fact that his mental health did not deteriorate.", "Opt_1": "interpretation", "Opt_2": "criterion", "Opt_3": "agent", "Opt_4": "victory", "Answer": "interpretation", "Opt_1_def": "explanation; assessment", "Opt_2_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something", "Opt_3_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone", "Opt_4_def": "win"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "We need to ____ a new strategy. This one isn't working.", "Opt_1": "criticize", "Opt_2": "adopt", "Opt_3": "suppose", "Opt_4": "contemplate", "Answer": "adopt", "Opt_1_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone", "Opt_2_def": "to take in; to start", "Opt_3_def": "to think, imagine", "Opt_4_def": "to think about; to consider"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The school decided to ____ the plan after a meeting with the parents.", "Opt_1": "adopt", "Opt_2": "exceed", "Opt_3": "denote", "Opt_4": "imply", "Answer": "adopt", "Opt_1_def": "to take in; to start", "Opt_2_def": "to be more than or better than", "Opt_3_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_4_def": "to mean; to give to understand"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If we learn to ____ effectively with others and are willing to risk sharing our own feelings and respect other's feelings, many rewards will await us.", "Opt_1": "communicate", "Opt_2": "adhere", "Opt_3": "indicate", "Opt_4": "release", "Answer": "communicate", "Opt_1_def": "to convey information", "Opt_2_def": "to keep to; to follow", "Opt_3_def": "to show or convey", "Opt_4_def": "to let go or let out"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The additional time is necessary to enable him to make a ____ decision on an Alaska natural gas transportation system.", "Opt_1": "authentic", "Opt_2": "external", "Opt_3": "sound", "Opt_4": "sane", "Answer": "sound", "Opt_1_def": "real, genuine; not made-up or artificial", "Opt_2_def": "outside", "Opt_3_def": "good; strong", "Opt_4_def": "reasonable; not mad"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "We conclude the year with a story that shows how severance from one's cultural past can ____ the search for a sense of self.", "Opt_1": "fulfill", "Opt_2": "dispose", "Opt_3": "participate", "Opt_4": "complicate", "Answer": "complicate", "Opt_1_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)", "Opt_2_def": "to get rid of", "Opt_3_def": "to take part", "Opt_4_def": "to make things more complex or difficult"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Some students see no ____ for learning German - especially if they know they will only be in the country for a short time.", "Opt_1": "mixture", "Opt_2": "bulk", "Opt_3": "source", "Opt_4": "motive", "Answer": "motive", "Opt_1_def": "combination", "Opt_2_def": "majority; largest part", "Opt_3_def": "where something begins, where you can find something", "Opt_4_def": "reason"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Many teachers are happier at a lower position in the school hierarchy. They do not want the ____ that comes with the top jobs.", "Opt_1": "embody", "Opt_2": "donate", "Opt_3": "seek", "Opt_4": "stress", "Answer": "stress", "Opt_1_def": "to be a good example of ..", "Opt_2_def": "to give (usually money)", "Opt_3_def": "to look for or want", "Opt_4_def": "to emphasize; to say what is important"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Asia is our closest region and essentially I feel that we need more understanding and ____ culturally to make sense of where we all are'.", "Opt_1": "exchange", "Opt_2": "descend", "Opt_3": "commit", "Opt_4": "prohibit", "Answer": "exchange", "Opt_1_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing", "Opt_2_def": "to go down", "Opt_3_def": "to do (often an offense)", "Opt_4_def": "to ban, disallow"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Every piece of ____ ground in the town centre has already been built on.", "Opt_1": "stable", "Opt_2": "willing", "Opt_3": "superior", "Opt_4": "spare", "Answer": "spare", "Opt_1_def": "not changing; not easy to change", "Opt_2_def": "happy or prepared to do something", "Opt_3_def": "better", "Opt_4_def": "not needed"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Students needed to devote considerable time to recognizing the three basic tenses (past, present, and future) and using the ____ tense in their own writing.", "Opt_1": "annual", "Opt_2": "massive", "Opt_3": "obvious", "Opt_4": "appropriate", "Answer": "appropriate", "Opt_1_def": "yearly", "Opt_2_def": "very large", "Opt_3_def": "clear, evident", "Opt_4_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The ____ from Frankfurt to Oberursel is about 12 kilometers.", "Opt_1": "access", "Opt_2": "period", "Opt_3": "distance", "Opt_4": "surface", "Answer": "distance", "Opt_1_def": "the right to enter or use", "Opt_2_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)", "Opt_3_def": "how far it is from one place to another", "Opt_4_def": "the outside layer of an object"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "I encourage you to spend part of the summer vacation reading. This is an excellent way to ____ your English.", "Opt_1": "purchase", "Opt_2": "define", "Opt_3": "confirm", "Opt_4": "improve", "Answer": "improve", "Opt_1_def": "to buy", "Opt_2_def": "to state what something is or means", "Opt_3_def": "to agree that something is correct", "Opt_4_def": "to get better"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Her ____ in the band concert was wonderful. She's probably the best piano player we have ever had at the school.", "Opt_1": "summary", "Opt_2": "performance", "Opt_3": "extract", "Opt_4": "assent", "Answer": "performance", "Opt_1_def": "a short account of the most important details", "Opt_2_def": "action or achievement", "Opt_3_def": "to remove; to take out and use", "Opt_4_def": "agreement"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The school is planning to revive its lunchtime sports program after hearing a ____ from the student council.", "Opt_1": "view", "Opt_2": "request", "Opt_3": "invent", "Opt_4": "protect", "Answer": "request", "Opt_1_def": "to have an opinion", "Opt_2_def": "to ask politely", "Opt_3_def": "to create (often a new object)", "Opt_4_def": "to keep something out of danger"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "European democratic nation states have increasingly lost influence over the ____ of their own economies.", "Opt_1": "conduct", "Opt_2": "advise", "Opt_3": "view", "Opt_4": "exclude", "Answer": "conduct", "Opt_1_def": "to do or perform; to behave", "Opt_2_def": "to say what someone should do; to give advice", "Opt_3_def": "to have an opinion", "Opt_4_def": "to leave out; opposite of include"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It's hard to ____ the temptation to buy from an unknown company when they're advertising low prices for name brand products.", "Opt_1": "receive", "Opt_2": "prevail", "Opt_3": "resist", "Opt_4": "interact", "Answer": "resist", "Opt_1_def": "to get", "Opt_2_def": "to succeed; to overcome", "Opt_3_def": "to fight against", "Opt_4_def": "to react, to affect and be affected"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Some people ____ that the reasons for invading Iraq were to gain control of its oil.", "Opt_1": "appoint", "Opt_2": "oppose", "Opt_3": "allege", "Opt_4": "found", "Answer": "allege", "Opt_1_def": "to give a job to someone", "Opt_2_def": "to be against or fight against something", "Opt_3_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_4_def": "to begin (often an organization)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "This is an excellent piece of work. You ____ your ideas very clearly.", "Opt_1": "express", "Opt_2": "assess", "Opt_3": "adjust", "Opt_4": "resist", "Answer": "express", "Opt_1_def": "to say or mean", "Opt_2_def": "to judge or test", "Opt_3_def": "to change (often in order to make something work properly)", "Opt_4_def": "to fight against"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Through appointments and legislation the President was able to ____ the Constitution of much of its meaning, with no public reaction.", "Opt_1": "advocate", "Opt_2": "deserve", "Opt_3": "drain", "Opt_4": "assimilate", "Answer": "drain", "Opt_1_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to have the right to something", "Opt_3_def": "to take away; to get rid of", "Opt_4_def": "to take in"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The older population of the U.S. and the world is growing rapidly, and these large numbers will ____ a major challenge for society in general.", "Opt_1": "represent", "Opt_2": "dictate", "Opt_3": "submit", "Opt_4": "disrupt", "Answer": "represent", "Opt_1_def": "to be; to show or indicate", "Opt_2_def": "to tell someone what to do", "Opt_3_def": "to give; to send", "Opt_4_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Most students are ____ about the suggestion to replace the blackboards with whiteboards.", "Opt_1": "stable", "Opt_2": "straightforward", "Opt_3": "evident", "Opt_4": "neutral", "Answer": "neutral", "Opt_1_def": "not changing; not easy to change", "Opt_2_def": "easy", "Opt_3_def": "clear", "Opt_4_def": "neither for nor against; neither positive nor negative"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government did not proceed with the recommendations ____ the disability program and decided to review changes to the program.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Teachers must accompany students and ____ activities in the computer room.", "Opt_1": "clarify", "Opt_2": "shrink", "Opt_3": "generate", "Opt_4": "supervise", "Answer": "supervise", "Opt_1_def": "to make something clear, explain", "Opt_2_def": "to get smaller", "Opt_3_def": "to make or produce", "Opt_4_def": "to control; to watch over people doing something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Whereas the origin of galactic magnetic fields has long posed a challenge for astrophysicists to explain, they ____ feel that they can say where they were not formed.", "Opt_1": "naturally", "Opt_2": "namely", "Opt_3": "therefore", "Opt_4": "nevertheless", "Answer": "nevertheless", "Opt_1_def": "of course, obviously", "Opt_2_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_3_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_4_def": "however (although / despite that)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The new factory near the school will ____ parts for mobile phones.", "Opt_1": "manufacture", "Opt_2": "prefer", "Opt_3": "attain", "Opt_4": "retain", "Answer": "manufacture", "Opt_1_def": "to produce (with machines)", "Opt_2_def": "to like better", "Opt_3_def": "to get, achieve", "Opt_4_def": "to keep"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Children who have no ____ to their behaviour are often unhappy.", "Opt_1": "interval", "Opt_2": "technique", "Opt_3": "labour", "Opt_4": "boundary", "Answer": "boundary", "Opt_1_def": "a period of time", "Opt_2_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "work", "Opt_4_def": "limit, extent"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "A frequent error in editing is to fix a word or ____ at one part of a sentence and not see that the fix affected something else in the sentence.", "Opt_1": "portion", "Opt_2": "phrase", "Opt_3": "motive", "Opt_4": "term", "Answer": "phrase", "Opt_1_def": "part, amount", "Opt_2_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure.", "Opt_3_def": "reason", "Opt_4_def": "a word or expression"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Numerous policy and ____ implications were derived from the study findings.", "Opt_1": "conflict", "Opt_2": "lecture", "Opt_3": "influence", "Opt_4": "programme", "Answer": "programme", "Opt_1_def": "problem, struggle or battle", "Opt_2_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "effect", "Opt_4_def": "a course of lessons; a project"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Many talented local young people have had to ____ graduate or professional education because of lack of access to such programs.", "Opt_1": "migrate", "Opt_2": "forego", "Opt_3": "modify", "Opt_4": "consider", "Answer": "forego", "Opt_1_def": "to go to another place", "Opt_2_def": "to do without; to give up", "Opt_3_def": "to change", "Opt_4_def": "to think"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The course will ____ the knowledge base regarding the finance of community education programs.", "Opt_1": "develop", "Opt_2": "communicate", "Opt_3": "advise", "Opt_4": "import", "Answer": "develop", "Opt_1_def": "to grow or improve", "Opt_2_def": "to convey information", "Opt_3_def": "to say what someone should do; to give advice", "Opt_4_def": "to bring in (to a country)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The Prime Minister broke off her visit to China due to an ____ problem at home.", "Opt_1": "compulsory", "Opt_2": "urgent", "Opt_3": "pure", "Opt_4": "exact", "Answer": "urgent", "Opt_1_def": "required, must be done", "Opt_2_def": "very important, must be done immediately", "Opt_3_def": "complete, 100%", "Opt_4_def": "precise, opposite of approximate"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Illegal drugs are grouped into one or other ____ according to how dangerous they are considered.", "Opt_1": "scale", "Opt_2": "attack", "Opt_3": "category", "Opt_4": "record", "Answer": "category", "Opt_1_def": "extent", "Opt_2_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage", "Opt_3_def": "group of similar items", "Opt_4_def": "evidence; documentation"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The main ____ of the greater study, of which this paper is a part, is to develop a model of discursive exclusion of groups of people in the public sphere.", "Opt_1": "background", "Opt_2": "aid", "Opt_3": "contrary", "Opt_4": "purpose", "Answer": "purpose", "Opt_1_def": "family experiences; circumstances", "Opt_2_def": "help (often financial help)", "Opt_3_def": "opposite", "Opt_4_def": "reason, goal"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "She is having serious problems in her mathematics class. She cannot even ____ two numbers using a calculator.", "Opt_1": "multiply", "Opt_2": "survive", "Opt_3": "prepare", "Opt_4": "arrange", "Answer": "multiply", "Opt_1_def": "to increase greatly", "Opt_2_def": "to not die", "Opt_3_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)", "Opt_4_def": "to plan to happen; to group together"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Individual academies apply the curriculum in the manner that best fits local ____ and opportunities.", "Opt_1": "version", "Opt_2": "facilities", "Opt_3": "record", "Opt_4": "substitute", "Answer": "facilities", "Opt_1_def": "form", "Opt_2_def": "buildings and other places that can be used by people", "Opt_3_def": "evidence; documentation", "Opt_4_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "They found that specific, simple steps can ____ reduce the number of drivers who drink.", "Opt_1": "approximately", "Opt_2": "seldom", "Opt_3": "respectively", "Opt_4": "greatly", "Answer": "greatly", "Opt_1_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_2_def": "rare", "Opt_3_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other", "Opt_4_def": "very much"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Since most employers spend less than a minute scanning a resume, it is necessary to be brief and to ____ all that is important.", "Opt_1": "replace", "Opt_2": "acquire", "Opt_3": "obey", "Opt_4": "highlight", "Answer": "highlight", "Opt_1_def": "to put in or take the place of ..", "Opt_2_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_3_def": "to do as commanded or expected", "Opt_4_def": "to show (the important features of something)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Cocaine did not ____ much popularity in the United States until the 1960s.", "Opt_1": "means", "Opt_2": "range", "Opt_3": "dimension", "Opt_4": "gain", "Answer": "gain", "Opt_1_def": "way", "Opt_2_def": "extent, distance between two points", "Opt_3_def": "importance; amount", "Opt_4_def": "to get; to increase in .."}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Recent research shows bias ____ African American mothers of any class who don't work.", "Opt_1": "among", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "in, between", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "below"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "If he was indeed employed by the Grand Duke, that would account for his ____ behaviour.", "Opt_1": "odd", "Opt_2": "formal", "Opt_3": "profound", "Opt_4": "visual", "Answer": "odd", "Opt_1_def": "strange, unusual", "Opt_2_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday", "Opt_3_def": "deep; great; serious", "Opt_4_def": "to do with sight and seeing"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Some solutions ____ to improve the performance of these devices, but naturally there are limitations how accessible they can be made.", "Opt_1": "exist", "Opt_2": "enable", "Opt_3": "reserve", "Opt_4": "react", "Answer": "exist", "Opt_1_def": "to be alive, to be in the world", "Opt_2_def": "to make something or someone able to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to keep", "Opt_4_def": "to respond"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The student's answer may not address all parts of the question or may demonstrate an inaccurate or ____ analysis of the passage.", "Opt_1": "superficial", "Opt_2": "harsh", "Opt_3": "considerable", "Opt_4": "key", "Answer": "superficial", "Opt_1_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial", "Opt_2_def": "hard, unfair", "Opt_3_def": "very big; very much", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Computer disk drives have been known to suffer from ____ cycle failure, but this is not a concern for broadband modems.", "Opt_1": "relationship", "Opt_2": "doubt", "Opt_3": "rank", "Opt_4": "power", "Answer": "power", "Opt_1_def": "the way to things are connected", "Opt_2_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)", "Opt_3_def": "position (in a list or hierarchy)", "Opt_4_def": "the right or authority to do something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The purpose of this study was to explore the internal and external factors influencing the ____ development of first generation Filipina Americans.", "Opt_1": "defect", "Opt_2": "domain", "Opt_3": "career", "Opt_4": "extract", "Answer": "career", "Opt_1_def": "problem; mistake", "Opt_2_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_3_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_4_def": "to remove; to take out and use"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "An important ____ of the course is the unit on grammar.", "Opt_1": "component", "Opt_2": "bond", "Opt_3": "surplus", "Opt_4": "speed", "Answer": "component", "Opt_1_def": "part of; an element of", "Opt_2_def": "link; tie", "Opt_3_def": "to be, go or make all the way around", "Opt_4_def": "how quickly something moves or changes"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "If you are trying to understand the instructions of a new piece of equipment like a camera, it helps to have a ____ to look at.", "Opt_1": "debt", "Opt_2": "feature", "Opt_3": "institution", "Opt_4": "diagram", "Answer": "diagram", "Opt_1_def": "something owed to another person (often money)", "Opt_2_def": "part, aspect", "Opt_3_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom", "Opt_4_def": "a type of picture or chart"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Advertising often tries to ____ the idea that the customer deserves to buy the product because they are worth it!", "Opt_1": "afford", "Opt_2": "form", "Opt_3": "promote", "Opt_4": "share", "Answer": "promote", "Opt_1_def": "to be able to pay for something", "Opt_2_def": "to make (into a shape)", "Opt_3_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job", "Opt_4_def": "to exchange; to give"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "In this particular poem, Dalton, while asking what woman's ____ is, also advises man on woman's potential and her proper place in life.", "Opt_1": "sphere", "Opt_2": "duration", "Opt_3": "decade", "Opt_4": "counsel", "Answer": "sphere", "Opt_1_def": "area of interest", "Opt_2_def": "period of time", "Opt_3_def": "a period of ten years", "Opt_4_def": "advice; advisor"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Spending months at a time in orbit, the scientists will be able to observe changes on the earth ____ them from day to day.", "Opt_1": "among", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "prior", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "in, between", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "before"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Sometimes it is necessary to impose a ____ on the number of solutions searched for, since in general the number of such solutions could be infinite.", "Opt_1": "limit", "Opt_2": "power", "Opt_3": "statistic", "Opt_4": "majority", "Answer": "limit", "Opt_1_def": "extent, boundary", "Opt_2_def": "the right or authority to do something", "Opt_3_def": "mathematical number", "Opt_4_def": "more than 50%"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "You will have to ____ your documents to fit the required length.", "Opt_1": "enlarge", "Opt_2": "govern", "Opt_3": "entitle", "Opt_4": "edit", "Answer": "edit", "Opt_1_def": "to make larger", "Opt_2_def": "to control or influence", "Opt_3_def": "to give the right to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The ____ was not visible in its entirety on the computer screen.", "Opt_1": "anomaly", "Opt_2": "passage", "Opt_3": "community", "Opt_4": "distance", "Answer": "passage", "Opt_1_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data", "Opt_2_def": "a piece of written or spoken text", "Opt_3_def": "a group of people", "Opt_4_def": "how far it is from one place to another"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "But when planned and deliberate ____ forces the price of oil down without good commercial reasons, then that means another war against Iraq.", "Opt_1": "potential", "Opt_2": "display", "Opt_3": "policy", "Opt_4": "balance", "Answer": "policy", "Opt_1_def": "good possibility", "Opt_2_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration", "Opt_3_def": "formal rules", "Opt_4_def": "equalness"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The police could find no ____ of the girl who was kidnapped from her hotel.", "Opt_1": "province", "Opt_2": "trace", "Opt_3": "apparatus", "Opt_4": "error", "Answer": "trace", "Opt_1_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_2_def": "sign; indication; evidence", "Opt_3_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job", "Opt_4_def": "a mistake"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The teacher was asked to ____ after it was discovered that he had lied about his absence from school.", "Opt_1": "refute", "Opt_2": "resign", "Opt_3": "disperse", "Opt_4": "comprehend", "Answer": "resign", "Opt_1_def": "to prove to be untrue; to deny", "Opt_2_def": "to give up (one's job)", "Opt_3_def": "to spread out; to move apart", "Opt_4_def": "to understand"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It is possible to find the volume of an ____ by measuring the amount of water that it displaces.", "Opt_1": "object", "Opt_2": "detail", "Opt_3": "attitude", "Opt_4": "policy", "Answer": "object", "Opt_1_def": "thing", "Opt_2_def": "a small piece of information", "Opt_3_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)", "Opt_4_def": "formal rules"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Student surveys find teaching to be too uniformly didactic, and their learning too passive. Students report spending ____ class time just taking notes.", "Opt_1": "considerable", "Opt_2": "official", "Opt_3": "subsequent", "Opt_4": "dense", "Answer": "considerable", "Opt_1_def": "very big; very much", "Opt_2_def": "approved by an authority", "Opt_3_def": "next, following", "Opt_4_def": "thick; full; detailed"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Asian companies are good at building small cars but will never ____ the mainstream US car market.", "Opt_1": "investigate", "Opt_2": "dominate", "Opt_3": "ruin", "Opt_4": "disperse", "Answer": "dominate", "Opt_1_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened", "Opt_2_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part", "Opt_3_def": "to spoil or damage", "Opt_4_def": "to spread out; to move apart"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Dinosaurs no longer ____ - they have been extinct for millions of years.", "Opt_1": "formulate", "Opt_2": "exist", "Opt_3": "reinforce", "Opt_4": "compel", "Answer": "exist", "Opt_1_def": "to express", "Opt_2_def": "to be alive, to be in the world", "Opt_3_def": "to make something stronger", "Opt_4_def": "to force or make happen"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "A small ____ of the government were against the Prime Minister's plan, but they were outvoted.", "Opt_1": "surplus", "Opt_2": "procedure", "Opt_3": "passage", "Opt_4": "proportion", "Answer": "proportion", "Opt_1_def": "to be, go or make all the way around", "Opt_2_def": "the way to do something", "Opt_3_def": "a piece of written or spoken text", "Opt_4_def": "amount; number; percentage"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The notion of the student as the school's primary customer provides an important guiding ____ for many of today's school reforms.", "Opt_1": "aspect", "Opt_2": "statement", "Opt_3": "principle", "Opt_4": "obligation", "Answer": "principle", "Opt_1_def": "environment that lifts people up,\" says Jain.", "Opt_2_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)", "Opt_3_def": "rule", "Opt_4_def": "a requirement to do something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government received information but did not consider it reliable and therefore decided to ____ it.", "Opt_1": "protest", "Opt_2": "evaluate", "Opt_3": "ignore", "Opt_4": "regard", "Answer": "ignore", "Opt_1_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_2_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something", "Opt_3_def": "to take no notice of; to leave out (of consideration)", "Opt_4_def": "to think or have an opinion about something or someone"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Now that you have revised your work, the next stage of the writing process is to ____ it for errors of grammar or spelling.", "Opt_1": "integrate", "Opt_2": "receive", "Opt_3": "manifest", "Opt_4": "edit", "Answer": "edit", "Opt_1_def": "to fit into a new situation", "Opt_2_def": "to get", "Opt_3_def": "show", "Opt_4_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Many people were very unhappy at the police's ____ of the demonstrators.", "Opt_1": "duty", "Opt_2": "lecture", "Opt_3": "outcome", "Opt_4": "treatment", "Answer": "treatment", "Opt_1_def": "responsibility, or job that you are required to do", "Opt_2_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "result", "Opt_4_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If breastfeeding is not possible, ____ infant milk formulas are a good alternative.", "Opt_1": "accurate", "Opt_2": "subsequent", "Opt_3": "immediate", "Opt_4": "commercial", "Answer": "commercial", "Opt_1_def": "exact, containing no mistakes", "Opt_2_def": "next, following", "Opt_3_def": "first (without delay)", "Opt_4_def": "to do with business"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Most teachers are ____ to students wearing hats or chewing gum in the classroom.", "Opt_1": "vital", "Opt_2": "vast", "Opt_3": "official", "Opt_4": "averse", "Answer": "averse", "Opt_1_def": "very important", "Opt_2_def": "very large", "Opt_3_def": "approved by an authority", "Opt_4_def": "against"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "A primary function of the system is to ____ the sharing of information with others.", "Opt_1": "control", "Opt_2": "prosper", "Opt_3": "precede", "Opt_4": "facilitate", "Answer": "facilitate", "Opt_1_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone", "Opt_2_def": "to do well; to become rich", "Opt_3_def": "to go or be before someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to make something easier"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "A serious problem of nuclear power is where and how to ____ of the radioactive waste.", "Opt_1": "culminate", "Opt_2": "represent", "Opt_3": "prosper", "Opt_4": "dispose", "Answer": "dispose", "Opt_1_def": "to end", "Opt_2_def": "to be; to show or indicate", "Opt_3_def": "to do well; to become rich", "Opt_4_def": "to get rid of"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "An even number multiplied by an odd number will always ____ an even number.", "Opt_1": "interfere", "Opt_2": "yield", "Opt_3": "stimulate", "Opt_4": "observe", "Answer": "yield", "Opt_1_def": "to prevent; to harm", "Opt_2_def": "to produce", "Opt_3_def": "to interest, make grow or encourage", "Opt_4_def": "to watch carefully"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "A large ____ map shows a small area with a large amount of detail.", "Opt_1": "delay", "Opt_2": "scale", "Opt_3": "staff", "Opt_4": "obstacle", "Answer": "scale", "Opt_1_def": "lateness", "Opt_2_def": "extent", "Opt_3_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)", "Opt_4_def": "barrier; problem"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The World Bank said China has the capacity to ____ the impact of the recent international financial market fluctuations.", "Opt_1": "convince", "Opt_2": "condemn", "Opt_3": "absorb", "Opt_4": "withdraw", "Answer": "absorb", "Opt_1_def": "to (try and) get someone to believe something", "Opt_2_def": "to express strong disapproval", "Opt_3_def": "to take in; to take up", "Opt_4_def": "to go back or take away"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "This is not a ____ in the notion of economic development as much as it is a problem with the fiscal structure of Alaska.", "Opt_1": "goal", "Opt_2": "phenomenon", "Opt_3": "defect", "Opt_4": "gap", "Answer": "defect", "Opt_1_def": "aim or intention", "Opt_2_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)", "Opt_3_def": "problem; mistake", "Opt_4_def": "space, opening or time between"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Including future irrelevant costs generally will not lead to a poor choice; it will only ____ the analysis.", "Opt_1": "complicate", "Opt_2": "abuse", "Opt_3": "emphasize", "Opt_4": "diminish", "Answer": "complicate", "Opt_1_def": "to make things more complex or difficult", "Opt_2_def": "to treat someone or something badly", "Opt_3_def": "to stress, to say something strongly", "Opt_4_def": "to get smaller or less important"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Describe the study in detail sufficient to convince the reviewer that the problem is ____ investigation.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "beneath", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "below", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The school can recommend that parents ____ by email, but they cannot insist on it.", "Opt_1": "conceal", "Opt_2": "precede", "Opt_3": "communicate", "Opt_4": "expose", "Answer": "communicate", "Opt_1_def": "to hide", "Opt_2_def": "to go or be before someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to convey information", "Opt_4_def": "to uncover, reveal"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It is not in the best interests of children if their parents are ____ protective of them.", "Opt_1": "therefore", "Opt_2": "indeed", "Opt_3": "overly", "Opt_4": "moreover", "Answer": "overly", "Opt_1_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_2_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_3_def": "too", "Opt_4_def": "also .., what is more .."}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The company report did not do much to ____ the reasons for the fall in business in the previous year.", "Opt_1": "stress", "Opt_2": "embody", "Opt_3": "reduce", "Opt_4": "illuminate", "Answer": "illuminate", "Opt_1_def": "to emphasize; to say what is important", "Opt_2_def": "to be a good example of ..", "Opt_3_def": "to make smaller or shorter", "Opt_4_def": "to show clearly; to light up"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "What's the ____ time needed to finish a course?", "Opt_1": "average", "Opt_2": "smooth", "Opt_3": "available", "Opt_4": "forthcoming", "Answer": "average", "Opt_1_def": "ordinary, typical", "Opt_2_def": "easy, unproblematic", "Opt_3_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_4_def": "coming soon"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "People today have become more conscious of their individual responsibility to ____ the environment.", "Opt_1": "restrict", "Opt_2": "dictate", "Opt_3": "protect", "Opt_4": "procure", "Answer": "protect", "Opt_1_def": "to limit", "Opt_2_def": "to tell someone what to do", "Opt_3_def": "to keep something out of danger", "Opt_4_def": "to get or obtain"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "People are more likely to ____ in times of war or economic poverty.", "Opt_1": "ensure", "Opt_2": "migrate", "Opt_3": "proceed", "Opt_4": "consist", "Answer": "migrate", "Opt_1_def": "to make sure (of)", "Opt_2_def": "to go to another place", "Opt_3_def": "to go forward (and do ..)", "Opt_4_def": "to have in it; to have as part of it"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The book focuses on the key role the family plays as teenagers navigate the difficult ____ from childhood to adulthood.", "Opt_1": "magnitude", "Opt_2": "transition", "Opt_3": "element", "Opt_4": "source", "Answer": "transition", "Opt_1_def": "size; amount", "Opt_2_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_3_def": "aspect, part", "Opt_4_def": "where something begins, where you can find something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "This page contains a ____ outline to be used as a guide for the creation of a strong outline.", "Opt_1": "sample", "Opt_2": "stage", "Opt_3": "symptom", "Opt_4": "programme", "Answer": "sample", "Opt_1_def": "example; a smaller number of a larger collection", "Opt_2_def": "period of time, part of a process", "Opt_3_def": "sign (often of a disease or other problem)", "Opt_4_def": "a course of lessons; a project"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The doctor had to ____ the x-rays carefully to find any signs of abnormality.", "Opt_1": "approach", "Opt_2": "spread", "Opt_3": "defend", "Opt_4": "inspect", "Answer": "inspect", "Opt_1_def": "to near; to get closer", "Opt_2_def": "to move (over a wider area)", "Opt_3_def": "to give reasons for", "Opt_4_def": "to look at carefully"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The study did not discover any significant ____ between the type of music and the amount of stress.", "Opt_1": "education", "Opt_2": "justice", "Opt_3": "relationship", "Opt_4": "component", "Answer": "relationship", "Opt_1_def": "schooling", "Opt_2_def": "fairness in law", "Opt_3_def": "the way to things are connected", "Opt_4_def": "part of; an element of"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Due to the new law, smokers will now have to ____ the pleasure of a cigarette with their drink in a restaurant or bar.", "Opt_1": "gather", "Opt_2": "create", "Opt_3": "forego", "Opt_4": "monitor", "Answer": "forego", "Opt_1_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_2_def": "to make; to use your imagination to make something new", "Opt_3_def": "to do without; to give up", "Opt_4_def": "to watch ( someone's or something's behaviour )"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "As ancient pottery workers experimented with the effects of higher temperatures on ceramics, they began to ____ methods to produce a high enough temperature that copper could be melted.", "Opt_1": "suppose", "Opt_2": "develop", "Opt_3": "represent", "Opt_4": "offer", "Answer": "develop", "Opt_1_def": "to think, imagine", "Opt_2_def": "to grow or improve", "Opt_3_def": "to be; to show or indicate", "Opt_4_def": "to ask if someone would like something (e.g. food or help)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "And finally, these estimates depend to some ____ on those proven numbers and, as we've already seen, those numbers are not very reliable.", "Opt_1": "instance", "Opt_2": "exponent", "Opt_3": "extent", "Opt_4": "technique", "Answer": "extent", "Opt_1_def": "example", "Opt_2_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion", "Opt_3_def": "size, amount", "Opt_4_def": "a method of doing something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Food irradiation can be an important tool in the war ____ illness and death from foodborne diseases.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "If you are accepted you will need to ____ to have an official copy of your scores sent to the Program address below.", "Opt_1": "cease", "Opt_2": "prosper", "Opt_3": "share", "Opt_4": "arrange", "Answer": "arrange", "Opt_1_def": "to stop", "Opt_2_def": "to do well; to become rich", "Opt_3_def": "to exchange; to give", "Opt_4_def": "to plan to happen; to group together"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The school cafeteria has made the ____ decision not to offer hamburgers, hot dogs and French fries to the younger students .", "Opt_1": "sane", "Opt_2": "complex", "Opt_3": "outstanding", "Opt_4": "entire", "Answer": "sane", "Opt_1_def": "reasonable; not mad", "Opt_2_def": "difficult, complicated", "Opt_3_def": "excellent", "Opt_4_def": "whole, all"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If the individual knows in advance when he or she wishes to apply for time away from the workplace, the individual should complete the preliminary ____ form.", "Opt_1": "reduce", "Opt_2": "multiply", "Opt_3": "request", "Opt_4": "ban", "Answer": "request", "Opt_1_def": "to make smaller or shorter", "Opt_2_def": "to increase greatly", "Opt_3_def": "to ask politely", "Opt_4_def": "to prohibit or forbid"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It is now ____ to almost everyone that the decision to invade Iraq was a very serious error of judgment.", "Opt_1": "various", "Opt_2": "logical", "Opt_3": "obvious", "Opt_4": "abundant", "Answer": "obvious", "Opt_1_def": "several, of different kinds", "Opt_2_def": "making sense", "Opt_3_def": "clear, evident", "Opt_4_def": "existing in large quantities"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It's good that the school employs employ new, young teachers every year. They can ____ discussions about teaching methods.", "Opt_1": "estimate", "Opt_2": "commit", "Opt_3": "stimulate", "Opt_4": "invent", "Answer": "stimulate", "Opt_1_def": "to make an intelligent guess", "Opt_2_def": "to do (often an offense)", "Opt_3_def": "to interest, make grow or encourage", "Opt_4_def": "to create (often a new object)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "I think this the first time that the ____ has done something almost totally against student interest.", "Opt_1": "administration", "Opt_2": "revenue", "Opt_3": "condition", "Opt_4": "margin", "Answer": "administration", "Opt_1_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school", "Opt_2_def": "money, income", "Opt_3_def": "state", "Opt_4_def": "amount; distance"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "And ____ failing to reduce unemployment, the government has also increased the tax on food.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "He seems to be lacking the ____ to improve his rather poor grades.", "Opt_1": "apparatus", "Opt_2": "ignorance", "Opt_3": "fund", "Opt_4": "impulse", "Answer": "impulse", "Opt_1_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job", "Opt_2_def": "lack of knowledge", "Opt_3_def": "money collected for a particular purpose", "Opt_4_def": "reason or motivation to do something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The terrorist plane crashing into the New York tower is an ____ that most people will never forget.", "Opt_1": "image", "Opt_2": "pressure", "Opt_3": "proportion", "Opt_4": "policy", "Answer": "image", "Opt_1_def": "picture", "Opt_2_def": "force; influence; stress", "Opt_3_def": "amount; number; percentage", "Opt_4_def": "formal rules"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "A ____ for other cultures is inherent in the philosophy of our international school.", "Opt_1": "respect", "Opt_2": "communicate", "Opt_3": "construct", "Opt_4": "yield", "Answer": "respect", "Opt_1_def": "to think positively about someone; to tolerate or avoid interfering with something", "Opt_2_def": "to convey information", "Opt_3_def": "to make", "Opt_4_def": "to produce"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "In the event of an ____ disaster a new virtual bulletin board will help the campus take roll.", "Opt_1": "royal", "Opt_2": "sole", "Opt_3": "actual", "Opt_4": "remote", "Answer": "actual", "Opt_1_def": "of kings and queens", "Opt_2_def": "only", "Opt_3_def": "real", "Opt_4_def": "far, distant, small"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The book is at its best when it delves energetically into some ____ event, and draws out its abstract meaning with reference to the grand themes.", "Opt_1": "particular", "Opt_2": "odd", "Opt_3": "scarce", "Opt_4": "instant", "Answer": "particular", "Opt_1_def": "specific", "Opt_2_def": "strange, unusual", "Opt_3_def": "rare, not abundant", "Opt_4_def": "immediate"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "How do we approach the ____ and perpetual problem of dealing with our own waste?", "Opt_1": "willing", "Opt_2": "military", "Opt_3": "essential", "Opt_4": "current", "Answer": "essential", "Opt_1_def": "happy or prepared to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to do with army", "Opt_3_def": "very important", "Opt_4_def": "happening now"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "People today have become more ____ of their individual responsibility to protect the environment.", "Opt_1": "slight", "Opt_2": "conscious", "Opt_3": "considerable", "Opt_4": "crucial", "Answer": "conscious", "Opt_1_def": "small", "Opt_2_def": "aware, knowing", "Opt_3_def": "very big; very much", "Opt_4_def": "extremely important"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Campuses must publish an annual security report detailing statistics ____ crimes committed on campus and at affiliated locations.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The journey to peace and prosperity in the region can only ____ when the civic authority is brought back in.", "Opt_1": "commence", "Opt_2": "continue", "Opt_3": "manifest", "Opt_4": "lessen", "Answer": "commence", "Opt_1_def": "to start", "Opt_2_def": "to carry on, not stop", "Opt_3_def": "show", "Opt_4_def": "to reduce"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It is a ____ in my family for everyone to get together for Sunday lunch.", "Opt_1": "attention", "Opt_2": "loss", "Opt_3": "tradition", "Opt_4": "scale", "Answer": "tradition", "Opt_1_def": "focus", "Opt_2_def": "removal or reduction", "Opt_3_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things", "Opt_4_def": "extent"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "You have one last opportunity to show that you can work hard and ____ properly. If you don't take it, you will be asked to leave the school.", "Opt_1": "tolerate", "Opt_2": "explore", "Opt_3": "prove", "Opt_4": "behave", "Answer": "behave", "Opt_1_def": "to allow to happen; to bear", "Opt_2_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)", "Opt_3_def": "to show to be true", "Opt_4_def": "to act or do things in a certain way"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "I was surprised that ____ me there were only about three or four people in favour of the proposal.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Some students claim that they can ____ watch TV and do their homework.", "Opt_1": "merely", "Opt_2": "simultaneously", "Opt_3": "somewhat", "Opt_4": "overly", "Answer": "simultaneously", "Opt_1_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_2_def": "at the same time", "Opt_3_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_4_def": "too"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The optical characteristics of the new hardware will have a profound ____ on high-speed networking across the globe.", "Opt_1": "disaster", "Opt_2": "implication", "Opt_3": "area", "Opt_4": "belief", "Answer": "implication", "Opt_1_def": "a huge problem or failure", "Opt_2_def": "result or consequence", "Opt_3_def": "field, sphere", "Opt_4_def": "what you think; what you believe in"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The university should not label students who take an extra year to ____ their studies as lazy.", "Opt_1": "complete", "Opt_2": "confident", "Opt_3": "vital", "Opt_4": "immense", "Answer": "complete", "Opt_1_def": "full or finished", "Opt_2_def": "sure that something will happen", "Opt_3_def": "very important", "Opt_4_def": "very large"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The teacher had to ____ the boy from the rest of the class. His bad behaviour was disrupting their learning.", "Opt_1": "maintain", "Opt_2": "isolate", "Opt_3": "transform", "Opt_4": "manipulate", "Answer": "isolate", "Opt_1_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_2_def": "to separate something or someone from others", "Opt_3_def": "to change (often completely)", "Opt_4_def": "to (use and) change"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Dairy farmers have led the latest in a long series of protests by agricultural associations, ____ the record high prices for farm products.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It is impossible to ____ any Yuan play in its original style because the music is lost and its social context has changed.", "Opt_1": "broadcast", "Opt_2": "occur", "Opt_3": "revive", "Opt_4": "consent", "Answer": "revive", "Opt_1_def": "to tell or transmit (often by means of a television programme)", "Opt_2_def": "to happen; take place", "Opt_3_def": "to bring back (to life)", "Opt_4_def": "to agree"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Doctors can give no ____ explanation for the fact that so many people smoke even though they know how dangerous it is.", "Opt_1": "actual", "Opt_2": "efficient", "Opt_3": "logical", "Opt_4": "widespread", "Answer": "logical", "Opt_1_def": "real", "Opt_2_def": "working quickly and easily", "Opt_3_def": "making sense", "Opt_4_def": "common"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The school plans to ____ \ufffd\ufffd10,000 to buy new computers next year for the science lab.", "Opt_1": "organize", "Opt_2": "protect", "Opt_3": "fade", "Opt_4": "allocate", "Answer": "allocate", "Opt_1_def": "to put into (its proper) place", "Opt_2_def": "to keep something out of danger", "Opt_3_def": "to disappear slowly", "Opt_4_def": "to give to (to promise to give)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Newspaper headline: MIT scientists ____ a new way to deliver gene therapy.", "Opt_1": "underlie", "Opt_2": "devise", "Opt_3": "hesitate", "Opt_4": "establish", "Answer": "devise", "Opt_1_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something", "Opt_2_def": "to create or think up", "Opt_3_def": "to pause before saying or doing something", "Opt_4_def": "to begin or set up"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government minister needed time to organize his ____ to the criticisms made about his department.", "Opt_1": "propensity", "Opt_2": "status", "Opt_3": "background", "Opt_4": "reply", "Answer": "reply", "Opt_1_def": "tendency; desire", "Opt_2_def": "position, standing", "Opt_3_def": "family experiences; circumstances", "Opt_4_def": "an answer"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "She has learned from her mother's experience, however, and does not ____ the error her mother made.", "Opt_1": "comprise", "Opt_2": "comprehend", "Opt_3": "justify", "Opt_4": "repeat", "Answer": "repeat", "Opt_1_def": "to be made up of; to include", "Opt_2_def": "to understand", "Opt_3_def": "to give a reason for doing something", "Opt_4_def": "to do or say again"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Teachers identified aspects intrinsic to the ____ of teaching, such as their interactions with students and their capacity to influence student achievement.", "Opt_1": "task", "Opt_2": "occasion", "Opt_3": "income", "Opt_4": "trait", "Answer": "task", "Opt_1_def": "job", "Opt_2_def": "time (opportunity)", "Opt_3_def": "money earned", "Opt_4_def": "characteristic; aspect"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The bank didn't think that her idea would generate enough money so they refused to ____ it.", "Opt_1": "circumstances", "Opt_2": "research", "Opt_3": "rise", "Opt_4": "finance", "Answer": "finance", "Opt_1_def": "situation", "Opt_2_def": "study; the finding of information", "Opt_3_def": "to go up", "Opt_4_def": "to do with money and payment"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Nine tenths of an iceberg is under water and hence ____ to ships.", "Opt_1": "significant", "Opt_2": "invisible", "Opt_3": "mobile", "Opt_4": "tough", "Answer": "invisible", "Opt_1_def": "important, large", "Opt_2_def": "cannot be seen", "Opt_3_def": "moving; able to move", "Opt_4_def": "difficult, strong"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "If you choose to do nothing to ____ to the changing conditions, you will probably make yourself miserable.", "Opt_1": "increase", "Opt_2": "adapt", "Opt_3": "explore", "Opt_4": "disturb", "Answer": "adapt", "Opt_1_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_2_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)", "Opt_3_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)", "Opt_4_def": "to interrupt, stop from working"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It is not usual that students ____ with their teachers whether they must do homework or not.", "Opt_1": "reverse", "Opt_2": "advise", "Opt_3": "negotiate", "Opt_4": "ruin", "Answer": "negotiate", "Opt_1_def": "to turn back or go back", "Opt_2_def": "to say what someone should do; to give advice", "Opt_3_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)", "Opt_4_def": "to spoil or damage"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government can suggest that people eat more healthily but it cannot ____ them to do so.", "Opt_1": "own", "Opt_2": "determine", "Opt_3": "prepare", "Opt_4": "force", "Answer": "force", "Opt_1_def": "to have or possess", "Opt_2_def": "to find out; to establish or identify; state", "Opt_3_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)", "Opt_4_def": "to make happen or to make someone do something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "After massive criticism the government has decided to ____ language courses for immigrants to the country.", "Opt_1": "restore", "Opt_2": "cover", "Opt_3": "assure", "Opt_4": "recover", "Answer": "restore", "Opt_1_def": "to put back, create again", "Opt_2_def": "to do; to complete", "Opt_3_def": "to make sure; to say that something will certainly happen", "Opt_4_def": "to get back"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "He questioned the security coordination that enabled the terrorists to ____ all their preparatory work. The authorities had failed to surround the school for three days.", "Opt_1": "expand", "Opt_2": "accomplish", "Opt_3": "harm", "Opt_4": "collapse", "Answer": "accomplish", "Opt_1_def": "to get bigger; to move into new areas", "Opt_2_def": "to do or achieve", "Opt_3_def": "to damage or injure", "Opt_4_def": "to fall down completely and heavily; to fail"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "You will ____ an email from the Financial Aid office when your financial aid eligibility has been determined.", "Opt_1": "receive", "Opt_2": "earn", "Opt_3": "abuse", "Opt_4": "own", "Answer": "receive", "Opt_1_def": "to get", "Opt_2_def": "to get money or another reward (usually by working for it)", "Opt_3_def": "to treat someone or something badly", "Opt_4_def": "to have or possess"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "FLO plays the key role as an ____ for ethically sensitive consumers.", "Opt_1": "agent", "Opt_2": "impact", "Opt_3": "instance", "Opt_4": "evidence", "Answer": "agent", "Opt_1_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone", "Opt_2_def": "effect", "Opt_3_def": "example", "Opt_4_def": "proof, signs"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is scheduled to begin at 3:30 p.m. A decision to cancel or ____ the match will be made later in the day, if necessary.", "Opt_1": "constitute", "Opt_2": "diminish", "Opt_3": "postpone", "Opt_4": "consult", "Answer": "postpone", "Opt_1_def": "to be; to make up", "Opt_2_def": "to get smaller or less important", "Opt_3_def": "to put back in time", "Opt_4_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Individual investors: ____ with caution.", "Opt_1": "correspond", "Opt_2": "neglect", "Opt_3": "obtain", "Opt_4": "proceed", "Answer": "proceed", "Opt_1_def": "to be related to", "Opt_2_def": "to not think about or care for", "Opt_3_def": "to get", "Opt_4_def": "to go forward (and do ..)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "He told the members that he quickly called for a car and telephoned the White House to set up an urgent meeting in order to ____ what he had just learned.", "Opt_1": "block", "Opt_2": "establish", "Opt_3": "share", "Opt_4": "commit", "Answer": "share", "Opt_1_def": "to not allow; to stop or prevent", "Opt_2_def": "to begin or set up", "Opt_3_def": "to exchange; to give", "Opt_4_def": "to do (often an offense)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Stated simply, this principle means that averaged over large enough distances, one part of the Universe looks ____ like any other part.", "Opt_1": "thereby", "Opt_2": "approximately", "Opt_3": "barely", "Opt_4": "somewhat", "Answer": "approximately", "Opt_1_def": "by doing this", "Opt_2_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_3_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_4_def": "quite, rather"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "We had disagreed strongly over politics before, and while these arguments did not strain our friendship in the least, I wished to ____ potential conflict.", "Opt_1": "clarify", "Opt_2": "monitor", "Opt_3": "avoid", "Opt_4": "unite", "Answer": "avoid", "Opt_1_def": "to make something clear, explain", "Opt_2_def": "to watch ( someone's or something's behaviour )", "Opt_3_def": "to not do something or go somewhere", "Opt_4_def": "to bring or get together"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The boss took the ____ decision to close the factory for a week.", "Opt_1": "arbitrary", "Opt_2": "independent", "Opt_3": "competent", "Opt_4": "suitable", "Answer": "arbitrary", "Opt_1_def": "not planned or thought-out; not considering the wishes of others", "Opt_2_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else", "Opt_3_def": "good at something (often a job)", "Opt_4_def": "good for a particular job or purpose"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The company was heavily in ____ after investing a lot of money in new machinery.", "Opt_1": "shift", "Opt_2": "scheme", "Opt_3": "debt", "Opt_4": "phase", "Answer": "debt", "Opt_1_def": "change", "Opt_2_def": "plan. idea, project", "Opt_3_def": "something owed to another person (often money)", "Opt_4_def": "a (short) period of time; stage"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "You will need to form project teams of two or three students, and then it will be your responsibility to ____ meetings.", "Opt_1": "explore", "Opt_2": "culminate", "Opt_3": "organize", "Opt_4": "supervise", "Answer": "organize", "Opt_1_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)", "Opt_2_def": "to end", "Opt_3_def": "to put into (its proper) place", "Opt_4_def": "to control; to watch over people doing something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Most scientists ____ that the life expectancy of people in developed countries will continue to rise.", "Opt_1": "facilitate", "Opt_2": "distribute", "Opt_3": "trigger", "Opt_4": "presume", "Answer": "presume", "Opt_1_def": "to make something easier", "Opt_2_def": "to give out", "Opt_3_def": "to (cause to) start", "Opt_4_def": "to believe, assume"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The publishing company brought a ____ of its books to display to teachers.", "Opt_1": "stage", "Opt_2": "sample", "Opt_3": "resource", "Opt_4": "hypothesis", "Answer": "sample", "Opt_1_def": "period of time, part of a process", "Opt_2_def": "example; a smaller number of a larger collection", "Opt_3_def": "a source of information or material", "Opt_4_def": "idea or prediction"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "On December 4, 1955, the ____ decision was made to boycott the bus system until they were treated with courtesy and black drivers could be hired.", "Opt_1": "frequent", "Opt_2": "anonymous", "Opt_3": "numerous", "Opt_4": "radical", "Answer": "anonymous", "Opt_1_def": "often", "Opt_2_def": "having no name or known author", "Opt_3_def": "very many", "Opt_4_def": "extreme, strong"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "D. perceives this as deviation from what she considers the traditional ____ of behaviour of Greek women.", "Opt_1": "guarantee", "Opt_2": "comparison", "Opt_3": "phrase", "Opt_4": "code", "Answer": "code", "Opt_1_def": "to promise or assure that something will or will not happen", "Opt_2_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different", "Opt_3_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure.", "Opt_4_def": "a set of rules"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Only seniors have the ____ of using this room. You will have to wait until you are in grade 12.", "Opt_1": "vary", "Opt_2": "feature", "Opt_3": "attention", "Opt_4": "privilege", "Answer": "privilege", "Opt_1_def": "to change or be different", "Opt_2_def": "part, aspect", "Opt_3_def": "focus", "Opt_4_def": "a right (to do something)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "\"Be fair, ____ and friendly\" is the advice often given to new teachers.", "Opt_1": "extraordinary", "Opt_2": "aware", "Opt_3": "firm", "Opt_4": "artificial", "Answer": "firm", "Opt_1_def": "very unusual", "Opt_2_def": "knowing", "Opt_3_def": "strong, cannot be changed", "Opt_4_def": "not real or natural"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government has little chance of success in its ____ to reduce crime unless it creates more jobs.", "Opt_1": "substitute", "Opt_2": "region", "Opt_3": "principle", "Opt_4": "struggle", "Answer": "struggle", "Opt_1_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another", "Opt_2_def": "part of a place", "Opt_3_def": "rule", "Opt_4_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "He wants to get a job in the engineering ____ when he leaves school.", "Opt_1": "record", "Opt_2": "loss", "Opt_3": "volume", "Opt_4": "industry", "Answer": "industry", "Opt_1_def": "evidence; documentation", "Opt_2_def": "removal or reduction", "Opt_3_def": "amount", "Opt_4_def": "area of business ( often manufacturing )"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "He was unable to ____ his plans for an industrial area, which he purchased from the Israel Land Administration.", "Opt_1": "control", "Opt_2": "damage", "Opt_3": "launch", "Opt_4": "implement", "Answer": "implement", "Opt_1_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone", "Opt_2_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_3_def": "to begin", "Opt_4_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Every ____ in this class has made excellent progress and passed the final exam.", "Opt_1": "commodity", "Opt_2": "affair", "Opt_3": "resident", "Opt_4": "individual", "Answer": "individual", "Opt_1_def": "a product; something you can buy", "Opt_2_def": "an event or series of events", "Opt_3_def": "a person who lives in a place", "Opt_4_def": "one person"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government was unable to ____ that it was considering invading North Korea.", "Opt_1": "contain", "Opt_2": "deprive", "Opt_3": "generate", "Opt_4": "deny", "Answer": "deny", "Opt_1_def": "to have in it; to hold inside", "Opt_2_def": "to take away (the opportunity)", "Opt_3_def": "to make or produce", "Opt_4_def": "to refuse ( responsibility for doing or saying something); to say that something is not correct"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The police did not have the necessary ____ to cut the man free from the crashed car.", "Opt_1": "proportion", "Opt_2": "equipment", "Opt_3": "process", "Opt_4": "stage", "Answer": "equipment", "Opt_1_def": "amount; number; percentage", "Opt_2_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)", "Opt_3_def": "a series of steps", "Opt_4_def": "period of time, part of a process"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The donors specified that they would like to help hardworking students with ____ grades who deserve help.", "Opt_1": "aware", "Opt_2": "medium", "Opt_3": "abundant", "Opt_4": "straightforward", "Answer": "medium", "Opt_1_def": "knowing", "Opt_2_def": "in the middle", "Opt_3_def": "existing in large quantities", "Opt_4_def": "easy"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The candidate must ____ clear written and verbal communication skills, and must be willing to work in a team project environment.", "Opt_1": "degree", "Opt_2": "majority", "Opt_3": "command", "Opt_4": "contract", "Answer": "command", "Opt_1_def": "amount", "Opt_2_def": "more than 50%", "Opt_3_def": "control", "Opt_4_def": "a written agreement, binding in law"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "There is no ____ about it - the seafloor of Baku harbor is virtually dead.", "Opt_1": "portion", "Opt_2": "doubt", "Opt_3": "programme", "Opt_4": "facilities", "Answer": "doubt", "Opt_1_def": "part, amount", "Opt_2_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)", "Opt_3_def": "a course of lessons; a project", "Opt_4_def": "buildings and other places that can be used by people"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The temperatures did not ____ as much this month as they did last month.", "Opt_1": "fluctuate", "Opt_2": "prevent", "Opt_3": "attend", "Opt_4": "afford", "Answer": "fluctuate", "Opt_1_def": "to vary; to rise and fall", "Opt_2_def": "to stop from doing or happening", "Opt_3_def": "to go to, to be present at", "Opt_4_def": "to be able to pay for something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government of Israel again stated that the attack was not ____ and that it would be investigated.", "Opt_1": "likely", "Opt_2": "various", "Opt_3": "rapid", "Opt_4": "deliberate", "Answer": "deliberate", "Opt_1_def": "probable", "Opt_2_def": "several, of different kinds", "Opt_3_def": "quick", "Opt_4_def": "intentional, not by accident"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It is clear that the Mid-Zambezi Project has failed in its ____ of controlling immigration.", "Opt_1": "state", "Opt_2": "objective", "Opt_3": "diagram", "Opt_4": "journey", "Answer": "objective", "Opt_1_def": "condition, situation", "Opt_2_def": "aim or goal", "Opt_3_def": "a type of picture or chart", "Opt_4_def": "a long trip to a different place"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The chairman decided to ____ the meeting when people started shouting at each other.", "Opt_1": "terminate", "Opt_2": "trust", "Opt_3": "disturb", "Opt_4": "avoid", "Answer": "terminate", "Opt_1_def": "to finish or stop", "Opt_2_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised", "Opt_3_def": "to interrupt, stop from working", "Opt_4_def": "to not do something or go somewhere"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The future energy system will need to ____ the unacceptable risk that the present system places on the environment.", "Opt_1": "release", "Opt_2": "eliminate", "Opt_3": "collapse", "Opt_4": "collaborate", "Answer": "eliminate", "Opt_1_def": "to let go or let out", "Opt_2_def": "to dispose of", "Opt_3_def": "to fall down completely and heavily; to fail", "Opt_4_def": "to work together"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The company directors invited the workers' union to ____ in a meeting to discuss the new factory.", "Opt_1": "enhance", "Opt_2": "achieve", "Opt_3": "participate", "Opt_4": "protect", "Answer": "participate", "Opt_1_def": "to make something better", "Opt_2_def": "to gain or get something (often academic success)", "Opt_3_def": "to take part", "Opt_4_def": "to keep something out of danger"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "We further believe that the general quality of student writing will not ____ unless we as a department are willing to state explicitly the standards we require.", "Opt_1": "intervene", "Opt_2": "conceal", "Opt_3": "improve", "Opt_4": "edit", "Answer": "improve", "Opt_1_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)", "Opt_2_def": "to hide", "Opt_3_def": "to get better", "Opt_4_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Rules do not usually stimulate creativity or passion; rather they ____ conformity and make us fear change.", "Opt_1": "description", "Opt_2": "volume", "Opt_3": "demand", "Opt_4": "finance", "Answer": "demand", "Opt_1_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like", "Opt_2_def": "amount", "Opt_3_def": "a need or desire for", "Opt_4_def": "to do with money and payment"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Worse yet, 1992 was no ____ but the culmination of bad trends, most of them directly related to the company's lack of focus.", "Opt_1": "cause", "Opt_2": "diagram", "Opt_3": "anomaly", "Opt_4": "speed", "Answer": "anomaly", "Opt_1_def": "the reason why something happens", "Opt_2_def": "a type of picture or chart", "Opt_3_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data", "Opt_4_def": "how quickly something moves or changes"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Biology courses will ____ all major human or animal body systems.", "Opt_1": "cover", "Opt_2": "base", "Opt_3": "attempt", "Opt_4": "diverge", "Answer": "cover", "Opt_1_def": "to do; to complete", "Opt_2_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something", "Opt_3_def": "to try", "Opt_4_def": "to move apart; to be different from"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "We could not detect any significant effect of our dietary recommendations in terms of birth weight and ____ of pregnancy.", "Opt_1": "constraint", "Opt_2": "desire", "Opt_3": "duration", "Opt_4": "quality", "Answer": "duration", "Opt_1_def": "to hold back; to prevent", "Opt_2_def": "a want or wish for something", "Opt_3_def": "period of time", "Opt_4_def": "worth or value"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Each College or School should ____ the teaching of basic technology skills at the earliest level possible.", "Opt_1": "reveal", "Opt_2": "annotate", "Opt_3": "classify", "Opt_4": "integrate", "Answer": "integrate", "Opt_1_def": "to show or uncover", "Opt_2_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing", "Opt_3_def": "to put into a category or class", "Opt_4_def": "to fit into a new situation"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The sports hall is on the school grounds but it doesn't ____ to the school.", "Opt_1": "tolerate", "Opt_2": "dominate", "Opt_3": "multiply", "Opt_4": "belong", "Answer": "belong", "Opt_1_def": "to allow to happen; to bear", "Opt_2_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part", "Opt_3_def": "to increase greatly", "Opt_4_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The company's efforts to increase business over the past year failed to ____ the shareholders.", "Opt_1": "impress", "Opt_2": "refer", "Opt_3": "repeat", "Opt_4": "measure", "Answer": "impress", "Opt_1_def": "to create a favourable reaction", "Opt_2_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean", "Opt_3_def": "to do or say again", "Opt_4_def": "to find out how much there is of something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "As a consequence, it often takes many years of regular water quality data collection to statistically ____ a trend.", "Opt_1": "exceed", "Opt_2": "detect", "Opt_3": "confront", "Opt_4": "master", "Answer": "detect", "Opt_1_def": "to be more than or better than", "Opt_2_def": "to see, find or notice", "Opt_3_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)", "Opt_4_def": "to (gain) control"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Vegetable crops are the most important ____ group for small farms in southern states and their importance is expected to increase.", "Opt_1": "commodity", "Opt_2": "trait", "Opt_3": "survey", "Opt_4": "counsel", "Answer": "commodity", "Opt_1_def": "a product; something you can buy", "Opt_2_def": "characteristic; aspect", "Opt_3_def": "questionnaire; information gained by questioning people or data", "Opt_4_def": "advice; advisor"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The first of the allegations came from a woman who, in the opinion of the Committee, was not a ____ witness.", "Opt_1": "available", "Opt_2": "credible", "Opt_3": "forthcoming", "Opt_4": "chief", "Answer": "credible", "Opt_1_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_2_def": "believable", "Opt_3_def": "coming soon", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Stated simply, this principle means that averaged over large enough distances, one part of the Universe looks ____ like any other part.", "Opt_1": "approximately", "Opt_2": "hardly", "Opt_3": "definitely", "Opt_4": "respectively", "Answer": "approximately", "Opt_1_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_2_def": "not very much", "Opt_3_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_4_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Rumours about teachers ____ quickly through schools.", "Opt_1": "advise", "Opt_2": "migrate", "Opt_3": "announce", "Opt_4": "circulate", "Answer": "circulate", "Opt_1_def": "to say what someone should do; to give advice", "Opt_2_def": "to go to another place", "Opt_3_def": "to state (often in an official way)", "Opt_4_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The causes of gun and knife crime ____ young people is an important field of inquiry.", "Opt_1": "among", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "in, between", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Since that time two major surveys were conducted with an attempt to define the ____ of the problem.", "Opt_1": "theory", "Opt_2": "schedule", "Opt_3": "cause", "Opt_4": "scope", "Answer": "scope", "Opt_1_def": "idea or hypothesis", "Opt_2_def": "timetable", "Opt_3_def": "the reason why something happens", "Opt_4_def": "extent, range"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government clearly did not ____ carefully enough on the consequences of its new law.", "Opt_1": "suspend", "Opt_2": "exploit", "Opt_3": "reflect", "Opt_4": "retain", "Answer": "reflect", "Opt_1_def": "to stop (often for a short time only)", "Opt_2_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)", "Opt_3_def": "to think or consider", "Opt_4_def": "to keep"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The researchers did not ____ people with known chronic disease from their study.", "Opt_1": "establish", "Opt_2": "exclude", "Opt_3": "gather", "Opt_4": "construct", "Answer": "exclude", "Opt_1_def": "to begin or set up", "Opt_2_def": "to leave out; opposite of include", "Opt_3_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_4_def": "to make"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "We could not detect any ____ effect of our dietary recommendations in terms of birth weight and duration of pregnancy.", "Opt_1": "significant", "Opt_2": "deliberate", "Opt_3": "capable", "Opt_4": "permanent", "Answer": "significant", "Opt_1_def": "important, large", "Opt_2_def": "intentional, not by accident", "Opt_3_def": "able", "Opt_4_def": "lasting for ever or for a very long time"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Therefore, it is important to ____ low birth weight infants according to their weight for their gestational age.", "Opt_1": "accelerate", "Opt_2": "classify", "Opt_3": "solve", "Opt_4": "modify", "Answer": "classify", "Opt_1_def": "to get or make faster", "Opt_2_def": "to put into a category or class", "Opt_3_def": "to find an answer", "Opt_4_def": "to change"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The court decided to ignore the ____ of the mental health specialist.", "Opt_1": "opinion", "Opt_2": "theory", "Opt_3": "occasion", "Opt_4": "effect", "Answer": "opinion", "Opt_1_def": "view; what you think about someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "idea or hypothesis", "Opt_3_def": "time (opportunity)", "Opt_4_def": "result"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "I found a ____ of her homework on the cafeteria. It looked like half the school had stepped on it!", "Opt_1": "region", "Opt_2": "vary", "Opt_3": "struggle", "Opt_4": "fragment", "Answer": "fragment", "Opt_1_def": "part of a place", "Opt_2_def": "to change or be different", "Opt_3_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome", "Opt_4_def": "part of something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Some historians still hesitate to ____ the incidents of 1915 as 'genocide ', choosing to use words like 'massacre ' or 'atrocities ' to describe the events instead.", "Opt_1": "label", "Opt_2": "hesitate", "Opt_3": "appeal", "Opt_4": "separate", "Answer": "label", "Opt_1_def": "to give a name to someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to pause before saying or doing something", "Opt_3_def": "to complain against an official judgment; to make a strong request", "Opt_4_def": "to pull or put apart"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The ____ cause of the accident is that the driver fell asleep, but police are investigating the possibility of a terrorist attack.", "Opt_1": "probable", "Opt_2": "imaginary", "Opt_3": "urban", "Opt_4": "original", "Answer": "probable", "Opt_1_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers.", "Opt_2_def": "not real; from the imagination", "Opt_3_def": "of the town or city", "Opt_4_def": "the first of its kind"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "You are recommended to ____ the computer to do your writing.", "Opt_1": "attend", "Opt_2": "disrupt", "Opt_3": "tend", "Opt_4": "utilize", "Answer": "utilize", "Opt_1_def": "to go to, to be present at", "Opt_2_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage", "Opt_3_def": "to often behave in a certain way", "Opt_4_def": "to use"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Burning of coal is a ____ way to obtain energy, but it creates a serious amount of pollution.", "Opt_1": "basic", "Opt_2": "fundamental", "Opt_3": "capable", "Opt_4": "convenient", "Answer": "convenient", "Opt_1_def": "first or easy", "Opt_2_def": "very important", "Opt_3_def": "able", "Opt_4_def": "easy, not causing problems"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Her frequent absence from school is the ____ reason for her bad grades in the final exams.", "Opt_1": "authentic", "Opt_2": "familiar", "Opt_3": "verbal", "Opt_4": "principal", "Answer": "principal", "Opt_1_def": "real, genuine; not made-up or artificial", "Opt_2_def": "known; well-known", "Opt_3_def": "to do with words and language (especially the spoken language)", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Lorelei's fine efforts in starting and maintaining the list have done much to ____ group communication and interaction.", "Opt_1": "facilitate", "Opt_2": "append", "Opt_3": "advise", "Opt_4": "resist", "Answer": "facilitate", "Opt_1_def": "to make something easier", "Opt_2_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)", "Opt_3_def": "to say what someone should do; to give advice", "Opt_4_def": "to fight against"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The management wanted to dismiss the incompetent employee but could find no-one better to ____ him.", "Opt_1": "inspect", "Opt_2": "recognize", "Opt_3": "entitle", "Opt_4": "replace", "Answer": "replace", "Opt_1_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_2_def": "to know or understand (who someone is or what something is)", "Opt_3_def": "to give the right to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to put in or take the place of .."}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Her family were persecuted by the Nazis, so it's no surprise that she shows ____ against the Germans.", "Opt_1": "resident", "Opt_2": "bias", "Opt_3": "exponent", "Opt_4": "disaster", "Answer": "bias", "Opt_1_def": "a person who lives in a place", "Opt_2_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice", "Opt_3_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion", "Opt_4_def": "a huge problem or failure"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It was not a ____ of which he was particularly proud.", "Opt_1": "theory", "Opt_2": "motive", "Opt_3": "deed", "Opt_4": "concept", "Answer": "deed", "Opt_1_def": "idea or hypothesis", "Opt_2_def": "reason", "Opt_3_def": "an action", "Opt_4_def": "idea; understanding"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "We will facilitate growth and development in our ____ communities by serving as a key educational resource.", "Opt_1": "district", "Opt_2": "intention", "Opt_3": "tool", "Opt_4": "sum", "Answer": "district", "Opt_1_def": "region of a city", "Opt_2_def": "plan, aim", "Opt_3_def": "something used to do a job", "Opt_4_def": "an amount of money, total"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The rise in the price of oil is set to ____ in future years due to increased demand in countries such as China and India.", "Opt_1": "accelerate", "Opt_2": "tolerate", "Opt_3": "label", "Opt_4": "strive", "Answer": "accelerate", "Opt_1_def": "to get or make faster", "Opt_2_def": "to allow to happen; to bear", "Opt_3_def": "to give a name to someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to work or try hard"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "This assignment is ____ on September 23.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Although his letter did not ____ Atlanta as the location of the new school, the Educational Commission quickly decided the matter.", "Opt_1": "complicate", "Opt_2": "encounter", "Opt_3": "regret", "Opt_4": "stipulate", "Answer": "stipulate", "Opt_1_def": "to make things more complex or difficult", "Opt_2_def": "to meet or experience", "Opt_3_def": "to feel sorry (for doing or saying something)", "Opt_4_def": "to require"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "There are many things that people can do in the battle ____ global warming. For instance, they can turn off lights when they leave the room.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The ____ service in Germany is much better than that in England.", "Opt_1": "drain", "Opt_2": "train", "Opt_3": "separate", "Opt_4": "permit", "Answer": "train", "Opt_1_def": "to take away; to get rid of", "Opt_2_def": "to teach someone how to do a job", "Opt_3_def": "to pull or put apart", "Opt_4_def": "to allow"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The grant is not a sufficient ____ for the excellence and hard work of this faculty and staff.", "Opt_1": "persuade", "Opt_2": "criticize", "Opt_3": "reward", "Opt_4": "attract", "Answer": "reward", "Opt_1_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something", "Opt_2_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone", "Opt_3_def": "to give something (e.g. a prize) for good work or behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Colorado State University scientists have found a way to ____ improve the quality of laser light at extremely short wavelengths.", "Opt_1": "naturally", "Opt_2": "virtually", "Opt_3": "dramatically", "Opt_4": "hardly", "Answer": "dramatically", "Opt_1_def": "of course, obviously", "Opt_2_def": "almost", "Opt_3_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_4_def": "not very much"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "On the back of this form or on a separate sheet, write a thorough ____ describing yourself, your interests, and why you have applied.", "Opt_1": "mechanism", "Opt_2": "phase", "Opt_3": "statement", "Opt_4": "method", "Answer": "statement", "Opt_1_def": "procedure, process", "Opt_2_def": "a (short) period of time; stage", "Opt_3_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)", "Opt_4_def": "a way of doing something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Some parents do not ____ their daughters to go on school trips.", "Opt_1": "permit", "Opt_2": "deduce", "Opt_3": "diminish", "Opt_4": "prove", "Answer": "permit", "Opt_1_def": "to allow", "Opt_2_def": "to come to a conclusion about someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to get smaller or less important", "Opt_4_def": "to show to be true"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "After Iraq some people feel strongly that the USA should never again ____ in the affairs of other countries.", "Opt_1": "intervene", "Opt_2": "discuss", "Opt_3": "accomplish", "Opt_4": "owe", "Answer": "intervene", "Opt_1_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)", "Opt_2_def": "to talk about", "Opt_3_def": "to do or achieve", "Opt_4_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Under the new plan, the garden would ____ at its current location on Walnut and Virginia streets and the pumping station would be built on the northeast.", "Opt_1": "remain", "Opt_2": "request", "Opt_3": "decrease", "Opt_4": "speculate", "Answer": "remain", "Opt_1_def": "to stay; still exist", "Opt_2_def": "to ask politely", "Opt_3_def": "to get smaller, to go down", "Opt_4_def": "to think and talk about (often future events)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "We are in the middle of the most serious ____ with the governments of these peoples and nations.", "Opt_1": "operation", "Opt_2": "conflict", "Opt_3": "instance", "Opt_4": "statistic", "Answer": "conflict", "Opt_1_def": "procedure; happening; process", "Opt_2_def": "problem, struggle or battle", "Opt_3_def": "example", "Opt_4_def": "mathematical number"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Unlike normal children she cannot attach its ordinary meaning to the word \"blue\", so she cannot fully understand ____ sentences.", "Opt_1": "basic", "Opt_2": "technical", "Opt_3": "genuine", "Opt_4": "discrete", "Answer": "basic", "Opt_1_def": "first or easy", "Opt_2_def": "to do with machines or the way things work", "Opt_3_def": "real and authentic", "Opt_4_def": "separate"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The school chose not to ____ news of the teacher's accident.", "Opt_1": "communicate", "Opt_2": "deserve", "Opt_3": "broadcast", "Opt_4": "owe", "Answer": "broadcast", "Opt_1_def": "to convey information", "Opt_2_def": "to have the right to something", "Opt_3_def": "to tell or transmit (often by means of a television programme)", "Opt_4_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Antarctica is a very ____ environment. Many explorers have lost their lives there.", "Opt_1": "abundant", "Opt_2": "feasible", "Opt_3": "deficient", "Opt_4": "hostile", "Answer": "hostile", "Opt_1_def": "existing in large quantities", "Opt_2_def": "possible", "Opt_3_def": "poor, lacking in quantity or quality", "Opt_4_def": "unfriendly; dangerous; strongly opposed to"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Microsoft has promised that the forthcoming operating system will be more ____ than ever before.", "Opt_1": "credible", "Opt_2": "secure", "Opt_3": "several", "Opt_4": "commercial", "Answer": "secure", "Opt_1_def": "believable", "Opt_2_def": "safe", "Opt_3_def": "many (about 6 or seven)", "Opt_4_def": "to do with business"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The decision does not usually ____ to aliens who are under mandatory detention.", "Opt_1": "apply", "Opt_2": "manifest", "Opt_3": "degenerate", "Opt_4": "monitor", "Answer": "apply", "Opt_1_def": "to be relevant (to)", "Opt_2_def": "show", "Opt_3_def": "to get worse", "Opt_4_def": "to watch ( someone's or something's behaviour )"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Thus, the results obtained are ____ with the popular belief that alcohol intoxication causes males to view women as more attractive.", "Opt_1": "exact", "Opt_2": "commercial", "Opt_3": "consistent", "Opt_4": "formal", "Answer": "consistent", "Opt_1_def": "precise, opposite of approximate", "Opt_2_def": "to do with business", "Opt_3_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same", "Opt_4_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The lesson plans contained an incomplete description of learners, their background and ____ knowledge.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Certain items are not available at this time since the originals have been put into storage for the ____ of the construction.", "Opt_1": "structure", "Opt_2": "duration", "Opt_3": "drawback", "Opt_4": "hierarchy", "Answer": "duration", "Opt_1_def": "the way something is made or organized", "Opt_2_def": "period of time", "Opt_3_def": "disadvantage, problem", "Opt_4_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "You need to be careful not to ____ people that you meet on the internet They may not be who they claim to be..", "Opt_1": "suppose", "Opt_2": "trust", "Opt_3": "warn", "Opt_4": "revise", "Answer": "trust", "Opt_1_def": "to think, imagine", "Opt_2_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised", "Opt_3_def": "to notify (of possible danger)", "Opt_4_def": "to change (in order to improve)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The men searched the entire camp, digging ____ the snow and even into the earth, but no paper was found, no diaries and no documents.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "prior", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "before"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "After several failed attempts to ____ the dispute by the efforts of the local community, the case was transferred to the City Community Court.", "Opt_1": "define", "Opt_2": "settle", "Opt_3": "trigger", "Opt_4": "persuade", "Answer": "settle", "Opt_1_def": "to state what something is or means", "Opt_2_def": "to solve a problem or dispute", "Opt_3_def": "to (cause to) start", "Opt_4_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The ____ for references must conform to the guidelines in the approved style manual.", "Opt_1": "format", "Opt_2": "exponent", "Opt_3": "doubt", "Opt_4": "exercise", "Answer": "format", "Opt_1_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting", "Opt_2_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion", "Opt_3_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)", "Opt_4_def": "a piece of work, activity"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "When societies ____ into violence the result is all too familiar: the destruction of life and infrastructure, gross abuses of human rights.", "Opt_1": "insert", "Opt_2": "justify", "Opt_3": "accumulate", "Opt_4": "collapse", "Answer": "collapse", "Opt_1_def": "to put in", "Opt_2_def": "to give a reason for doing something", "Opt_3_def": "to grow; to gather together", "Opt_4_def": "to fall down completely and heavily; to fail"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "My overall ____ of him since he joined the class is very positive.", "Opt_1": "error", "Opt_2": "atmosphere", "Opt_3": "stereotype", "Opt_4": "opinion", "Answer": "opinion", "Opt_1_def": "a mistake", "Opt_2_def": "mood among people or groups", "Opt_3_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)", "Opt_4_def": "view; what you think about someone or something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The government ____ was cleared of protesters by riot police and police horses.", "Opt_1": "district", "Opt_2": "decision", "Opt_3": "plenty", "Opt_4": "prospect", "Answer": "district", "Opt_1_def": "region of a city", "Opt_2_def": "intention to do something, choice", "Opt_3_def": "many, lots of", "Opt_4_def": "chance, likelihood"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government hopes that its new tax law will ____ indirectly in a reduction in teenage pregnancy.", "Opt_1": "sum", "Opt_2": "profit", "Opt_3": "course", "Opt_4": "result", "Answer": "result", "Opt_1_def": "an amount of money, total", "Opt_2_def": "money gained", "Opt_3_def": "a subject or period of study", "Opt_4_def": "outcome, effect"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The ____ assumes a single step - that life originated on Earth - ahead of the more elaborate idea that life formed elsewhere and was subsequently transported to Earth.", "Opt_1": "liable", "Opt_2": "former", "Opt_3": "chief", "Opt_4": "feasible", "Answer": "former", "Opt_1_def": "likely to happen; at risk of happening", "Opt_2_def": "previous, the one before, the first of two", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "possible"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The Bible laid down some rules for the humane treatment of slaves but did not ____ the practice.", "Opt_1": "deserve", "Opt_2": "condemn", "Opt_3": "impress", "Opt_4": "trust", "Answer": "condemn", "Opt_1_def": "to have the right to something", "Opt_2_def": "to express strong disapproval", "Opt_3_def": "to create a favourable reaction", "Opt_4_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "His advice was to ____ short-term temptation when investing in stocks.", "Opt_1": "purchase", "Opt_2": "achieve", "Opt_3": "resist", "Opt_4": "recognize", "Answer": "resist", "Opt_1_def": "to buy", "Opt_2_def": "to gain or get something (often academic success)", "Opt_3_def": "to fight against", "Opt_4_def": "to know or understand (who someone is or what something is)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "A hunt for hazardous asteroids by University of Hawaii astronomers who use a ____ search strategy has paid off.", "Opt_1": "absent", "Opt_2": "sole", "Opt_3": "unique", "Opt_4": "imaginary", "Answer": "unique", "Opt_1_def": "being not there; missing", "Opt_2_def": "only", "Opt_3_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind", "Opt_4_def": "not real; from the imagination"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The university should not ____ students who take an extra year to complete their studies as lazy.", "Opt_1": "elect", "Opt_2": "label", "Opt_3": "affect", "Opt_4": "spread", "Answer": "label", "Opt_1_def": "to choose by voting", "Opt_2_def": "to give a name to someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to have an influence on", "Opt_4_def": "to move (over a wider area)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The CLAS Institute identifies, evaluates, and promotes effective and appropriate early intervention and preschool practices that are sensitive to ____ cultural and linguistic backgrounds.", "Opt_1": "diverse", "Opt_2": "compulsory", "Opt_3": "reliable", "Opt_4": "liable", "Answer": "diverse", "Opt_1_def": "many and different", "Opt_2_def": "required, must be done", "Opt_3_def": "can be trusted, does not let you down \r\n", "Opt_4_def": "likely to happen; at risk of happening"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Her problems are close to the ____ and tend to be expressed in more direct, less symbolic, behavioral and emotional terms.", "Opt_1": "support", "Opt_2": "exponent", "Opt_3": "surface", "Opt_4": "insight", "Answer": "surface", "Opt_1_def": "help", "Opt_2_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion", "Opt_3_def": "the outside layer of an object", "Opt_4_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "But his son, who had hoped to ____ the throne of Armenia, could not conceal his discontent.", "Opt_1": "occupy", "Opt_2": "circulate", "Opt_3": "discuss", "Opt_4": "insert", "Answer": "occupy", "Opt_1_def": "to up space or time", "Opt_2_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)", "Opt_3_def": "to talk about", "Opt_4_def": "to put in"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Indeed, we know that the Fleming, who was first to ____ the telescope, was a simple maker of ordinary spectacles.", "Opt_1": "eliminate", "Opt_2": "resist", "Opt_3": "consume", "Opt_4": "invent", "Answer": "invent", "Opt_1_def": "to dispose of", "Opt_2_def": "to fight against", "Opt_3_def": "to use, or use up", "Opt_4_def": "to create (often a new object)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The book is at its best when it delves energetically into some particular event, and draws out its ____ meaning with reference to the grand themes.", "Opt_1": "abstract", "Opt_2": "prime", "Opt_3": "remote", "Opt_4": "urban", "Answer": "abstract", "Opt_1_def": "not specific or concrete", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "far, distant, small", "Opt_4_def": "of the town or city"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Your main ____ for this lesson is to work together to prepare a presentation on air pollution.", "Opt_1": "experiment", "Opt_2": "task", "Opt_3": "decision", "Opt_4": "dimension", "Answer": "task", "Opt_1_def": "test", "Opt_2_def": "job", "Opt_3_def": "intention to do something, choice", "Opt_4_def": "importance; amount"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It is extremely important to ____ the installation with all parties involved.", "Opt_1": "interfere", "Opt_2": "justify", "Opt_3": "emerge", "Opt_4": "coordinate", "Answer": "coordinate", "Opt_1_def": "to prevent; to harm", "Opt_2_def": "to give a reason for doing something", "Opt_3_def": "to come out; to become known", "Opt_4_def": "to bring things or people together so that they work well"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Television and the other news media have helped to ____ the person and the institution of the presidency.", "Opt_1": "magnify", "Opt_2": "supervise", "Opt_3": "apply", "Opt_4": "invest", "Answer": "magnify", "Opt_1_def": "to make or show larger", "Opt_2_def": "to control; to watch over people doing something", "Opt_3_def": "to be relevant (to)", "Opt_4_def": "to put money into something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Janice Walker wanted to examine further ways to continue this great ____ to the company's staff as well as the company's productivity.", "Opt_1": "layer", "Opt_2": "innovation", "Opt_3": "supply", "Opt_4": "benefit", "Answer": "benefit", "Opt_1_def": "level", "Opt_2_def": "new object or idea", "Opt_3_def": "provision, store", "Opt_4_def": "advantage"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The school is planning to ____ the school day until 4:30.", "Opt_1": "participate", "Opt_2": "estimate", "Opt_3": "compete", "Opt_4": "extend", "Answer": "extend", "Opt_1_def": "to take part", "Opt_2_def": "to make an intelligent guess", "Opt_3_def": "to try and win against someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to make longer in time or space"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "He rightly concludes that the end of the Cold War failed to induce ____ changes in the Horn of Africa or to improve the mutual security of states.", "Opt_1": "capable", "Opt_2": "original", "Opt_3": "significant", "Opt_4": "initial", "Answer": "significant", "Opt_1_def": "able", "Opt_2_def": "the first of its kind", "Opt_3_def": "important, large", "Opt_4_def": "starting, first"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "She will ____ her chances of graduating unless she starts to attend school more regularly.", "Opt_1": "signify", "Opt_2": "harm", "Opt_3": "suspect", "Opt_4": "protect", "Answer": "harm", "Opt_1_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_2_def": "to damage or injure", "Opt_3_def": "to believe", "Opt_4_def": "to keep something out of danger"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "If submitted in other languages, an English ____ must accompany the submission.", "Opt_1": "version", "Opt_2": "portion", "Opt_3": "expert", "Opt_4": "comment", "Answer": "version", "Opt_1_def": "form", "Opt_2_def": "part, amount", "Opt_3_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field", "Opt_4_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "A snowstorm failed to ____ soccer practice on the Inlet early last week.", "Opt_1": "assemble", "Opt_2": "enforce", "Opt_3": "interrupt", "Opt_4": "conserve", "Answer": "interrupt", "Opt_1_def": "to get, put or bring together", "Opt_2_def": "to make something happen (particularly a law or regulation)", "Opt_3_def": "to stop something from happening", "Opt_4_def": "to preserve; to not use"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "There is no point having a law if the police are not ____ to enforce it.", "Opt_1": "abnormal", "Opt_2": "entire", "Opt_3": "willing", "Opt_4": "perpetual", "Answer": "willing", "Opt_1_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_2_def": "whole, all", "Opt_3_def": "happy or prepared to do something", "Opt_4_def": "continuing for ever; never disappearing"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Most western countries want to ____ with China. It's the largest market in the world and its developing fast.", "Opt_1": "unite", "Opt_2": "repeat", "Opt_3": "trade", "Opt_4": "protect", "Answer": "trade", "Opt_1_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_2_def": "to do or say again", "Opt_3_def": "to exchange products or services", "Opt_4_def": "to keep something out of danger"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "I ____ we are going to have a test on this. - You are right!", "Opt_1": "transmit", "Opt_2": "proceed", "Opt_3": "protect", "Opt_4": "suppose", "Answer": "suppose", "Opt_1_def": "to send or convey", "Opt_2_def": "to go forward (and do ..)", "Opt_3_def": "to keep something out of danger", "Opt_4_def": "to think, imagine"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The computer manager is trying to ____ who has been sending email spam to all the teachers and students.", "Opt_1": "destroy", "Opt_2": "detect", "Opt_3": "reserve", "Opt_4": "convey", "Answer": "detect", "Opt_1_def": "to break or damage completely", "Opt_2_def": "to see, find or notice", "Opt_3_def": "to keep", "Opt_4_def": "to pass on to another person (often by speaking)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "A company's success or continuation should not depend on the service of outside ____ contractors.", "Opt_1": "rapid", "Opt_2": "independent", "Opt_3": "abnormal", "Opt_4": "average", "Answer": "independent", "Opt_1_def": "quick", "Opt_2_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else", "Opt_3_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_4_def": "ordinary, typical"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "To develop a ____ approach to business, managers must utilize the strengths of their employees in assigning tasks.", "Opt_1": "relevant", "Opt_2": "vague", "Opt_3": "comprehensive", "Opt_4": "commercial", "Answer": "comprehensive", "Opt_1_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration", "Opt_2_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_3_def": "full, complete", "Opt_4_def": "to do with business"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The most serious objection raised against the survey questions the use of self-report scales to ____ prejudice.", "Opt_1": "formulate", "Opt_2": "assess", "Opt_3": "violate", "Opt_4": "explain", "Answer": "assess", "Opt_1_def": "to express", "Opt_2_def": "to judge or test", "Opt_3_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_4_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "For the purposes of this study, then, increasing the testing strength did not ____ more accurate results.", "Opt_1": "attach", "Opt_2": "yield", "Opt_3": "expand", "Opt_4": "arrange", "Answer": "yield", "Opt_1_def": "to put together with", "Opt_2_def": "to produce", "Opt_3_def": "to get bigger; to move into new areas", "Opt_4_def": "to plan to happen; to group together"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Some people have claimed that the sole reason for the invasion of Iraq was to ____ control of the oil fields.", "Opt_1": "revolution", "Opt_2": "facilities", "Opt_3": "gain", "Opt_4": "individual", "Answer": "gain", "Opt_1_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_2_def": "buildings and other places that can be used by people", "Opt_3_def": "to get; to increase in ..", "Opt_4_def": "one person"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "When a block of wood is gently put into still water, it will ____ by the force of gravity, until it has displaced a quantity of water, equal to its own.", "Opt_1": "select", "Opt_2": "protest", "Opt_3": "decrease", "Opt_4": "descend", "Answer": "descend", "Opt_1_def": "to choose", "Opt_2_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_3_def": "to get smaller, to go down", "Opt_4_def": "to go down"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Many people who are old and sick are comforted by their ____ in God.", "Opt_1": "guarantee", "Opt_2": "province", "Opt_3": "attention", "Opt_4": "belief", "Answer": "belief", "Opt_1_def": "to promise or assure that something will or will not happen", "Opt_2_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_3_def": "focus", "Opt_4_def": "what you think; what you believe in"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government plans to introduce an ____ for long-term unemployed people to start looking for work again.", "Opt_1": "incentive", "Opt_2": "exercise", "Opt_3": "factor", "Opt_4": "notion", "Answer": "incentive", "Opt_1_def": "reason to do something", "Opt_2_def": "a piece of work, activity", "Opt_3_def": "an aspect to be considered", "Opt_4_def": "idea; concept"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The first of the allegations came from a woman who, in the ____ of the Committee, was not a credible witness.", "Opt_1": "standard", "Opt_2": "opinion", "Opt_3": "degree", "Opt_4": "effort", "Answer": "opinion", "Opt_1_def": "quality", "Opt_2_def": "view; what you think about someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "amount", "Opt_4_def": "hard work; attempt"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The Bush administration will not back down on pursuing new sanctions against Iran over its nuclear program ____ questions about their effectiveness.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government neither intends to comment on the event nor even to ____ that it actually happened.", "Opt_1": "abuse", "Opt_2": "store", "Opt_3": "praise", "Opt_4": "admit", "Answer": "admit", "Opt_1_def": "to treat someone or something badly", "Opt_2_def": "to put something in a place where it can be found and used later", "Opt_3_def": "to express approval about something someone has done", "Opt_4_def": "to allow to enter"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "As a simple soldier he gained much ____ by conducting a retreat after all the superior officers had been killed or wounded.", "Opt_1": "precaution", "Opt_2": "error", "Opt_3": "growth", "Opt_4": "credit", "Answer": "credit", "Opt_1_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems", "Opt_2_def": "a mistake", "Opt_3_def": "development, increase", "Opt_4_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Nadeem has worked with FSU London since early 2004 as a permanent ____ of staff managing the Information Technology Systems.", "Opt_1": "intention", "Opt_2": "member", "Opt_3": "context", "Opt_4": "instance", "Answer": "member", "Opt_1_def": "plan, aim", "Opt_2_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization", "Opt_3_def": "the place or situation in which something is found", "Opt_4_def": "example"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "A respect for other cultures is ____ in the philosophy of our international school.", "Opt_1": "inevitable", "Opt_2": "necessary", "Opt_3": "permanent", "Opt_4": "inherent", "Answer": "inherent", "Opt_1_def": "cannot be changed or avoided; obvious", "Opt_2_def": "needed; very important", "Opt_3_def": "lasting for ever or for a very long time", "Opt_4_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "This was a ____ attempt at addressing the issue, and not a very scholarly or intellectual attempt.", "Opt_1": "proper", "Opt_2": "spontaneous", "Opt_3": "technical", "Opt_4": "entire", "Answer": "spontaneous", "Opt_1_def": "correct, appropriate", "Opt_2_def": "happening without warning or planning", "Opt_3_def": "to do with machines or the way things work", "Opt_4_def": "whole, all"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The science teacher planned to ____ how water evaporates more quickly in hot temperatures.", "Opt_1": "neglect", "Opt_2": "attract", "Opt_3": "abandon", "Opt_4": "demonstrate", "Answer": "demonstrate", "Opt_1_def": "to not think about or care for", "Opt_2_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like", "Opt_3_def": "to leave or give up", "Opt_4_def": "to show"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government has invested little money in the health system. The quality of hospital care is sure to ____ more and more.", "Opt_1": "preserve", "Opt_2": "manifest", "Opt_3": "sustain", "Opt_4": "deteriorate", "Answer": "deteriorate", "Opt_1_def": "forward,\" said Michele Gougeon.", "Opt_2_def": "show", "Opt_3_def": "to keep going; to maintain", "Opt_4_def": "to get worse"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The ____ between the United States and Mexico represents one of the greatest divisions of wealth on Earth.", "Opt_1": "boundary", "Opt_2": "phrase", "Opt_3": "asset", "Opt_4": "credit", "Answer": "boundary", "Opt_1_def": "limit, extent", "Opt_2_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure.", "Opt_3_def": "advantage", "Opt_4_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The most important thing to keep in mind as you begin working on your assignments is that a philosophy paper is not an obstacle to be overcome but an ____ to show what you have learned.", "Opt_1": "challenge", "Opt_2": "criterion", "Opt_3": "opportunity", "Opt_4": "period", "Answer": "opportunity", "Opt_1_def": "difficult situation; problem", "Opt_2_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something", "Opt_3_def": "chance", "Opt_4_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "During the period of time that a student is on probation, any further instance of misconduct will cause the Board seriously to consider requiring the student to ____ from the College.", "Opt_1": "diverge", "Opt_2": "suppress", "Opt_3": "withdraw", "Opt_4": "realize", "Answer": "withdraw", "Opt_1_def": "to move apart; to be different from", "Opt_2_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen", "Opt_3_def": "to go back or take away", "Opt_4_def": "to come to know or understand"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The student's answer may not address all parts of the question or may demonstrate an inaccurate or ____ analysis of the passage.", "Opt_1": "averse", "Opt_2": "superficial", "Opt_3": "elaborate", "Opt_4": "prompt", "Answer": "superficial", "Opt_1_def": "against", "Opt_2_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial", "Opt_3_def": "detailed; complex", "Opt_4_def": "quick; on or before time"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It was not a ____ of which he was particularly proud.", "Opt_1": "contrary", "Opt_2": "hierarchy", "Opt_3": "deed", "Opt_4": "propensity", "Answer": "deed", "Opt_1_def": "opposite", "Opt_2_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)", "Opt_3_def": "an action", "Opt_4_def": "tendency; desire"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "He was highly confidential and did not ____ his (personal) accomplishments.", "Opt_1": "broadcast", "Opt_2": "displace", "Opt_3": "enable", "Opt_4": "appreciate", "Answer": "broadcast", "Opt_1_def": "to tell or transmit (often by means of a television programme)", "Opt_2_def": "to push out or take the place of something or someone", "Opt_3_def": "to make something or someone able to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to understand (the value of someone or something)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The OCC provides ____ and legal advice in the development of policy, procedures, and strategy related to the management and operation of the UC Riverside campus.", "Opt_1": "status", "Opt_2": "counsel", "Opt_3": "sequence", "Opt_4": "performance", "Answer": "counsel", "Opt_1_def": "position, standing", "Opt_2_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_3_def": "the order in which things are arranged or happen", "Opt_4_def": "action or achievement"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Arming the Bosnian Serbs was regarded as a political ____ than a military issue.", "Opt_1": "rather", "Opt_2": "respectively", "Opt_3": "roughly", "Opt_4": "moreover", "Answer": "rather", "Opt_1_def": "instead", "Opt_2_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other", "Opt_3_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_4_def": "also .., what is more .."}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Hmong elders did not have symptoms before coming to the U.S. and question why diabetes exists in the U.S. There is no ____ for diabetes in the Hmong language.", "Opt_1": "support", "Opt_2": "equipment", "Opt_3": "episode", "Opt_4": "term", "Answer": "term", "Opt_1_def": "help", "Opt_2_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)", "Opt_3_def": "period of time", "Opt_4_def": "a word or expression"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The author had failed to ____ his report, so it was impossible to check the truth of his claims.", "Opt_1": "cooperate", "Opt_2": "allocate", "Opt_3": "annotate", "Opt_4": "measure", "Answer": "annotate", "Opt_1_def": "to work (well) with another person", "Opt_2_def": "to give to (to promise to give)", "Opt_3_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing", "Opt_4_def": "to find out how much there is of something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Kiewra found that students who did not even ____ the lecture but reviewed the instructor notes performed better than students who did ____ but failed to take notes.", "Opt_1": "attend", "Opt_2": "occur", "Opt_3": "advise", "Opt_4": "isolate", "Answer": "attend", "Opt_1_def": "to go to, to be present at", "Opt_2_def": "to happen; take place", "Opt_3_def": "to say what someone should do; to give advice", "Opt_4_def": "to separate something or someone from others"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Medical science now uses a computer scanning technique to examine the ____ of the human body.", "Opt_1": "atmosphere", "Opt_2": "boundary", "Opt_3": "occasion", "Opt_4": "interior", "Answer": "interior", "Opt_1_def": "mood among people or groups", "Opt_2_def": "limit, extent", "Opt_3_def": "time (opportunity)", "Opt_4_def": "inside"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Banks that adopt the Equator Principles ____ them globally to project financing in all industry sectors including mining, oil and gas, and forestry.", "Opt_1": "comprehend", "Opt_2": "explain", "Opt_3": "displace", "Opt_4": "apply", "Answer": "apply", "Opt_1_def": "to understand", "Opt_2_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to push out or take the place of something or someone", "Opt_4_def": "to be relevant (to)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "These findings suggest that something in the brain's pain-processing and pain-killing systems may ____ by race and ethnicity.", "Opt_1": "contrast", "Opt_2": "vary", "Opt_3": "entity", "Opt_4": "sequence", "Answer": "vary", "Opt_1_def": "difference", "Opt_2_def": "to change or be different", "Opt_3_def": "thing; body; organization", "Opt_4_def": "the order in which things are arranged or happen"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The company yesterday said it made a ____ of \ufffd\ufffd217.46 million for the six months to June.", "Opt_1": "intention", "Opt_2": "profit", "Opt_3": "field", "Opt_4": "equipment", "Answer": "profit", "Opt_1_def": "plan, aim", "Opt_2_def": "money gained", "Opt_3_def": "area of interest or study", "Opt_4_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "A foreigner who wants to become a ____ of the USA cannot have a criminal record.", "Opt_1": "citizen", "Opt_2": "asset", "Opt_3": "argument", "Opt_4": "error", "Answer": "citizen", "Opt_1_def": "person (member of a country)", "Opt_2_def": "advantage", "Opt_3_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)", "Opt_4_def": "a mistake"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Not everyone is fortunate enough to have internet ____ at home.", "Opt_1": "access", "Opt_2": "duty", "Opt_3": "power", "Opt_4": "command", "Answer": "access", "Opt_1_def": "the right to enter or use", "Opt_2_def": "responsibility, or job that you are required to do", "Opt_3_def": "the right or authority to do something", "Opt_4_def": "control"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "While you may not admit to political pressure, you must be ____ of its almost constant presence; and you must recognize it and be prepared to deal with it.", "Opt_1": "temporary", "Opt_2": "vital", "Opt_3": "imaginary", "Opt_4": "aware", "Answer": "aware", "Opt_1_def": "for a short or limited time", "Opt_2_def": "very important", "Opt_3_def": "not real; from the imagination", "Opt_4_def": "knowing"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Is this a ____ picture by Picasso or is it a fake?", "Opt_1": "genuine", "Opt_2": "superior", "Opt_3": "compatible", "Opt_4": "numerous", "Answer": "genuine", "Opt_1_def": "real and authentic", "Opt_2_def": "better", "Opt_3_def": "able to work with someone or something else", "Opt_4_def": "very many"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "My ____ impression of him is that he is very intelligent and that his poor behaviour is because of boredom.", "Opt_1": "accurate", "Opt_2": "eligible", "Opt_3": "preliminary", "Opt_4": "distinct", "Answer": "preliminary", "Opt_1_def": "exact, containing no mistakes", "Opt_2_def": "being entitled or qualified to do something", "Opt_3_def": "first; initial", "Opt_4_def": "clear and strong"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "How do we approach the essential and ____ problem of dealing with our own waste?", "Opt_1": "perpetual", "Opt_2": "genuine", "Opt_3": "effective", "Opt_4": "certain", "Answer": "perpetual", "Opt_1_def": "continuing for ever; never disappearing", "Opt_2_def": "real and authentic", "Opt_3_def": "good, working well", "Opt_4_def": "sure"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "My ____ mathematics teacher is sick so we have had a substitute for the last 2 weeks.", "Opt_1": "firm", "Opt_2": "appropriate", "Opt_3": "moderate", "Opt_4": "regular", "Answer": "regular", "Opt_1_def": "strong, cannot be changed", "Opt_2_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable", "Opt_3_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme", "Opt_4_def": "predictable, following a pattern; normal"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The teacher's threat to give the student a detention had an ____ impact on his behaviour.", "Opt_1": "forthcoming", "Opt_2": "immediate", "Opt_3": "mobile", "Opt_4": "trivial", "Answer": "immediate", "Opt_1_def": "coming soon", "Opt_2_def": "first (without delay)", "Opt_3_def": "moving; able to move", "Opt_4_def": "not important"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Most companies ____ to replace machines, like refrigerators or computers, if they break down in the first year.", "Opt_1": "guarantee", "Opt_2": "amount", "Opt_3": "reluctance", "Opt_4": "counsel", "Answer": "guarantee", "Opt_1_def": "to promise or assure that something will or will not happen", "Opt_2_def": "how much there is of something", "Opt_3_def": "unwillingness; hesitation", "Opt_4_def": "advice; advisor"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "This is not an ____ test for ESL beginners. It is far too difficult.", "Opt_1": "apart", "Opt_2": "dense", "Opt_3": "appropriate", "Opt_4": "consistent", "Answer": "appropriate", "Opt_1_def": "not together, separate", "Opt_2_def": "thick; full; detailed", "Opt_3_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable", "Opt_4_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "He has made ____ progress all year and should have no trouble passing his exams.", "Opt_1": "broad", "Opt_2": "several", "Opt_3": "superior", "Opt_4": "smooth", "Answer": "smooth", "Opt_1_def": "wide, extensive", "Opt_2_def": "many (about 6 or seven)", "Opt_3_def": "better", "Opt_4_def": "easy, unproblematic"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "African-Americans have disproportionately failed to ____ in American society.", "Opt_1": "fail", "Opt_2": "replace", "Opt_3": "prosper", "Opt_4": "exaggerate", "Answer": "prosper", "Opt_1_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly", "Opt_2_def": "to put in or take the place of ..", "Opt_3_def": "to do well; to become rich", "Opt_4_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Research shows that earnings ____ strongly with IQ levels.", "Opt_1": "offend", "Opt_2": "correlate", "Opt_3": "promote", "Opt_4": "refute", "Answer": "correlate", "Opt_1_def": "to go against; to upset", "Opt_2_def": "to have a close connection", "Opt_3_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job", "Opt_4_def": "to prove to be untrue; to deny"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Indeed, we know that the Fleming, who was first to ____ the telescope, was a simple maker of ordinary spectacles.", "Opt_1": "affect", "Opt_2": "invent", "Opt_3": "blame", "Opt_4": "assess", "Answer": "invent", "Opt_1_def": "to have an influence on", "Opt_2_def": "to create (often a new object)", "Opt_3_def": "to accuse", "Opt_4_def": "to judge or test"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Historically, there was compensation for crop and livestock losses, but the problem of estimating the damage and ____ of funds for compensation programs has been significant.", "Opt_1": "lack", "Opt_2": "figure", "Opt_3": "aim", "Opt_4": "region", "Answer": "lack", "Opt_1_def": "absence of a thing", "Opt_2_def": "number", "Opt_3_def": "goal or intention", "Opt_4_def": "part of a place"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "His examination failure did not ____ through lack of effort or ability but because of serious illness in the weeks before.", "Opt_1": "occur", "Opt_2": "convince", "Opt_3": "denote", "Opt_4": "modify", "Answer": "occur", "Opt_1_def": "to happen; take place", "Opt_2_def": "to (try and) get someone to believe something", "Opt_3_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_4_def": "to change"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The new policy means that faculty members can no longer enter or ____ grades for these classes online.", "Opt_1": "modify", "Opt_2": "represent", "Opt_3": "earn", "Opt_4": "reflect", "Answer": "modify", "Opt_1_def": "to change", "Opt_2_def": "to be; to show or indicate", "Opt_3_def": "to get money or another reward (usually by working for it)", "Opt_4_def": "to think or consider"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It started to ____ after much questioning that the reasons for his bad behaviour were problems at home.", "Opt_1": "predict", "Opt_2": "accept", "Opt_3": "emerge", "Opt_4": "select", "Answer": "emerge", "Opt_1_def": "to say what will happen in the future", "Opt_2_def": "to agree (to have)", "Opt_3_def": "to come out; to become known", "Opt_4_def": "to choose"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "However, no one ____ will be the sole reason for lack of admission to the program.", "Opt_1": "fund", "Opt_2": "phrase", "Opt_3": "consequence", "Opt_4": "criterion", "Answer": "criterion", "Opt_1_def": "money collected for a particular purpose", "Opt_2_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure.", "Opt_3_def": "result", "Opt_4_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The June 1992 Gender Equity Study found a significant ____ in salaries between men and women.", "Opt_1": "objective", "Opt_2": "fragment", "Opt_3": "shift", "Opt_4": "gap", "Answer": "gap", "Opt_1_def": "aim or goal", "Opt_2_def": "part of something", "Opt_3_def": "change", "Opt_4_def": "space, opening or time between"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The illegal downloading of music via the internet is widespread ____ young people.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Hydrogen has the potential to provide a clean, storable, transportable and renewable ____ of energy that can meet the need for power throughout the world.", "Opt_1": "source", "Opt_2": "comparison", "Opt_3": "design", "Opt_4": "ability", "Answer": "source", "Opt_1_def": "where something begins, where you can find something", "Opt_2_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different", "Opt_3_def": "planning (drawing)", "Opt_4_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Military power is not an appropriate ____ to transform the Middle East.", "Opt_1": "dimension", "Opt_2": "penalty", "Opt_3": "tool", "Opt_4": "fee", "Answer": "tool", "Opt_1_def": "importance; amount", "Opt_2_def": "negative consequence; punishment", "Opt_3_def": "something used to do a job", "Opt_4_def": "money for a service (e.g. a baking service)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The problem for France was that the population did not ____ of responsible citizens which were necessary for the desired liberal system.", "Opt_1": "consist", "Opt_2": "enable", "Opt_3": "provoke", "Opt_4": "inquire", "Answer": "consist", "Opt_1_def": "to have in it; to have as part of it", "Opt_2_def": "to make something or someone able to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to cause to happen", "Opt_4_def": "to ask"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Our ____ is to motivate each student to achieve their full potential as they strive for success in our five cornerstones of Academic Excellence.", "Opt_1": "dedicate", "Opt_2": "accomplish", "Opt_3": "focus", "Opt_4": "dispose", "Answer": "focus", "Opt_1_def": "to devote (time and attention)", "Opt_2_def": "to do or achieve", "Opt_3_def": "to direct attention (on an issue)", "Opt_4_def": "to get rid of"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Children in Experiment 2 did not exhibit any ____ of recognizing the familiarized words in the passages.", "Opt_1": "assent", "Opt_2": "status", "Opt_3": "evidence", "Opt_4": "occasion", "Answer": "evidence", "Opt_1_def": "agreement", "Opt_2_def": "position, standing", "Opt_3_def": "proof, signs", "Opt_4_def": "time (opportunity)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "This project involves students in the process of learning in an attempt to ____ their skills and their successes across all areas of the course.", "Opt_1": "enhance", "Opt_2": "ban", "Opt_3": "attract", "Opt_4": "prevail", "Answer": "enhance", "Opt_1_def": "to make something better", "Opt_2_def": "to prohibit or forbid", "Opt_3_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like", "Opt_4_def": "to succeed; to overcome"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "He has a strong ____ against religion since suffering badly as a child in a strictly religious school.", "Opt_1": "bulk", "Opt_2": "progress", "Opt_3": "record", "Opt_4": "bias", "Answer": "bias", "Opt_1_def": "majority; largest part", "Opt_2_def": "improvement or development", "Opt_3_def": "evidence; documentation", "Opt_4_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Some students will ____ that advertising does not \"mean\" anything; they may feel that ads have little effect on the way people think and act.", "Opt_1": "comply", "Opt_2": "inhibit", "Opt_3": "insist", "Opt_4": "expose", "Answer": "insist", "Opt_1_def": "to do what someone asks or orders", "Opt_2_def": "to prevent or stop", "Opt_3_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim", "Opt_4_def": "to uncover, reveal"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The army sent 2,000 of its soldiers to ____ clothing to the refugees driven out of their homes by fighting.", "Opt_1": "address", "Opt_2": "isolate", "Opt_3": "distribute", "Opt_4": "create", "Answer": "distribute", "Opt_1_def": "to give attention to (an issue)", "Opt_2_def": "to separate something or someone from others", "Opt_3_def": "to give out", "Opt_4_def": "to make; to use your imagination to make something new"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The case of Nicaragua demonstrates how the United States failed to ____ on the implementation of democratic procedures.", "Opt_1": "abandon", "Opt_2": "insist", "Opt_3": "survive", "Opt_4": "donate", "Answer": "insist", "Opt_1_def": "to leave or give up", "Opt_2_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim", "Opt_3_def": "to not die", "Opt_4_def": "to give (usually money)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "There is no mechanism in the master plan to ____ whether or not we are doing what we are supposed to do.", "Opt_1": "protest", "Opt_2": "assess", "Opt_3": "qualify", "Opt_4": "resist", "Answer": "assess", "Opt_1_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_2_def": "to judge or test", "Opt_3_def": "to become eligible", "Opt_4_def": "to fight against"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The school needs to address the ____ problem of bullying among grade 7 students.", "Opt_1": "hostile", "Opt_2": "credible", "Opt_3": "ambiguous", "Opt_4": "serious", "Answer": "serious", "Opt_1_def": "unfriendly; dangerous; strongly opposed to", "Opt_2_def": "believable", "Opt_3_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation", "Opt_4_def": "severe, large"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The greatest ____ that we face is to reduce global warming.", "Opt_1": "sum", "Opt_2": "income", "Opt_3": "challenge", "Opt_4": "prejudice", "Answer": "challenge", "Opt_1_def": "an amount of money, total", "Opt_2_def": "money earned", "Opt_3_def": "difficult situation; problem", "Opt_4_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "I often find it difficult to ____ my advice so that the ESL beginners in the class can understand me.", "Opt_1": "disturb", "Opt_2": "formulate", "Opt_3": "control", "Opt_4": "own", "Answer": "formulate", "Opt_1_def": "to interrupt, stop from working", "Opt_2_def": "to express", "Opt_3_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone", "Opt_4_def": "to have or possess"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The Prime Minister broke off her visit to China ____ to an urgent problem at home.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The geographer urges upon his students that they first master those principles and then consider the ____ problems.", "Opt_1": "identical", "Opt_2": "subsequent", "Opt_3": "instant", "Opt_4": "legitimate", "Answer": "subsequent", "Opt_1_def": "exactly the same", "Opt_2_def": "next, following", "Opt_3_def": "immediate", "Opt_4_def": "correct; allowed"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The ____ way of attacking the security of computer programs is to feed them unexpected and deceptive inputs.", "Opt_1": "domestic", "Opt_2": "slight", "Opt_3": "abstract", "Opt_4": "classic", "Answer": "classic", "Opt_1_def": "home", "Opt_2_def": "small", "Opt_3_def": "not specific or concrete", "Opt_4_def": "very good, the best or most used"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The machine did not work properly because the person installing it did not ____ the instructions.", "Opt_1": "violate", "Opt_2": "obey", "Opt_3": "possess", "Opt_4": "accompany", "Answer": "obey", "Opt_1_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_2_def": "to do as commanded or expected", "Opt_3_def": "to have or own", "Opt_4_def": "to go with someone or something; to exist together"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Giuliani's leadership during New York City's darkest hours of the September 11th terrorist attacks earned him global ____ and admiration.", "Opt_1": "underlie", "Opt_2": "diminish", "Opt_3": "praise", "Opt_4": "blame", "Answer": "praise", "Opt_1_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something", "Opt_2_def": "to get smaller or less important", "Opt_3_def": "to express approval about something someone has done", "Opt_4_def": "to accuse"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "English may be a global language but it is not yet a ____ tool for exploring most of the world's societies and cultures.", "Opt_1": "proper", "Opt_2": "valid", "Opt_3": "likely", "Opt_4": "various", "Answer": "proper", "Opt_1_def": "correct, appropriate", "Opt_2_def": "correct", "Opt_3_def": "probable", "Opt_4_def": "several, of different kinds"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "There are ____ of things that the new government needs to change when it comes into power.", "Opt_1": "structure", "Opt_2": "transition", "Opt_3": "occasion", "Opt_4": "plenty", "Answer": "plenty", "Opt_1_def": "the way something is made or organized", "Opt_2_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_3_def": "time (opportunity)", "Opt_4_def": "many, lots of"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Knowing when to seek treatment for ____ health disorders is important for parents and families.", "Opt_1": "instant", "Opt_2": "mental", "Opt_3": "royal", "Opt_4": "rigid", "Answer": "mental", "Opt_1_def": "immediate", "Opt_2_def": "of the brain or mind", "Opt_3_def": "of kings and queens", "Opt_4_def": "strict, unbending"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The police are looking for a woman of ____ height, last seen wearing a red jacket.", "Opt_1": "medium", "Opt_2": "liable", "Opt_3": "overall", "Opt_4": "latter", "Answer": "medium", "Opt_1_def": "in the middle", "Opt_2_def": "likely to happen; at risk of happening", "Opt_3_def": "general", "Opt_4_def": "the second of two things mentioned"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Demonstrators tried to ____ the opening of the new airport runway.", "Opt_1": "accompany", "Opt_2": "postpone", "Opt_3": "discern", "Opt_4": "frustrate", "Answer": "frustrate", "Opt_1_def": "to go with someone or something; to exist together", "Opt_2_def": "to put back in time", "Opt_3_def": "to see; to perceive", "Opt_4_def": "to stop or prevent"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The purpose of this tutorial is to give you an idea of the ____ of events leading up to graduation.", "Opt_1": "cause", "Opt_2": "command", "Opt_3": "sequence", "Opt_4": "impact", "Answer": "sequence", "Opt_1_def": "the reason why something happens", "Opt_2_def": "control", "Opt_3_def": "the order in which things are arranged or happen", "Opt_4_def": "effect"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The strategy failed to ____ workers themselves to consider domestic service as anything other than a temporary transition.", "Opt_1": "disperse", "Opt_2": "halt", "Opt_3": "admit", "Opt_4": "persuade", "Answer": "persuade", "Opt_1_def": "to spread out; to move apart", "Opt_2_def": "to stop", "Opt_3_def": "to allow to enter", "Opt_4_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "One can fill a small book just describing the commonsense knowledge needed to solve an ____ problem like how to get to the airport.", "Opt_1": "instant", "Opt_2": "abundant", "Opt_3": "ordinary", "Opt_4": "bold", "Answer": "ordinary", "Opt_1_def": "immediate", "Opt_2_def": "existing in large quantities", "Opt_3_def": "usual, typical, every day", "Opt_4_def": "brave"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The number of students at the school with learning difficulties has begun to ____ in the last few years.", "Opt_1": "convey", "Opt_2": "donate", "Opt_3": "expel", "Opt_4": "decline", "Answer": "decline", "Opt_1_def": "to pass on to another person (often by speaking)", "Opt_2_def": "to give (usually money)", "Opt_3_def": "to drive or push out", "Opt_4_def": "to go down or get worse"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The ____ way of attacking the security of computer programs is to feed them unexpected and deceptive inputs.", "Opt_1": "classic", "Opt_2": "utter", "Opt_3": "reliable", "Opt_4": "positive", "Answer": "classic", "Opt_1_def": "very good, the best or most used", "Opt_2_def": "complete, total", "Opt_3_def": "can be trusted, does not let you down \r\n", "Opt_4_def": "good; optimistic"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "If faculty ____ that a mental health problem may be the cause of a student's violation of the Student Code of Conduct, they should contact the Dean of Students immediately.", "Opt_1": "decrease", "Opt_2": "enlarge", "Opt_3": "suspect", "Opt_4": "expel", "Answer": "suspect", "Opt_1_def": "to get smaller, to go down", "Opt_2_def": "to make larger", "Opt_3_def": "to believe", "Opt_4_def": "to drive or push out"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The result of such ____ was increased poverty in Russia and lost belief in the fairness of governmental institutions.", "Opt_1": "degenerate", "Opt_2": "abuse", "Opt_3": "signify", "Opt_4": "conceal", "Answer": "abuse", "Opt_1_def": "to get worse", "Opt_2_def": "to treat someone or something badly", "Opt_3_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_4_def": "to hide"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Perhaps we will have to revive the ____ of the 'Child Friendly City'.", "Opt_1": "bias", "Opt_2": "coincidence", "Opt_3": "issue", "Opt_4": "relationship", "Answer": "issue", "Opt_1_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice", "Opt_2_def": "an uncommon happening of two things", "Opt_3_def": "a matter or problem", "Opt_4_def": "the way to things are connected"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Check the ____ below for specific dates and starting times.", "Opt_1": "statistic", "Opt_2": "schedule", "Opt_3": "sample", "Opt_4": "mixture", "Answer": "schedule", "Opt_1_def": "mathematical number", "Opt_2_def": "timetable", "Opt_3_def": "example; a smaller number of a larger collection", "Opt_4_def": "combination"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It's a total ____ that young girls are being pressured into near-starving themselves into being too thin.", "Opt_1": "level", "Opt_2": "expense", "Opt_3": "citizen", "Opt_4": "fallacy", "Answer": "fallacy", "Opt_1_def": "standard; layer; amount", "Opt_2_def": "cost", "Opt_3_def": "person (member of a country)", "Opt_4_def": "mistake; false belief"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "He had no good reason for being late, so he decided to ____ one.", "Opt_1": "request", "Opt_2": "invent", "Opt_3": "possess", "Opt_4": "correspond", "Answer": "invent", "Opt_1_def": "to ask politely", "Opt_2_def": "to create (often a new object)", "Opt_3_def": "to have or own", "Opt_4_def": "to be related to"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Though Sima and Codreanu both attempted to prevent the murder, it ____ took place, and produced harsh consequences.", "Opt_1": "overly", "Opt_2": "somewhat", "Opt_3": "nevertheless", "Opt_4": "thus", "Answer": "nevertheless", "Opt_1_def": "too", "Opt_2_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_3_def": "however (although / despite that)", "Opt_4_def": "so"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The conclusion did not ____ the truth of the situation even though the student ____ed some of the data that he collected.", "Opt_1": "distort", "Opt_2": "import", "Opt_3": "discern", "Opt_4": "precede", "Answer": "distort", "Opt_1_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)", "Opt_2_def": "to bring in (to a country)", "Opt_3_def": "to see; to perceive", "Opt_4_def": "to go or be before someone or something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Different newspapers will often have a different account of the same event - ____ newspapers from different parts of the world.", "Opt_1": "moreover", "Opt_2": "namely", "Opt_3": "somewhat", "Opt_4": "especially", "Answer": "especially", "Opt_1_def": "also .., what is more ..", "Opt_2_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_3_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_4_def": "particularly"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If you want to be successful in business, it is certainly an ____ to be able to speak more than one language.", "Opt_1": "controversy", "Opt_2": "power", "Opt_3": "advantage", "Opt_4": "volume", "Answer": "advantage", "Opt_1_def": "an issue on which their are strong and conflicting opinions", "Opt_2_def": "the right or authority to do something", "Opt_3_def": "benefit", "Opt_4_def": "amount"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Her problems began to ____ themselves after she was absent for more than a month.", "Opt_1": "estimate", "Opt_2": "manifest", "Opt_3": "occur", "Opt_4": "comply", "Answer": "manifest", "Opt_1_def": "to make an intelligent guess", "Opt_2_def": "show", "Opt_3_def": "to happen; take place", "Opt_4_def": "to do what someone asks or orders"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government will ____ its announcement until it has up-to-date information.", "Opt_1": "prohibit", "Opt_2": "postpone", "Opt_3": "review", "Opt_4": "recover", "Answer": "postpone", "Opt_1_def": "to ban, disallow", "Opt_2_def": "to put back in time", "Opt_3_def": "to check over (and make changes)", "Opt_4_def": "to get back"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "While you may not admit to political pressure, you must be ____ of its almost constant presence; and you must recognize it and be prepared to deal with it.", "Opt_1": "aware", "Opt_2": "invisible", "Opt_3": "sufficient", "Opt_4": "positive", "Answer": "aware", "Opt_1_def": "knowing", "Opt_2_def": "cannot be seen", "Opt_3_def": "enough", "Opt_4_def": "good; optimistic"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The government should not ____ its tax policies on what newspaper editors tell it to do.", "Opt_1": "base", "Opt_2": "attach", "Opt_3": "invent", "Opt_4": "receive", "Answer": "base", "Opt_1_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something", "Opt_2_def": "to put together with", "Opt_3_def": "to create (often a new object)", "Opt_4_def": "to get"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The World Bank said China has the capacity to absorb the ____ of the recent international financial market fluctuations.", "Opt_1": "magnitude", "Opt_2": "revenue", "Opt_3": "impact", "Opt_4": "ability", "Answer": "impact", "Opt_1_def": "size; amount", "Opt_2_def": "money, income", "Opt_3_def": "effect", "Opt_4_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "A typical problem is that many companies will only employ workers with experience, but how do young people ____ that experience if they are not given a job. This is called a \"vicious circle\".", "Opt_1": "insight", "Opt_2": "gain", "Opt_3": "term", "Opt_4": "standard", "Answer": "gain", "Opt_1_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)", "Opt_2_def": "to get; to increase in ..", "Opt_3_def": "a word or expression", "Opt_4_def": "quality"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Did anyone manage to ____ question 11?", "Opt_1": "solve", "Opt_2": "consent", "Opt_3": "accumulate", "Opt_4": "add", "Answer": "solve", "Opt_1_def": "to find an answer", "Opt_2_def": "to agree", "Opt_3_def": "to grow; to gather together", "Opt_4_def": "to include; to give or say extra"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "We do not ____ a unilateral ban on cosmetic testing on animals, nor do we reject the use of animals in biomedical research.", "Opt_1": "degenerate", "Opt_2": "derive", "Opt_3": "emphasize", "Opt_4": "advocate", "Answer": "advocate", "Opt_1_def": "to get worse", "Opt_2_def": "to come from or get from", "Opt_3_def": "to stress, to say something strongly", "Opt_4_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Your first piece of writing was very good, but the ____ ones have been of much lower quality.", "Opt_1": "economic", "Opt_2": "initial", "Opt_3": "subsequent", "Opt_4": "willing", "Answer": "subsequent", "Opt_1_def": "financial; to do with money", "Opt_2_def": "starting, first", "Opt_3_def": "next, following", "Opt_4_def": "happy or prepared to do something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "You will need to explain your situation as clearly as possible and ____ appropriate supporting documentation.", "Opt_1": "reserve", "Opt_2": "integrate", "Opt_3": "provide", "Opt_4": "identify", "Answer": "provide", "Opt_1_def": "to keep", "Opt_2_def": "to fit into a new situation", "Opt_3_def": "to give", "Opt_4_def": "to know or say who or what something is"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "While I am not in favor of teaching creationism in public schools, I am also not ____ to having it presented and examined.", "Opt_1": "sufficient", "Opt_2": "averse", "Opt_3": "entire", "Opt_4": "local", "Answer": "averse", "Opt_1_def": "enough", "Opt_2_def": "against", "Opt_3_def": "whole, all", "Opt_4_def": "in the area where you live or work"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "You will need to form project teams of two or three students, and then it will be your ____ to organize meetings.", "Opt_1": "decision", "Opt_2": "reply", "Opt_3": "detail", "Opt_4": "responsibility", "Answer": "responsibility", "Opt_1_def": "intention to do something, choice", "Opt_2_def": "an answer", "Opt_3_def": "a small piece of information", "Opt_4_def": "job, duty to do something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government received information but did not consider it reliable and ____ decided to ignore it.", "Opt_1": "simply", "Opt_2": "gradually", "Opt_3": "therefore", "Opt_4": "somewhat", "Answer": "therefore", "Opt_1_def": "completely; just; only", "Opt_2_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_3_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_4_def": "quite, rather"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "You need to do a better job when you ____ your work. There are far too many unnecessary spelling and punctuation errors.", "Opt_1": "protect", "Opt_2": "receive", "Opt_3": "edit", "Opt_4": "attach", "Answer": "edit", "Opt_1_def": "to keep something out of danger", "Opt_2_def": "to get", "Opt_3_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing", "Opt_4_def": "to put together with"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government needs to ____ more financial support to young married couples who want to buy a house.", "Opt_1": "offer", "Opt_2": "declare", "Opt_3": "maintain", "Opt_4": "depend", "Answer": "offer", "Opt_1_def": "to ask if someone would like something (e.g. food or help)", "Opt_2_def": "to state", "Opt_3_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_4_def": "be influenced (by)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It was a very ____ problem. All the students were able to solve it within 5 minutes.", "Opt_1": "adjacent", "Opt_2": "inherent", "Opt_3": "infinite", "Opt_4": "elementary", "Answer": "elementary", "Opt_1_def": "next to", "Opt_2_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of", "Opt_3_def": "without an end", "Opt_4_def": "easy"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If you discover that you have the wrong textbook, you must contact the ____ from which you purchased the book and make arrangements to exchange the book.", "Opt_1": "source", "Opt_2": "target", "Opt_3": "battle", "Opt_4": "compensation", "Answer": "source", "Opt_1_def": "where something begins, where you can find something", "Opt_2_def": "aim, goal", "Opt_3_def": "fight, part of a war", "Opt_4_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The Smartboard is an excellent ____ for teaching language.", "Opt_1": "goal", "Opt_2": "profit", "Opt_3": "device", "Opt_4": "resident", "Answer": "device", "Opt_1_def": "aim or intention", "Opt_2_def": "money gained", "Opt_3_def": "object; method", "Opt_4_def": "a person who lives in a place"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The applicant's qualifications must ____ to the qualifications required to perform the duties of the position as indicated in the job description.", "Opt_1": "amend", "Opt_2": "approve", "Opt_3": "impress", "Opt_4": "correlate", "Answer": "correlate", "Opt_1_def": "to change (usually to improve something)", "Opt_2_def": "to agree to", "Opt_3_def": "to create a favourable reaction", "Opt_4_def": "to have a close connection"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Most teachers are ____ to students wearing hats or chewing gum in the classroom.", "Opt_1": "vital", "Opt_2": "thorough", "Opt_3": "conscious", "Opt_4": "averse", "Answer": "averse", "Opt_1_def": "very important", "Opt_2_def": "complete and careful", "Opt_3_def": "aware, knowing", "Opt_4_def": "against"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The director was not prepared to even listen to ideas ____ to his own.", "Opt_1": "environment", "Opt_2": "balance", "Opt_3": "contrary", "Opt_4": "argument", "Answer": "contrary", "Opt_1_def": "the world around us", "Opt_2_def": "equalness", "Opt_3_def": "opposite", "Opt_4_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "People with eye problems often cannot ____ the colors red and green.", "Opt_1": "differentiate", "Opt_2": "procure", "Opt_3": "exert", "Opt_4": "control", "Answer": "differentiate", "Opt_1_def": "to make different; to see the difference", "Opt_2_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_3_def": "to use", "Opt_4_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The course introduces students to the structure and ____ of cities and ways planners solve urban problems.", "Opt_1": "response", "Opt_2": "journey", "Opt_3": "function", "Opt_4": "tradition", "Answer": "function", "Opt_1_def": "answer or reply; reaction", "Opt_2_def": "a long trip to a different place", "Opt_3_def": "job or role", "Opt_4_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Dinosaurs no longer ____ - they have been extinct for millions of years.", "Opt_1": "exist", "Opt_2": "enhance", "Opt_3": "imply", "Opt_4": "criticize", "Answer": "exist", "Opt_1_def": "to be alive, to be in the world", "Opt_2_def": "to make something better", "Opt_3_def": "to mean; to give to understand", "Opt_4_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The committee will investigate the ____ by which the decision was made.", "Opt_1": "revolution", "Opt_2": "volume", "Opt_3": "member", "Opt_4": "process", "Answer": "process", "Opt_1_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_2_def": "amount", "Opt_3_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization", "Opt_4_def": "a series of steps"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government should ____ all its energy to reducing unemployment.", "Opt_1": "comply", "Opt_2": "dedicate", "Opt_3": "speculate", "Opt_4": "modify", "Answer": "dedicate", "Opt_1_def": "to do what someone asks or orders", "Opt_2_def": "to devote (time and attention)", "Opt_3_def": "to think and talk about (often future events)", "Opt_4_def": "to change"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If the student contacts you before or after the ____ with a valid excuse, you can cancel the appointment without penalty.", "Opt_1": "prejudice", "Opt_2": "phrase", "Opt_3": "experiment", "Opt_4": "forecast", "Answer": "experiment", "Opt_1_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background", "Opt_2_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure.", "Opt_3_def": "test", "Opt_4_def": "prediction"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "She did not follow the directions on the label, ____ carefully reading it.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "We will also tell you how the ____ to take if you decide to use email as an official means of communication.", "Opt_1": "precaution", "Opt_2": "component", "Opt_3": "layer", "Opt_4": "rate", "Answer": "precaution", "Opt_1_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems", "Opt_2_def": "part of; an element of", "Opt_3_def": "level", "Opt_4_def": "quantity; proportion; speed"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "You need to ____ on your admissions application that you will have 24 credits completed at the time of attendance.", "Opt_1": "indicate", "Opt_2": "request", "Opt_3": "comply", "Opt_4": "discuss", "Answer": "indicate", "Opt_1_def": "to show or convey", "Opt_2_def": "to ask politely", "Opt_3_def": "to do what someone asks or orders", "Opt_4_def": "to talk about"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "She will need an ____ performance to have any chance of winning the game. Her opponent is much better.", "Opt_1": "ultimate", "Opt_2": "authentic", "Opt_3": "outstanding", "Opt_4": "invisible", "Answer": "outstanding", "Opt_1_def": "final or most important", "Opt_2_def": "real, genuine; not made-up or artificial", "Opt_3_def": "excellent", "Opt_4_def": "cannot be seen"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It is an insult in some countries to ____ an offer of the local food.", "Opt_1": "apply", "Opt_2": "reject", "Opt_3": "avoid", "Opt_4": "withdraw", "Answer": "reject", "Opt_1_def": "to be relevant (to)", "Opt_2_def": "to refuse", "Opt_3_def": "to not do something or go somewhere", "Opt_4_def": "to go back or take away"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Most scientists are more interested in the ____ of winning the Nobel Prize than the money they get for doing so.", "Opt_1": "contrast", "Opt_2": "prestige", "Opt_3": "transition", "Opt_4": "counsel", "Answer": "prestige", "Opt_1_def": "difference", "Opt_2_def": "fame and respect", "Opt_3_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_4_def": "advice; advisor"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Seed cleaning is not an ____ that requires a large amount of labor.", "Opt_1": "defect", "Opt_2": "extract", "Opt_3": "community", "Opt_4": "operation", "Answer": "operation", "Opt_1_def": "problem; mistake", "Opt_2_def": "to remove; to take out and use", "Opt_3_def": "a group of people", "Opt_4_def": "procedure; happening; process"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The committee needs to ____ of both teachers and parents.", "Opt_1": "contain", "Opt_2": "consist", "Opt_3": "announce", "Opt_4": "determine", "Answer": "consist", "Opt_1_def": "to have in it; to hold inside", "Opt_2_def": "to have in it; to have as part of it", "Opt_3_def": "to state (often in an official way)", "Opt_4_def": "to find out; to establish or identify; state"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The school offers basketball ____ in the vacation.", "Opt_1": "instruction", "Opt_2": "custom", "Opt_3": "scheme", "Opt_4": "occasion", "Answer": "instruction", "Opt_1_def": "advice or teaching how to do something; an order to do something", "Opt_2_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)", "Opt_3_def": "plan. idea, project", "Opt_4_def": "time (opportunity)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It is often necessary to revise a mathematical model several times in the course of an ____ operations research study.", "Opt_1": "elementary", "Opt_2": "urban", "Opt_3": "utter", "Opt_4": "uniform", "Answer": "urban", "Opt_1_def": "easy", "Opt_2_def": "of the town or city", "Opt_3_def": "complete, total", "Opt_4_def": "having the same qualities"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "He alleged that the state had adopted the policy of attacking the ____ independent media rather than targeting individual journalists as in the past.", "Opt_1": "subsequent", "Opt_2": "valid", "Opt_3": "related", "Opt_4": "entire", "Answer": "entire", "Opt_1_def": "next, following", "Opt_2_def": "correct", "Opt_3_def": "connected; having something to do with each other", "Opt_4_def": "whole, all"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The University of Maryland team is particularly focused on using their ____ to test drugs that may block cell-to-cell \"quorum-sensing\".", "Opt_1": "limit", "Opt_2": "vary", "Opt_3": "environment", "Opt_4": "device", "Answer": "device", "Opt_1_def": "extent, boundary", "Opt_2_def": "to change or be different", "Opt_3_def": "the world around us", "Opt_4_def": "object; method"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Computers are a much more ____ way of storing and retrieving large amounts of data than keeping it on paper in huge cabinets.", "Opt_1": "convenient", "Opt_2": "willing", "Opt_3": "efficient", "Opt_4": "formal", "Answer": "efficient", "Opt_1_def": "easy, not causing problems", "Opt_2_def": "happy or prepared to do something", "Opt_3_def": "working quickly and easily", "Opt_4_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Our focus is to motivate each student to achieve their full potential as they ____ for success in our five cornerstones of Academic Excellence.", "Opt_1": "diminish", "Opt_2": "strive", "Opt_3": "install", "Opt_4": "adhere", "Answer": "strive", "Opt_1_def": "to get smaller or less important", "Opt_2_def": "to work or try hard", "Opt_3_def": "to put in (often a machine or new system)", "Opt_4_def": "to keep to; to follow"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "There is land ____ the ice in Antarctica, but water ____ it at the North Pole.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "below"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The school is will continue to ____ problems in its attempt to attract new students unless it reduces its tuition fees.", "Opt_1": "analyze", "Opt_2": "expose", "Opt_3": "affect", "Opt_4": "undergo", "Answer": "undergo", "Opt_1_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it", "Opt_2_def": "to uncover, reveal", "Opt_3_def": "to have an influence on", "Opt_4_def": "to receive or experience"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Curiously absent from the report is any mention of the type of action that the State would have taken against the ____ sources of TCE.", "Opt_1": "capable", "Opt_2": "obsolete", "Opt_3": "typical", "Opt_4": "diverse", "Answer": "diverse", "Opt_1_def": "able", "Opt_2_def": "not used or needed any more; out of date", "Opt_3_def": "usual", "Opt_4_def": "many and different"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It's a serious attack on any community's authority to ____ and implement housing policies without consultation.", "Opt_1": "occur", "Opt_2": "arise", "Opt_3": "develop", "Opt_4": "exist", "Answer": "develop", "Opt_1_def": "to happen; take place", "Opt_2_def": "to happen", "Opt_3_def": "to grow or improve", "Opt_4_def": "to be alive, to be in the world"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The Earth's interior is divided into four layers, which is ____ of rocky planets.", "Opt_1": "novel", "Opt_2": "political", "Opt_3": "drastic", "Opt_4": "typical", "Answer": "typical", "Opt_1_def": "new", "Opt_2_def": "to do government and politics", "Opt_3_def": "severe; great", "Opt_4_def": "usual"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "One ____ of the internet that concerns many parents and teachers is that a huge amount of very offensive material is just a click away.", "Opt_1": "entity", "Opt_2": "instinct", "Opt_3": "feature", "Opt_4": "concept", "Answer": "feature", "Opt_1_def": "thing; body; organization", "Opt_2_def": "natural feeling or reaction", "Opt_3_def": "part, aspect", "Opt_4_def": "idea; understanding"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government plans to ____ heavier punishment for dropping litter in the streets.", "Opt_1": "compile", "Opt_2": "consent", "Opt_3": "defend", "Opt_4": "impose", "Answer": "impose", "Opt_1_def": "to put together (often in a list", "Opt_2_def": "to agree", "Opt_3_def": "to give reasons for", "Opt_4_def": "to force; to require to happen"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The ____ of the Urselbach river is high in the Taunus hills behind the school.", "Opt_1": "source", "Opt_2": "finance", "Opt_3": "attention", "Opt_4": "member", "Answer": "source", "Opt_1_def": "where something begins, where you can find something", "Opt_2_def": "to do with money and payment", "Opt_3_def": "focus", "Opt_4_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Only seniors have the ____ of using this room. You will have to wait until you are in grade 12.", "Opt_1": "agent", "Opt_2": "means", "Opt_3": "opportunity", "Opt_4": "privilege", "Answer": "privilege", "Opt_1_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone", "Opt_2_def": "way", "Opt_3_def": "chance", "Opt_4_def": "a right (to do something)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Most people have a vague ____ of their financial goals even if they have never written them down.", "Opt_1": "disaster", "Opt_2": "formula", "Opt_3": "tool", "Opt_4": "notion", "Answer": "notion", "Opt_1_def": "a huge problem or failure", "Opt_2_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "something used to do a job", "Opt_4_def": "idea; concept"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The Director develops and oversees an ____ program of professional development and leadership training for history and social science teachers.", "Opt_1": "elaborate", "Opt_2": "adequate", "Opt_3": "ambitious", "Opt_4": "thorough", "Answer": "ambitious", "Opt_1_def": "detailed; complex", "Opt_2_def": "good enough; ok", "Opt_3_def": "having high goals (especially in a career; challenging", "Opt_4_def": "complete and careful"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The continued presence of a huge military ____ in the Gulf area provides the necessary element of pressure to ensure implementation of obligations.", "Opt_1": "force", "Opt_2": "prove", "Opt_3": "behave", "Opt_4": "include", "Answer": "force", "Opt_1_def": "to make happen or to make someone do something", "Opt_2_def": "to show to be true", "Opt_3_def": "to act or do things in a certain way", "Opt_4_def": "to put in; to have in"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The ____ between mother and child is said to be the strongest of any personal relationships.", "Opt_1": "equipment", "Opt_2": "fragment", "Opt_3": "bond", "Opt_4": "episode", "Answer": "bond", "Opt_1_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)", "Opt_2_def": "part of something", "Opt_3_def": "link; tie", "Opt_4_def": "period of time"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "You have not got these words in the right order. In German the main verb must be the second ____ in the sentence.", "Opt_1": "issue", "Opt_2": "element", "Opt_3": "power", "Opt_4": "role", "Answer": "element", "Opt_1_def": "a matter or problem", "Opt_2_def": "aspect, part", "Opt_3_def": "the right or authority to do something", "Opt_4_def": "job or function"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "There is no point in turning on the computer. The ____ isn't working.", "Opt_1": "exert", "Opt_2": "exist", "Opt_3": "monitor", "Opt_4": "select", "Answer": "monitor", "Opt_1_def": "to use", "Opt_2_def": "to be alive, to be in the world", "Opt_3_def": "to watch ( someone's or something's behaviour )", "Opt_4_def": "to choose"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "He has two problems; ____ his inability to concentrate in class and his unwillingness to do homework.", "Opt_1": "absolutely", "Opt_2": "therefore", "Opt_3": "namely", "Opt_4": "gradually", "Answer": "namely", "Opt_1_def": "completely; 100%", "Opt_2_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_3_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_4_def": "slowly; steadily"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government are concerned about the ____ small number of people who voted in the last election.", "Opt_1": "dramatically", "Opt_2": "perhaps", "Opt_3": "accordingly", "Opt_4": "rather", "Answer": "dramatically", "Opt_1_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_2_def": "maybe, possibly", "Opt_3_def": "appropriate to; in compliance with", "Opt_4_def": "instead"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It is not necessarily subjected to a thorough analysis, ____ it will need to be evaluated by the user.", "Opt_1": "namely", "Opt_2": "universally", "Opt_3": "simply", "Opt_4": "thus", "Answer": "thus", "Opt_1_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_2_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_3_def": "completely; just; only", "Opt_4_def": "so"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The organization has published a ____ of its history since it was founded in 1965.", "Opt_1": "cycle", "Opt_2": "summary", "Opt_3": "figure", "Opt_4": "loss", "Answer": "summary", "Opt_1_def": "a complete series of events or processes", "Opt_2_def": "a short account of the most important details", "Opt_3_def": "number", "Opt_4_def": "removal or reduction"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "A headache may seem like a ____ problem, but it could be the sign of something more serious.", "Opt_1": "trivial", "Opt_2": "suitable", "Opt_3": "inevitable", "Opt_4": "moderate", "Answer": "trivial", "Opt_1_def": "not important", "Opt_2_def": "good for a particular job or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "cannot be changed or avoided; obvious", "Opt_4_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Even today some Russian people refuse to ____ Stalin with the terrible crimes that were committed when he was Russian leader.", "Opt_1": "broadcast", "Opt_2": "abandon", "Opt_3": "incorporate", "Opt_4": "associate", "Answer": "associate", "Opt_1_def": "to tell or transmit (often by means of a television programme)", "Opt_2_def": "to leave or give up", "Opt_3_def": "to include", "Opt_4_def": "to link to; to make a connection to"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The best way to ensure that your machine has a ____ name is to use your University account name for your computer name.", "Opt_1": "essential", "Opt_2": "unique", "Opt_3": "adjacent", "Opt_4": "exact", "Answer": "unique", "Opt_1_def": "very important", "Opt_2_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind", "Opt_3_def": "next to", "Opt_4_def": "precise, opposite of approximate"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "John continue to maintain that he gave me his homework, but I'm ____ he didn't.", "Opt_1": "flexible", "Opt_2": "certain", "Opt_3": "sane", "Opt_4": "relevant", "Answer": "certain", "Opt_1_def": "can be changed or bent", "Opt_2_def": "sure", "Opt_3_def": "reasonable; not mad", "Opt_4_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Looking up all the ____ words in an important passage should be considered a background check for all literary analysis.", "Opt_1": "former", "Opt_2": "key", "Opt_3": "superior", "Opt_4": "inherent", "Answer": "key", "Opt_1_def": "previous, the one before, the first of two", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "better", "Opt_4_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Some people have claimed that the ____ reason for the invasion of Iraq was to gain control of the oil fields.", "Opt_1": "complete", "Opt_2": "substantial", "Opt_3": "ancient", "Opt_4": "sole", "Answer": "sole", "Opt_1_def": "full or finished", "Opt_2_def": "large", "Opt_3_def": "very old", "Opt_4_def": "only"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "You must ____ at the top of the page how many words you wrote.", "Opt_1": "dedicate", "Opt_2": "tolerate", "Opt_3": "procure", "Opt_4": "indicate", "Answer": "indicate", "Opt_1_def": "to devote (time and attention)", "Opt_2_def": "to allow to happen; to bear", "Opt_3_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_4_def": "to show or convey"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "We had disagreed strongly over politics before, and while these arguments did not ____ our friendship in the least, I wished to avoid potential conflict.", "Opt_1": "distribute", "Opt_2": "strain", "Opt_3": "isolate", "Opt_4": "accomplish", "Answer": "strain", "Opt_1_def": "to give out", "Opt_2_def": "to put under stress or make difficult", "Opt_3_def": "to separate something or someone from others", "Opt_4_def": "to do or achieve"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Worse yet, 1992 was no ____ but the culmination of bad trends, most of them directly related to the company's lack of focus.", "Opt_1": "anomaly", "Opt_2": "habit", "Opt_3": "community", "Opt_4": "legislation", "Answer": "anomaly", "Opt_1_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data", "Opt_2_def": "something you do regularly", "Opt_3_def": "a group of people", "Opt_4_def": "governmental rule; law"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The police ____ give details of whom they have arrested until they know that the person will be charged with a crime.", "Opt_1": "seldom", "Opt_2": "occasionally", "Opt_3": "extremely", "Opt_4": "especially", "Answer": "seldom", "Opt_1_def": "rare", "Opt_2_def": "sometimes", "Opt_3_def": "very", "Opt_4_def": "particularly"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The district of most big cities around the main ____ station is often a dangerous place to be at night.", "Opt_1": "perceive", "Opt_2": "train", "Opt_3": "contain", "Opt_4": "assemble", "Answer": "train", "Opt_1_def": "to see; to become aware of with one of the senses; to think", "Opt_2_def": "to teach someone how to do a job", "Opt_3_def": "to have in it; to hold inside", "Opt_4_def": "to get, put or bring together"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Until ____ there have been few sources of information about the morphological and syntactic structure of the Kam language.", "Opt_1": "namely", "Opt_2": "recently", "Opt_3": "gradually", "Opt_4": "absolutely", "Answer": "recently", "Opt_1_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_2_def": "in the near past", "Opt_3_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_4_def": "completely; 100%"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The many demonstrators on the streets of the capital city were a clear ____ of the government's unpopularity.", "Opt_1": "symptom", "Opt_2": "argument", "Opt_3": "obligation", "Opt_4": "standard", "Answer": "symptom", "Opt_1_def": "sign (often of a disease or other problem)", "Opt_2_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)", "Opt_3_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_4_def": "quality"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "These ever-changing factors necessitate the creation of a ____ policy that can respond and adapt to the needs of our library users.", "Opt_1": "flexible", "Opt_2": "vital", "Opt_3": "commercial", "Opt_4": "legitimate", "Answer": "flexible", "Opt_1_def": "can be changed or bent", "Opt_2_def": "very important", "Opt_3_def": "to do with business", "Opt_4_def": "correct; allowed"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The website shows how schools ____ and use their resources.", "Opt_1": "allocate", "Opt_2": "eliminate", "Opt_3": "dispose", "Opt_4": "stimulate", "Answer": "allocate", "Opt_1_def": "to give to (to promise to give)", "Opt_2_def": "to dispose of", "Opt_3_def": "to get rid of", "Opt_4_def": "to interest, make grow or encourage"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "If you saved a file to a library PC running Windows prior to a crash or being logged out, you should be able to ____ it.", "Opt_1": "recover", "Opt_2": "degenerate", "Opt_3": "affect", "Opt_4": "exaggerate", "Answer": "recover", "Opt_1_def": "to get back", "Opt_2_def": "to get worse", "Opt_3_def": "to have an influence on", "Opt_4_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "This ____ that you will be able to add money from your bank account to your StanfordCardPlan using this new online service.", "Opt_1": "means", "Opt_2": "treatment", "Opt_3": "interval", "Opt_4": "formula", "Answer": "means", "Opt_1_def": "way", "Opt_2_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)", "Opt_3_def": "a period of time", "Opt_4_def": "a method of doing something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "This also helps you determine which variables it is essential to control to ____ an ambiguous answer.", "Opt_1": "displace", "Opt_2": "occur", "Opt_3": "oppose", "Opt_4": "avoid", "Answer": "avoid", "Opt_1_def": "to push out or take the place of something or someone", "Opt_2_def": "to happen; take place", "Opt_3_def": "to be against or fight against something", "Opt_4_def": "to not do something or go somewhere"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "A common science ____ for young people is to investigate the growth of plants under different soil, light and water conditions.", "Opt_1": "responsibility", "Opt_2": "experiment", "Opt_3": "decision", "Opt_4": "forecast", "Answer": "experiment", "Opt_1_def": "job, duty to do something", "Opt_2_def": "test", "Opt_3_def": "intention to do something, choice", "Opt_4_def": "prediction"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It would not be wise to ____ from our planned course of action.", "Opt_1": "deviate", "Opt_2": "recur", "Opt_3": "imply", "Opt_4": "fulfill", "Answer": "deviate", "Opt_1_def": "to be different", "Opt_2_def": "to happen again", "Opt_3_def": "to mean; to give to understand", "Opt_4_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "We would probably become engaged in discussions from which we could not ____ ourselves and therefore our freedom of action would be limited.", "Opt_1": "level", "Opt_2": "extract", "Opt_3": "individual", "Opt_4": "apparatus", "Answer": "extract", "Opt_1_def": "standard; layer; amount", "Opt_2_def": "to remove; to take out and use", "Opt_3_def": "one person", "Opt_4_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The results on the tests are ____ to expectations.", "Opt_1": "citizen", "Opt_2": "penalty", "Opt_3": "contrary", "Opt_4": "point", "Answer": "contrary", "Opt_1_def": "person (member of a country)", "Opt_2_def": "negative consequence; punishment", "Opt_3_def": "opposite", "Opt_4_def": "purpose; reason; value"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "My initial ____ was to resign, but then I changed my mind.", "Opt_1": "result", "Opt_2": "intention", "Opt_3": "pressure", "Opt_4": "description", "Answer": "intention", "Opt_1_def": "outcome, effect", "Opt_2_def": "plan, aim", "Opt_3_def": "force; influence; stress", "Opt_4_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The government is set to suffer a heavy defeat in the vote to ____ its new tax policy.", "Opt_1": "approve", "Opt_2": "afford", "Opt_3": "compel", "Opt_4": "prove", "Answer": "approve", "Opt_1_def": "to agree to", "Opt_2_def": "to be able to pay for something", "Opt_3_def": "to force or make happen", "Opt_4_def": "to show to be true"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Every piece of ____ ground in the town centre has already been built on.", "Opt_1": "spare", "Opt_2": "massive", "Opt_3": "valid", "Opt_4": "appropriate", "Answer": "spare", "Opt_1_def": "not needed", "Opt_2_def": "very large", "Opt_3_def": "correct", "Opt_4_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The ____ response of the Hu Jintao government has won widespread praise, both inside and outside China.", "Opt_1": "official", "Opt_2": "sound", "Opt_3": "prompt", "Opt_4": "external", "Answer": "prompt", "Opt_1_def": "approved by an authority", "Opt_2_def": "good; strong", "Opt_3_def": "quick; on or before time", "Opt_4_def": "outside"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government has become unpopular recently and is ____ to lose the coming election.", "Opt_1": "thorough", "Opt_2": "compulsory", "Opt_3": "liable", "Opt_4": "abnormal", "Answer": "liable", "Opt_1_def": "complete and careful", "Opt_2_def": "required, must be done", "Opt_3_def": "likely to happen; at risk of happening", "Opt_4_def": "not normal, unusual"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Therefore, if a farm has efficiency problems, simply expanding the operation may just ____ the problems.", "Opt_1": "notice", "Opt_2": "approach", "Opt_3": "purchase", "Opt_4": "magnify", "Answer": "magnify", "Opt_1_def": "to see or realize", "Opt_2_def": "to near; to get closer", "Opt_3_def": "to buy", "Opt_4_def": "to make or show larger"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "As life spans increase, the fraction of life spent in retirement will ____ unless we delay our exit from paid work.", "Opt_1": "target", "Opt_2": "rise", "Opt_3": "surface", "Opt_4": "command", "Answer": "rise", "Opt_1_def": "aim, goal", "Opt_2_def": "to go up", "Opt_3_def": "the outside layer of an object", "Opt_4_def": "control"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Al Gore ____ did not deserve the Nobel peace prize. On a personal level, he has not reduced his own carbon dioxide emissions.", "Opt_1": "absolutely", "Opt_2": "perhaps", "Opt_3": "conversely", "Opt_4": "universally", "Answer": "absolutely", "Opt_1_def": "completely; 100%", "Opt_2_def": "maybe, possibly", "Opt_3_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand", "Opt_4_def": "all over the world; by everyone"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Teacher trainees will need to master problem-solving strategies that ____ clear practical solutions to issues that affect those in poverty.", "Opt_1": "recover", "Opt_2": "occur", "Opt_3": "ban", "Opt_4": "offer", "Answer": "offer", "Opt_1_def": "to get back", "Opt_2_def": "to happen; take place", "Opt_3_def": "to prohibit or forbid", "Opt_4_def": "to ask if someone would like something (e.g. food or help)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "We could not ____ any significant effect of our dietary recommendations in terms of birth weight and duration of pregnancy.", "Opt_1": "import", "Opt_2": "degenerate", "Opt_3": "emphasize", "Opt_4": "detect", "Answer": "detect", "Opt_1_def": "to bring in (to a country)", "Opt_2_def": "to get worse", "Opt_3_def": "to stress, to say something strongly", "Opt_4_def": "to see, find or notice"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Your password should ____ only letters or numbers.", "Opt_1": "collaborate", "Opt_2": "supervise", "Opt_3": "contain", "Opt_4": "compete", "Answer": "contain", "Opt_1_def": "to work together", "Opt_2_def": "to control; to watch over people doing something", "Opt_3_def": "to have in it; to hold inside", "Opt_4_def": "to try and win against someone or something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "While a considerable degree of agreement was attained, a ____ approach to food policy could not be reached.", "Opt_1": "various", "Opt_2": "inherent", "Opt_3": "uniform", "Opt_4": "immediate", "Answer": "uniform", "Opt_1_def": "several, of different kinds", "Opt_2_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of", "Opt_3_def": "having the same qualities", "Opt_4_def": "first (without delay)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "What do western Louisville and the Appalachian region have in common ____ being two of the poorest areas in Kentucky?", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Unlike normal children she cannot attach its ____ meaning to the word \"blue\", so she cannot fully understand basic sentences.", "Opt_1": "widespread", "Opt_2": "compulsory", "Opt_3": "crucial", "Opt_4": "ordinary", "Answer": "ordinary", "Opt_1_def": "common", "Opt_2_def": "required, must be done", "Opt_3_def": "extremely important", "Opt_4_def": "usual, typical, every day"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government was fully ____ of the magnitude of its decision to go to war.", "Opt_1": "inevitable", "Opt_2": "subsequent", "Opt_3": "aware", "Opt_4": "urgent", "Answer": "aware", "Opt_1_def": "cannot be changed or avoided; obvious", "Opt_2_def": "next, following", "Opt_3_def": "knowing", "Opt_4_def": "very important, must be done immediately"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "An enormous amount of research has been conducted into the ____ by which young children learn to speak.", "Opt_1": "mechanism", "Opt_2": "objection", "Opt_3": "alternative", "Opt_4": "advantage", "Answer": "mechanism", "Opt_1_def": "procedure, process", "Opt_2_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval", "Opt_3_def": "other possibility", "Opt_4_def": "benefit"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The U.S. government likely approached China on this matter ____ to the announcement of sanctions, but did not receive a satisfactory response.", "Opt_1": "among", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "beneath", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "in, between", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "below", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "A regular driving license does not ____ the license holder to drive a bus or a truck.", "Opt_1": "override", "Opt_2": "entitle", "Opt_3": "speculate", "Opt_4": "exploit", "Answer": "entitle", "Opt_1_def": "to take precedence over; to disregard", "Opt_2_def": "to give the right to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to think and talk about (often future events)", "Opt_4_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Mrs Cho spoke on ____ of the Korean Parents Group and thanked the school for buying Korean books for the library.", "Opt_1": "performance", "Opt_2": "desire", "Opt_3": "innovation", "Opt_4": "behalf", "Answer": "behalf", "Opt_1_def": "action or achievement", "Opt_2_def": "a want or wish for something", "Opt_3_def": "new object or idea", "Opt_4_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It is inevitable that any ____ society will have some sort of taxation system.", "Opt_1": "complex", "Opt_2": "preliminary", "Opt_3": "ancient", "Opt_4": "explicit", "Answer": "complex", "Opt_1_def": "difficult, complicated", "Opt_2_def": "first; initial", "Opt_3_def": "very old", "Opt_4_def": "clearly and openly expressed"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "In other words, his father did not ____ the level of resources, whether they be human or monetary, necessary for success.", "Opt_1": "exchange", "Opt_2": "focus", "Opt_3": "arise", "Opt_4": "invest", "Answer": "invest", "Opt_1_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing", "Opt_2_def": "to direct attention (on an issue)", "Opt_3_def": "to happen", "Opt_4_def": "to put money into something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The organization has published a ____ of its history since it was founded in 1965.", "Opt_1": "summary", "Opt_2": "doubt", "Opt_3": "term", "Opt_4": "assent", "Answer": "summary", "Opt_1_def": "a short account of the most important details", "Opt_2_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)", "Opt_3_def": "a word or expression", "Opt_4_def": "agreement"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "If a child consistently begs to stay home from school, has extreme ____ of being away from a parent etc., there may be a cause for concern about the child.", "Opt_1": "fear", "Opt_2": "utilize", "Opt_3": "continue", "Opt_4": "lessen", "Answer": "fear", "Opt_1_def": "to be concerned or frightened about", "Opt_2_def": "to use", "Opt_3_def": "to carry on, not stop", "Opt_4_def": "to reduce"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "He said the ____ now should exclude events of the past and the focus should be on what the UN, the US and Iraq could do to achieve the results.", "Opt_1": "debate", "Opt_2": "proportion", "Opt_3": "tool", "Opt_4": "exponent", "Answer": "debate", "Opt_1_def": "formal discussion", "Opt_2_def": "amount; number; percentage", "Opt_3_def": "something used to do a job", "Opt_4_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "I was headed into new ____ not in what I was teaching but in how I was to teach it.", "Opt_1": "interior", "Opt_2": "operation", "Opt_3": "territory", "Opt_4": "aspect", "Answer": "territory", "Opt_1_def": "inside", "Opt_2_def": "procedure; happening; process", "Opt_3_def": "land; area (of interest)", "Opt_4_def": "environment that lifts people up,\" says Jain."}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The company has the liberty to ____ employees without giving a reason during the first 6 months of their employment.", "Opt_1": "represent", "Opt_2": "imply", "Opt_3": "degenerate", "Opt_4": "dismiss", "Answer": "dismiss", "Opt_1_def": "to be; to show or indicate", "Opt_2_def": "to mean; to give to understand", "Opt_3_def": "to get worse", "Opt_4_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "There is evidence that increases in short sale transactions ____ stock price declines.", "Opt_1": "mention", "Opt_2": "strive", "Opt_3": "precede", "Opt_4": "comply", "Answer": "precede", "Opt_1_def": "to say; state", "Opt_2_def": "to work or try hard", "Opt_3_def": "to go or be before someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to do what someone asks or orders"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "After listening to the students' assurance, the ____ decided not to block their plan for a sleepover in the school gym.", "Opt_1": "firm", "Opt_2": "prime", "Opt_3": "mobile", "Opt_4": "principal", "Answer": "principal", "Opt_1_def": "strong, cannot be changed", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "moving; able to move", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "A common teacher ____ to students who are not listening in class is: Pay attention.", "Opt_1": "master", "Opt_2": "edit", "Opt_3": "warn", "Opt_4": "request", "Answer": "request", "Opt_1_def": "to (gain) control", "Opt_2_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing", "Opt_3_def": "to notify (of possible danger)", "Opt_4_def": "to ask politely"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The Prime Minister broke off her visit to China due to an ____ problem at home.", "Opt_1": "mental", "Opt_2": "urgent", "Opt_3": "valid", "Opt_4": "principal", "Answer": "urgent", "Opt_1_def": "of the brain or mind", "Opt_2_def": "very important, must be done immediately", "Opt_3_def": "correct", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "His father's ideas were ____ and out of time. They were traditional views that were losing much of their appeal.", "Opt_1": "appropriate", "Opt_2": "superficial", "Opt_3": "obsolete", "Opt_4": "feasible", "Answer": "obsolete", "Opt_1_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable", "Opt_2_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial", "Opt_3_def": "not used or needed any more; out of date", "Opt_4_def": "possible"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The writer Emile Zola exposed the ____ to the general public in the literary newspaper L'Aurore (The Dawn) in a famous open letter to the President.", "Opt_1": "affair", "Opt_2": "community", "Opt_3": "situation", "Opt_4": "command", "Answer": "affair", "Opt_1_def": "an event or series of events", "Opt_2_def": "a group of people", "Opt_3_def": "circumstances", "Opt_4_def": "control"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It is often impossible to ____ the pronunciation of a word from its spelling alone.", "Opt_1": "establish", "Opt_2": "notice", "Opt_3": "conserve", "Opt_4": "infer", "Answer": "infer", "Opt_1_def": "to begin or set up", "Opt_2_def": "to see or realize", "Opt_3_def": "to preserve; to not use", "Opt_4_def": "to come to a conclusion about something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Your first piece of writing was very good, but the ____ ones have been of much lower quality.", "Opt_1": "subsequent", "Opt_2": "sane", "Opt_3": "drastic", "Opt_4": "obvious", "Answer": "subsequent", "Opt_1_def": "next, following", "Opt_2_def": "reasonable; not mad", "Opt_3_def": "severe; great", "Opt_4_def": "clear, evident"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Experts believe that the problem will ____ until the government takes it more seriously.", "Opt_1": "fade", "Opt_2": "adhere", "Opt_3": "recur", "Opt_4": "emphasize", "Answer": "recur", "Opt_1_def": "to disappear slowly", "Opt_2_def": "to keep to; to follow", "Opt_3_def": "to happen again", "Opt_4_def": "to stress, to say something strongly"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The ____ of the conflict remains very much in doubt.", "Opt_1": "income", "Opt_2": "image", "Opt_3": "insight", "Opt_4": "outcome", "Answer": "outcome", "Opt_1_def": "money earned", "Opt_2_def": "picture", "Opt_3_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)", "Opt_4_def": "result"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "About a quarter of the elementary and secondary students typically did not ____ with the teacher at all during class.", "Opt_1": "interact", "Opt_2": "ban", "Opt_3": "cease", "Opt_4": "explain", "Answer": "interact", "Opt_1_def": "to react, to affect and be affected", "Opt_2_def": "to prohibit or forbid", "Opt_3_def": "to stop", "Opt_4_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "In most school parents are asked to ____ to their child participating in sex education lessons.", "Opt_1": "embody", "Opt_2": "approach", "Opt_3": "illuminate", "Opt_4": "consent", "Answer": "consent", "Opt_1_def": "to be a good example of ..", "Opt_2_def": "to near; to get closer", "Opt_3_def": "to show clearly; to light up", "Opt_4_def": "to agree"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "My father's contract in Germany will ____ at the end of the year.", "Opt_1": "terminate", "Opt_2": "realize", "Opt_3": "explain", "Opt_4": "warn", "Answer": "terminate", "Opt_1_def": "to finish or stop", "Opt_2_def": "to come to know or understand", "Opt_3_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to notify (of possible danger)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "High school students who have completed this difficult ____ deserve a reward.", "Opt_1": "original", "Opt_2": "novel", "Opt_3": "liable", "Opt_4": "practical", "Answer": "novel", "Opt_1_def": "the first of its kind", "Opt_2_def": "new", "Opt_3_def": "likely to happen; at risk of happening", "Opt_4_def": "useful; possible"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Economics is the allocation of scarce resources ____ competing ends.", "Opt_1": "due", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "I usually keep a supply of ____ pencils in my desk, so that I can lend one to any student who comes without.", "Opt_1": "urgent", "Opt_2": "final", "Opt_3": "spare", "Opt_4": "ordinary", "Answer": "spare", "Opt_1_def": "very important, must be done immediately", "Opt_2_def": "last", "Opt_3_def": "not needed", "Opt_4_def": "usual, typical, every day"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The ____ of American voters have turned against the war in Iraq but not against the American troops and not against patriotism.", "Opt_1": "motive", "Opt_2": "majority", "Opt_3": "order", "Opt_4": "relationship", "Answer": "majority", "Opt_1_def": "reason", "Opt_2_def": "more than 50%", "Opt_3_def": "sequence, place", "Opt_4_def": "the way to things are connected"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The student could not ____ the basic factors in a solution to the problem.", "Opt_1": "identify", "Opt_2": "rotate", "Opt_3": "predict", "Opt_4": "label", "Answer": "identify", "Opt_1_def": "to know or say who or what something is", "Opt_2_def": "to turn or move (around)", "Opt_3_def": "to say what will happen in the future", "Opt_4_def": "to give a name to someone or something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It was not ____ to use the river as the source for your drinking water before you analyzed it.", "Opt_1": "explicit", "Opt_2": "wise", "Opt_3": "genuine", "Opt_4": "rapid", "Answer": "wise", "Opt_1_def": "clearly and openly expressed", "Opt_2_def": "intelligent; sensible", "Opt_3_def": "real and authentic", "Opt_4_def": "quick"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "A significant ____ of winning the bid for the next Olympic Games is that it will cost the country an enormous amount of money.", "Opt_1": "cause", "Opt_2": "statistic", "Opt_3": "drawback", "Opt_4": "bias", "Answer": "drawback", "Opt_1_def": "the reason why something happens", "Opt_2_def": "mathematical number", "Opt_3_def": "disadvantage, problem", "Opt_4_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "A new class of antibiotic drugs is not expected to ____ in the immediate future.", "Opt_1": "fluctuate", "Opt_2": "recur", "Opt_3": "advance", "Opt_4": "appear", "Answer": "appear", "Opt_1_def": "to vary; to rise and fall", "Opt_2_def": "to happen again", "Opt_3_def": "to go or move forward; to get better", "Opt_4_def": "to come, be seen"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The additional time is necessary to ____ him to make a sound decision on an Alaska natural gas transportation system.", "Opt_1": "judge", "Opt_2": "occur", "Opt_3": "override", "Opt_4": "enable", "Answer": "enable", "Opt_1_def": "to give an opinion about someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to happen; take place", "Opt_3_def": "to take precedence over; to disregard", "Opt_4_def": "to make something or someone able to do something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "He did not ____ to develop a particularly good balance in his own life until he was able to stop worrying about what others thought of him.", "Opt_1": "procure", "Opt_2": "qualify", "Opt_3": "manage", "Opt_4": "threaten", "Answer": "manage", "Opt_1_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_2_def": "to become eligible", "Opt_3_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to warn or show signs of danger"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "She was very feminine, yet very strong, very ____ under the surface.", "Opt_1": "frequent", "Opt_2": "main", "Opt_3": "tough", "Opt_4": "liable", "Answer": "tough", "Opt_1_def": "often", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "difficult, strong", "Opt_4_def": "likely to happen; at risk of happening"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The researchers did not ____ people with known chronic disease from their study.", "Opt_1": "deteriorate", "Opt_2": "exclude", "Opt_3": "incorporate", "Opt_4": "announce", "Answer": "exclude", "Opt_1_def": "to get worse", "Opt_2_def": "to leave out; opposite of include", "Opt_3_def": "to include", "Opt_4_def": "to state (often in an official way)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The School of Medicine will ____ the buildings in two phases.", "Opt_1": "transfer", "Opt_2": "ignore", "Opt_3": "abuse", "Opt_4": "occupy", "Answer": "occupy", "Opt_1_def": "to move to a different place or job", "Opt_2_def": "to take no notice of; to leave out (of consideration)", "Opt_3_def": "to treat someone or something badly", "Opt_4_def": "to up space or time"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The Euro has taken on a dimension far greater than its ____ substance.", "Opt_1": "technical", "Opt_2": "abstract", "Opt_3": "economic", "Opt_4": "homogeneous", "Answer": "economic", "Opt_1_def": "to do with machines or the way things work", "Opt_2_def": "not specific or concrete", "Opt_3_def": "financial; to do with money", "Opt_4_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The school will ____ use of the library for all students unless the student who damaged the photocopier is found.", "Opt_1": "recommend", "Opt_2": "suspend", "Opt_3": "declare", "Opt_4": "stress", "Answer": "suspend", "Opt_1_def": "to suggest something to someone because it is good", "Opt_2_def": "to stop (often for a short time only)", "Opt_3_def": "to state", "Opt_4_def": "to emphasize; to say what is important"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The main reason for not responding to terrorism was not an external issue, but an internal one: the government failed to ____ its duties.", "Opt_1": "manufacture", "Opt_2": "refer", "Opt_3": "exploit", "Opt_4": "fulfill", "Answer": "fulfill", "Opt_1_def": "to produce (with machines)", "Opt_2_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean", "Opt_3_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)", "Opt_4_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "This alone makes the book a worthwhile read for students whose received knowledge about Africans is often little more than a stereotype of ____ victims.", "Opt_1": "passive", "Opt_2": "reliable", "Opt_3": "liable", "Opt_4": "numerous", "Answer": "passive", "Opt_1_def": "not active; unresponsive", "Opt_2_def": "can be trusted, does not let you down \r\n", "Opt_3_def": "likely to happen; at risk of happening", "Opt_4_def": "very many"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "In 1986, 23 percent of parents said obedience was the most important ____ they expected from their children.", "Opt_1": "result", "Opt_2": "directions", "Opt_3": "trait", "Opt_4": "research", "Answer": "trait", "Opt_1_def": "outcome, effect", "Opt_2_def": "instructions", "Opt_3_def": "characteristic; aspect", "Opt_4_def": "study; the finding of information"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Please remember to ____ any rented vehicle before driving it and note any scratches or other damage to the vehicle on the rental form.", "Opt_1": "survive", "Opt_2": "precede", "Opt_3": "store", "Opt_4": "inspect", "Answer": "inspect", "Opt_1_def": "to not die", "Opt_2_def": "to go or be before someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to put something in a place where it can be found and used later", "Opt_4_def": "to look at carefully"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "A frequent error in editing is to fix a word or ____ at one part of a sentence and not see that the fix affected something else in the sentence.", "Opt_1": "phrase", "Opt_2": "legislation", "Opt_3": "truth", "Opt_4": "version", "Answer": "phrase", "Opt_1_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure.", "Opt_2_def": "governmental rule; law", "Opt_3_def": "actual reason or fact", "Opt_4_def": "form"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "You should not ____ that the test questions this semester will be on the same topics.", "Opt_1": "communicate", "Opt_2": "label", "Opt_3": "exaggerate", "Opt_4": "assume", "Answer": "assume", "Opt_1_def": "to convey information", "Opt_2_def": "to give a name to someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is", "Opt_4_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The mask must always ____ the actor in expressing both joy and grief.", "Opt_1": "construct", "Opt_2": "appreciate", "Opt_3": "integrate", "Opt_4": "inhibit", "Answer": "inhibit", "Opt_1_def": "to make", "Opt_2_def": "to understand (the value of someone or something)", "Opt_3_def": "to fit into a new situation", "Opt_4_def": "to prevent or stop"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Dr. Blumenthal begins by analyzing why health care reform ____ failed to pass Congress in 1994.", "Opt_1": "legislation", "Opt_2": "effect", "Opt_3": "diagram", "Opt_4": "alternative", "Answer": "legislation", "Opt_1_def": "governmental rule; law", "Opt_2_def": "result", "Opt_3_def": "a type of picture or chart", "Opt_4_def": "other possibility"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The ____ to the school grounds is the stream. You must not cross it.", "Opt_1": "duration", "Opt_2": "vary", "Opt_3": "interval", "Opt_4": "boundary", "Answer": "boundary", "Opt_1_def": "period of time", "Opt_2_def": "to change or be different", "Opt_3_def": "a period of time", "Opt_4_def": "limit, extent"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "But please keep in mind that the Internet doesn't replace ____ counseling.", "Opt_1": "scope", "Opt_2": "career", "Opt_3": "equipment", "Opt_4": "labour", "Answer": "career", "Opt_1_def": "extent, range", "Opt_2_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_3_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)", "Opt_4_def": "work"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Everyone knows the dangers of smoking, yet hundred of young people start the ____ each year..", "Opt_1": "limit", "Opt_2": "habit", "Opt_3": "portion", "Opt_4": "issue", "Answer": "habit", "Opt_1_def": "extent, boundary", "Opt_2_def": "something you do regularly", "Opt_3_def": "part, amount", "Opt_4_def": "a matter or problem"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "A respect for other cultures is ____ in the philosophy of our international school.", "Opt_1": "complex", "Opt_2": "inherent", "Opt_3": "considerable", "Opt_4": "practical", "Answer": "inherent", "Opt_1_def": "difficult, complicated", "Opt_2_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of", "Opt_3_def": "very big; very much", "Opt_4_def": "useful; possible"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "If the student refuses to leave after being requested to do so, the instructor may summon University Police to ____ the student.", "Opt_1": "remove", "Opt_2": "separate", "Opt_3": "demonstrate", "Opt_4": "base", "Answer": "remove", "Opt_1_def": "to take away", "Opt_2_def": "to pull or put apart", "Opt_3_def": "to show", "Opt_4_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "His examination failure did not ____ through lack of effort or ability but because of serious illness in the weeks before.", "Opt_1": "obey", "Opt_2": "occur", "Opt_3": "underlie", "Opt_4": "transmit", "Answer": "occur", "Opt_1_def": "to do as commanded or expected", "Opt_2_def": "to happen; take place", "Opt_3_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something", "Opt_4_def": "to send or convey"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "You are making very ____ progress in learning English! You only started learning a year ago, and you can already speak quite fluently.", "Opt_1": "public", "Opt_2": "rapid", "Opt_3": "familiar", "Opt_4": "competent", "Answer": "rapid", "Opt_1_def": "open to all; not private", "Opt_2_def": "quick", "Opt_3_def": "known; well-known", "Opt_4_def": "good at something (often a job)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The company was heavily in ____ after investing a lot of money in new machinery.", "Opt_1": "contrast", "Opt_2": "debt", "Opt_3": "incentive", "Opt_4": "event", "Answer": "debt", "Opt_1_def": "difference", "Opt_2_def": "something owed to another person (often money)", "Opt_3_def": "reason to do something", "Opt_4_def": "a happening"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The school had similar exam results to last year, with the ____ion ____ that mathematics scores were a little higher.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "He is an American citizen which obviously puts him in a different ____ from the kinds of individuals that the president has suggested might be suitable.", "Opt_1": "feature", "Opt_2": "category", "Opt_3": "sector", "Opt_4": "penalty", "Answer": "category", "Opt_1_def": "part, aspect", "Opt_2_def": "group of similar items", "Opt_3_def": "part; area", "Opt_4_def": "negative consequence; punishment"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Students will undertake comprehensive analysis of several works and will ____ a database of quality literature.", "Opt_1": "risk", "Opt_2": "earn", "Opt_3": "devise", "Opt_4": "compile", "Answer": "compile", "Opt_1_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure", "Opt_2_def": "to get money or another reward (usually by working for it)", "Opt_3_def": "to create or think up", "Opt_4_def": "to put together (often in a list"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "This is to be expected, of course, since natural selection is a natural process, and one cannot ____ moral principles from scientific findings.", "Opt_1": "derive", "Opt_2": "fade", "Opt_3": "justify", "Opt_4": "harm", "Answer": "derive", "Opt_1_def": "to come from or get from", "Opt_2_def": "to disappear slowly", "Opt_3_def": "to give a reason for doing something", "Opt_4_def": "to damage or injure"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Participants ____ a small amount of blood or saliva, which will be used as a comparison to blood from children with genetic diseases.", "Opt_1": "label", "Opt_2": "acknowledge", "Opt_3": "donate", "Opt_4": "provide", "Answer": "donate", "Opt_1_def": "to give a name to someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to agree with; admit to; give credit to", "Opt_3_def": "to give (usually money)", "Opt_4_def": "to give"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "This tells us that there is a very large market for us to ____ into, if we take advantage of the opportunities as they arise.", "Opt_1": "expand", "Opt_2": "realize", "Opt_3": "infer", "Opt_4": "ensure", "Answer": "expand", "Opt_1_def": "to get bigger; to move into new areas", "Opt_2_def": "to come to know or understand", "Opt_3_def": "to come to a conclusion about something", "Opt_4_def": "to make sure (of)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Nine tenths of an iceberg is under water and hence ____ to ships.", "Opt_1": "passive", "Opt_2": "deliberate", "Opt_3": "novel", "Opt_4": "invisible", "Answer": "invisible", "Opt_1_def": "not active; unresponsive", "Opt_2_def": "intentional, not by accident", "Opt_3_def": "new", "Opt_4_def": "cannot be seen"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Spending months at a time in orbit, the scientists will be able to observe changes on the earth ____ them from day to day.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "In ____ to make up a missed exam, you must produce written evidence within 48 hours of the exam which shows that you had a legitimate reason to do so.", "Opt_1": "manner", "Opt_2": "order", "Opt_3": "objection", "Opt_4": "compensation", "Answer": "order", "Opt_1_def": "way of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "sequence, place", "Opt_3_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval", "Opt_4_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The plants in many of the world's ____ places have not yet been analysed for their possible medical effects.", "Opt_1": "remote", "Opt_2": "rational", "Opt_3": "physical", "Opt_4": "subjective", "Answer": "remote", "Opt_1_def": "far, distant, small", "Opt_2_def": "base on reason, not on emotion or instinct", "Opt_3_def": "of the body", "Opt_4_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The goal is to produce world-class scholars with capabilities in research, teaching, and service within the ____ area of Information and Decision Sciences.", "Opt_1": "current", "Opt_2": "entire", "Opt_3": "broad", "Opt_4": "extraordinary", "Answer": "broad", "Opt_1_def": "happening now", "Opt_2_def": "whole, all", "Opt_3_def": "wide, extensive", "Opt_4_def": "very unusual"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Advertising often tries to promote the idea that the customer deserves to buy the product because they are ____ it!", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "If your ____ is temporary and is impacting only attendance, make sure you follow up with your professors and contact the Dean of Students Office.", "Opt_1": "condition", "Opt_2": "record", "Opt_3": "forecast", "Opt_4": "asset", "Answer": "condition", "Opt_1_def": "state", "Opt_2_def": "evidence; documentation", "Opt_3_def": "prediction", "Opt_4_def": "advantage"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Whereas the origin of galactic magnetic fields has long posed a challenge for astrophysicists to explain, they ____ feel that they can say where they were not formed.", "Opt_1": "perhaps", "Opt_2": "nevertheless", "Opt_3": "dramatically", "Opt_4": "moreover", "Answer": "nevertheless", "Opt_1_def": "maybe, possibly", "Opt_2_def": "however (although / despite that)", "Opt_3_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_4_def": "also .., what is more .."}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Most of the school's ____ comes from the school fees paid by the companies who send their employees to work in Germany.", "Opt_1": "revenue", "Opt_2": "attitude", "Opt_3": "surplus", "Opt_4": "concern", "Answer": "revenue", "Opt_1_def": "money, income", "Opt_2_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)", "Opt_3_def": "to be, go or make all the way around", "Opt_4_def": "worry, fear"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "During the ____ of time that a student is on probation, any further instance of misconduct will cause the Board seriously to consider requiring the student to withdraw from the College.", "Opt_1": "task", "Opt_2": "education", "Opt_3": "procedure", "Opt_4": "period", "Answer": "period", "Opt_1_def": "job", "Opt_2_def": "schooling", "Opt_3_def": "the way to do something", "Opt_4_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Use positive words and phrases; don't ____ the energy of the interview by focusing on the negative.", "Opt_1": "omit", "Opt_2": "inquire", "Opt_3": "drain", "Opt_4": "forego", "Answer": "drain", "Opt_1_def": "to leave something out or not do something", "Opt_2_def": "to ask", "Opt_3_def": "to take away; to get rid of", "Opt_4_def": "to do without; to give up"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "TOEFL is not the most ____ part of the application, but it is an unavoidable part, which sometimes can be quite painful and time- consuming.", "Opt_1": "verbal", "Opt_2": "crucial", "Opt_3": "confident", "Opt_4": "effective", "Answer": "crucial", "Opt_1_def": "to do with words and language (especially the spoken language)", "Opt_2_def": "extremely important", "Opt_3_def": "sure that something will happen", "Opt_4_def": "good, working well"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The journey to peace and prosperity in the region can only commence when the civic ____ is brought back in.", "Opt_1": "authority", "Opt_2": "institution", "Opt_3": "impulse", "Opt_4": "diagram", "Answer": "authority", "Opt_1_def": "control (right to control)", "Opt_2_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom", "Opt_3_def": "reason or motivation to do something", "Opt_4_def": "a type of picture or chart"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The problem is that parents start to ____ the expectation that we will provide unlimited services and that's just not feasible.", "Opt_1": "dispose", "Opt_2": "develop", "Opt_3": "block", "Opt_4": "regard", "Answer": "develop", "Opt_1_def": "to get rid of", "Opt_2_def": "to grow or improve", "Opt_3_def": "to not allow; to stop or prevent", "Opt_4_def": "to think or have an opinion about something or someone"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Some people have claimed that the ____ reason for the invasion of Iraq was to gain control of the oil fields.", "Opt_1": "artificial", "Opt_2": "subtle", "Opt_3": "numerous", "Opt_4": "sole", "Answer": "sole", "Opt_1_def": "not real or natural", "Opt_2_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_3_def": "very many", "Opt_4_def": "only"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Army leadership must emphasize the importance of reducing energy ____ to decrease costs.", "Opt_1": "demand", "Opt_2": "range", "Opt_3": "skill", "Opt_4": "account", "Answer": "demand", "Opt_1_def": "a need or desire for", "Opt_2_def": "extent, distance between two points", "Opt_3_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)", "Opt_4_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Employees must have worked for the State for at least five years, and have a ____ record of sick leave usage and work performance.", "Opt_1": "satisfactory", "Opt_2": "authentic", "Opt_3": "eligible", "Opt_4": "rigid", "Answer": "satisfactory", "Opt_1_def": "enough;OK", "Opt_2_def": "real, genuine; not made-up or artificial", "Opt_3_def": "being entitled or qualified to do something", "Opt_4_def": "strict, unbending"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "A student enrolled in these types of courses really didn't get to know the instructor well and ____ did not feel any sense of community.", "Opt_1": "definitely", "Opt_2": "indeed", "Opt_3": "namely", "Opt_4": "simply", "Answer": "definitely", "Opt_1_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_2_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_3_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_4_def": "completely; just; only"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If you fail the last test, this will seriously ____ your overall grade for the year.", "Opt_1": "affect", "Opt_2": "proceed", "Opt_3": "publish", "Opt_4": "constitute", "Answer": "affect", "Opt_1_def": "to have an influence on", "Opt_2_def": "to go forward (and do ..)", "Opt_3_def": "to make available in paper or online form", "Opt_4_def": "to be; to make up"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Perhaps the most elaborate example of an arthropod joint, ____ one of the most complex skeletal structures known, is the wing hinge of insects.", "Opt_1": "indeed", "Opt_2": "naturally", "Opt_3": "merely", "Opt_4": "greatly", "Answer": "indeed", "Opt_1_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_2_def": "of course, obviously", "Opt_3_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_4_def": "very much"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "After about a year his family realized that this was not just a ____ and that he was serious about me and that we really cared about each other.", "Opt_1": "term", "Opt_2": "phase", "Opt_3": "ratio", "Opt_4": "reply", "Answer": "phase", "Opt_1_def": "a word or expression", "Opt_2_def": "a (short) period of time; stage", "Opt_3_def": "mathematical relationship between two amount", "Opt_4_def": "an answer"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Computer disk drives have been known to suffer from power ____ failure, but this is not a concern for broadband modems.", "Opt_1": "materials", "Opt_2": "statistic", "Opt_3": "error", "Opt_4": "cycle", "Answer": "cycle", "Opt_1_def": "the things you need to do something", "Opt_2_def": "mathematical number", "Opt_3_def": "a mistake", "Opt_4_def": "a complete series of events or processes"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The Committee is concerned that children dropping out of school during the ____ stage of education have insufficient alternative educational opportunities.", "Opt_1": "verbal", "Opt_2": "vague", "Opt_3": "prime", "Opt_4": "compulsory", "Answer": "compulsory", "Opt_1_def": "to do with words and language (especially the spoken language)", "Opt_2_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "required, must be done"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "She always goes ____ what is expected of her. No wonder she gets such good grades.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The museum plans to ____ a collection of late works by Picasso.", "Opt_1": "topic", "Opt_2": "exhibit", "Opt_3": "choice", "Opt_4": "margin", "Answer": "exhibit", "Opt_1_def": "area of interest or discussion", "Opt_2_def": "to show", "Opt_3_def": "decision, selection", "Opt_4_def": "amount; distance"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The Committee will ____ the request for disability payment if the disability is not adequately documented.", "Opt_1": "reveal", "Opt_2": "assure", "Opt_3": "deny", "Opt_4": "invest", "Answer": "deny", "Opt_1_def": "to show or uncover", "Opt_2_def": "to make sure; to say that something will certainly happen", "Opt_3_def": "to refuse ( responsibility for doing or saying something); to say that something is not correct", "Opt_4_def": "to put money into something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Tourists who visit a foreign city often ____ a guide to show them the most interesting things to see.", "Opt_1": "employ", "Opt_2": "defend", "Opt_3": "cancel", "Opt_4": "confirm", "Answer": "employ", "Opt_1_def": "to give a job to someone; to use", "Opt_2_def": "to give reasons for", "Opt_3_def": "to cut or stop from happening", "Opt_4_def": "to agree that something is correct"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "A poorly selected specimen or inaccurate information may result in an erroneous ____ or an inappropriate control recommendation.", "Opt_1": "diagnosis", "Opt_2": "object", "Opt_3": "tradition", "Opt_4": "shift", "Answer": "diagnosis", "Opt_1_def": "assessment of a situation (particularly of a problem)", "Opt_2_def": "thing", "Opt_3_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things", "Opt_4_def": "change"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If you look at the course policies you will notice an ____ that accounts for 4% of your grade.", "Opt_1": "context", "Opt_2": "lecture", "Opt_3": "item", "Opt_4": "display", "Answer": "item", "Opt_1_def": "the place or situation in which something is found", "Opt_2_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "thing, element", "Opt_4_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The student must ____ the thesis before a committee of three or more faculty members.", "Opt_1": "belong", "Opt_2": "differentiate", "Opt_3": "defend", "Opt_4": "risk", "Answer": "defend", "Opt_1_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone", "Opt_2_def": "to make different; to see the difference", "Opt_3_def": "to give reasons for", "Opt_4_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "If you want your letter to be a private communication, I usually do not ____ sending copies to other people, since they may decide to act on the matter.", "Opt_1": "produce", "Opt_2": "gather", "Opt_3": "recur", "Opt_4": "recommend", "Answer": "recommend", "Opt_1_def": "to make or create", "Opt_2_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_3_def": "to happen again", "Opt_4_def": "to suggest something to someone because it is good"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "These tips do not relieve you of the ____ to read and follow the Instruction Booklet which is ONLY available on line this year!", "Opt_1": "obligation", "Opt_2": "proportion", "Opt_3": "resource", "Opt_4": "pattern", "Answer": "obligation", "Opt_1_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_2_def": "amount; number; percentage", "Opt_3_def": "a source of information or material", "Opt_4_def": "clear and consistent behaviour"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The expulsion of a student for smoking in the toilets caused a big ____ in the school.", "Opt_1": "profit", "Opt_2": "controversy", "Opt_3": "finance", "Opt_4": "description", "Answer": "controversy", "Opt_1_def": "money gained", "Opt_2_def": "an issue on which their are strong and conflicting opinions", "Opt_3_def": "to do with money and payment", "Opt_4_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It's usually possible for teachers to ____ quite closely what grades their students are going to get in tests.", "Opt_1": "accelerate", "Opt_2": "owe", "Opt_3": "predict", "Opt_4": "formulate", "Answer": "predict", "Opt_1_def": "to get or make faster", "Opt_2_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)", "Opt_3_def": "to say what will happen in the future", "Opt_4_def": "to express"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "You should be able to ____ the answer if you think carefully enough.", "Opt_1": "acknowledge", "Opt_2": "dominate", "Opt_3": "enhance", "Opt_4": "deduce", "Answer": "deduce", "Opt_1_def": "to agree with; admit to; give credit to", "Opt_2_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part", "Opt_3_def": "to make something better", "Opt_4_def": "to come to a conclusion about someone or something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Sometimes it is necessary to impose a ____ on the number of solutions searched for, since in general the number of such solutions could be infinite.", "Opt_1": "diagnosis", "Opt_2": "shortage", "Opt_3": "assignment", "Opt_4": "limit", "Answer": "limit", "Opt_1_def": "assessment of a situation (particularly of a problem)", "Opt_2_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed", "Opt_3_def": "a task; the giving of a task", "Opt_4_def": "extent, boundary"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It is noted that the university regulations ____ that a course can be offered only if a minimum number of students is enrolled.", "Opt_1": "afford", "Opt_2": "disrupt", "Opt_3": "criticize", "Opt_4": "stipulate", "Answer": "stipulate", "Opt_1_def": "to be able to pay for something", "Opt_2_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage", "Opt_3_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone", "Opt_4_def": "to require"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "If you want to live a long and healthy life, it is essential that you eat well and get ____ of exercise.", "Opt_1": "phenomenon", "Opt_2": "plenty", "Opt_3": "justice", "Opt_4": "rise", "Answer": "plenty", "Opt_1_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)", "Opt_2_def": "many, lots of", "Opt_3_def": "fairness in law", "Opt_4_def": "to go up"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The court decided to ____ the opinion of the mental health specialist.", "Opt_1": "ignore", "Opt_2": "detect", "Opt_3": "disrupt", "Opt_4": "appear", "Answer": "ignore", "Opt_1_def": "to take no notice of; to leave out (of consideration)", "Opt_2_def": "to see, find or notice", "Opt_3_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage", "Opt_4_def": "to come, be seen"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Students are able to use basic communication and mathematics skills for purposes and situations they will ____ throughout their lives.", "Opt_1": "decrease", "Opt_2": "encounter", "Opt_3": "reinforce", "Opt_4": "verify", "Answer": "encounter", "Opt_1_def": "to get smaller, to go down", "Opt_2_def": "to meet or experience", "Opt_3_def": "to make something stronger", "Opt_4_def": "to prove or claim the truth"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "TOEFL is not the most ____ part of the application, but it is an unavoidable part, which sometimes can be quite painful and time- consuming.", "Opt_1": "subjective", "Opt_2": "local", "Opt_3": "crucial", "Opt_4": "fortunate", "Answer": "crucial", "Opt_1_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling", "Opt_2_def": "in the area where you live or work", "Opt_3_def": "extremely important", "Opt_4_def": "lucky"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The data is ____ as some analysts measure this figure according to different moments of the year, geographic regions and other variables.", "Opt_1": "available", "Opt_2": "domestic", "Opt_3": "sane", "Opt_4": "ambiguous", "Answer": "ambiguous", "Opt_1_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_2_def": "home", "Opt_3_def": "reasonable; not mad", "Opt_4_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "He said the debate now should ____ events of the past and the focus should be on what the UN, the US and Iraq could do to achieve the results.", "Opt_1": "commit", "Opt_2": "exclude", "Opt_3": "exchange", "Opt_4": "culminate", "Answer": "exclude", "Opt_1_def": "to do (often an offense)", "Opt_2_def": "to leave out; opposite of include", "Opt_3_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing", "Opt_4_def": "to end"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It was ____ of him to fail to prepare properly for the test.", "Opt_1": "domestic", "Opt_2": "novel", "Opt_3": "fundamental", "Opt_4": "characteristic", "Answer": "characteristic", "Opt_1_def": "home", "Opt_2_def": "new", "Opt_3_def": "very important", "Opt_4_def": "typical"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government ministers ____ to treat people as children to be protected from all the ills of the world.", "Opt_1": "tend", "Opt_2": "predict", "Opt_3": "enforce", "Opt_4": "presume", "Answer": "tend", "Opt_1_def": "to often behave in a certain way", "Opt_2_def": "to say what will happen in the future", "Opt_3_def": "to make something happen (particularly a law or regulation)", "Opt_4_def": "to believe, assume"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The word give is substituted for the word ____ to express more clearly the intent of the section.", "Opt_1": "transfer", "Opt_2": "invent", "Opt_3": "afford", "Opt_4": "deliver", "Answer": "deliver", "Opt_1_def": "to move to a different place or job", "Opt_2_def": "to create (often a new object)", "Opt_3_def": "to be able to pay for something", "Opt_4_def": "to provide (often by bringing to people)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "They ____ their nutrients from the air and not from the plant on which they are growing.", "Opt_1": "depart", "Opt_2": "solve", "Opt_3": "derive", "Opt_4": "comprehend", "Answer": "derive", "Opt_1_def": "to leave; to be different from", "Opt_2_def": "to find an answer", "Opt_3_def": "to come from or get from", "Opt_4_def": "to understand"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The lack of available parking spaces is a significant ____ to faculty and students.", "Opt_1": "consequence", "Opt_2": "term", "Opt_3": "incident", "Opt_4": "detriment", "Answer": "detriment", "Opt_1_def": "result", "Opt_2_def": "a word or expression", "Opt_3_def": "happening; event", "Opt_4_def": "disadvantage"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Job applicants often find that their personal attributes match what a company values; when this occurs, you should ____ these attributes in your CV.", "Opt_1": "refuse", "Opt_2": "highlight", "Opt_3": "solve", "Opt_4": "accuse", "Answer": "highlight", "Opt_1_def": "to not do something that someone wants you to do", "Opt_2_def": "to show (the important features of something)", "Opt_3_def": "to find an answer", "Opt_4_def": "to blame"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The cost of establishing links will ____ as improvements are made to the underlying communication infrastructure.", "Opt_1": "overlap", "Opt_2": "acquire", "Opt_3": "achieve", "Opt_4": "diminish", "Answer": "diminish", "Opt_1_def": "to have in common; to cover part of", "Opt_2_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_3_def": "to gain or get something (often academic success)", "Opt_4_def": "to get smaller or less important"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "If you move to London you will have to learn to ____ noise, crime and high prices.", "Opt_1": "circulate", "Opt_2": "contribute", "Opt_3": "tolerate", "Opt_4": "dictate", "Answer": "tolerate", "Opt_1_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)", "Opt_2_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in", "Opt_3_def": "to allow to happen; to bear", "Opt_4_def": "to tell someone what to do"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "So, what's the ____ of all this hindsight and what do we stand to gain from it?", "Opt_1": "drawback", "Opt_2": "situation", "Opt_3": "authority", "Opt_4": "point", "Answer": "point", "Opt_1_def": "disadvantage, problem", "Opt_2_def": "circumstances", "Opt_3_def": "control (right to control)", "Opt_4_def": "purpose; reason; value"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It is a particular ____ to welcome several San Francisco State University alumni who embody all that we commemorate today.", "Opt_1": "exhibit", "Opt_2": "privilege", "Opt_3": "implication", "Opt_4": "rise", "Answer": "privilege", "Opt_1_def": "to show", "Opt_2_def": "a right (to do something)", "Opt_3_def": "result or consequence", "Opt_4_def": "to go up"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The ____ of the aid money that has been allocated to Afghanistan has been wasted.", "Opt_1": "hypothesis", "Opt_2": "bulk", "Opt_3": "territory", "Opt_4": "quantity", "Answer": "bulk", "Opt_1_def": "idea or prediction", "Opt_2_def": "majority; largest part", "Opt_3_def": "land; area (of interest)", "Opt_4_def": "amount"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Microsoft has promised that the forthcoming operating system will be more ____ than ever before.", "Opt_1": "ultimate", "Opt_2": "apparent", "Opt_3": "secure", "Opt_4": "prime", "Answer": "secure", "Opt_1_def": "final or most important", "Opt_2_def": "clear; obvious", "Opt_3_def": "safe", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "This is a very ____ and inadequate outline of a few of the leading points in a very large investigation with which I am occupied.", "Opt_1": "military", "Opt_2": "brief", "Opt_3": "artificial", "Opt_4": "sole", "Answer": "brief", "Opt_1_def": "to do with army", "Opt_2_def": "short", "Opt_3_def": "not real or natural", "Opt_4_def": "only"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "My overall impression is that this plan describes a very ____ attempt to address an important issue in a scientifically credible manner.", "Opt_1": "genuine", "Opt_2": "ambitious", "Opt_3": "available", "Opt_4": "permanent", "Answer": "ambitious", "Opt_1_def": "real and authentic", "Opt_2_def": "having high goals (especially in a career; challenging", "Opt_3_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_4_def": "lasting for ever or for a very long time"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "We have a rigid ____ of no drugs in our school. You will be expelled if you are caught with them in the building.", "Opt_1": "vary", "Opt_2": "lecture", "Opt_3": "policy", "Opt_4": "process", "Answer": "policy", "Opt_1_def": "to change or be different", "Opt_2_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "formal rules", "Opt_4_def": "a series of steps"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Most of the families at our international school are here for a ____ of 2-3 years The ____ of the Earth's orbit around the sun is 365 days.", "Opt_1": "duration", "Opt_2": "phase", "Opt_3": "impact", "Opt_4": "passage", "Answer": "duration", "Opt_1_def": "period of time", "Opt_2_def": "a (short) period of time; stage", "Opt_3_def": "effect", "Opt_4_def": "a piece of written or spoken text"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "But he did not ____ himself to theoretical matters alone. He now drew attention to the lack of American minority students on campus.", "Opt_1": "advise", "Opt_2": "confine", "Opt_3": "rotate", "Opt_4": "fail", "Answer": "confine", "Opt_1_def": "to say what someone should do; to give advice", "Opt_2_def": "to limit", "Opt_3_def": "to turn or move (around)", "Opt_4_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "There have been several reviews done ____ the comparison of online course delivery tools that are on the market today.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Omitting the transportation costs would ____ the company's financial position.", "Opt_1": "speculate", "Opt_2": "insist", "Opt_3": "enhance", "Opt_4": "distort", "Answer": "distort", "Opt_1_def": "to think and talk about (often future events)", "Opt_2_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim", "Opt_3_def": "to make something better", "Opt_4_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government's proposals will have a ____ effect on the education of every child in the country.", "Opt_1": "profound", "Opt_2": "credible", "Opt_3": "satisfactory", "Opt_4": "ambiguous", "Answer": "profound", "Opt_1_def": "deep; great; serious", "Opt_2_def": "believable", "Opt_3_def": "enough;OK", "Opt_4_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Various approaches to environmental ____ are discussed, along with steps in the planning process when citizen involvement is particularly effective.", "Opt_1": "supply", "Opt_2": "outcome", "Opt_3": "degree", "Opt_4": "justice", "Answer": "justice", "Opt_1_def": "provision, store", "Opt_2_def": "result", "Opt_3_def": "amount", "Opt_4_def": "fairness in law"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The unpleasant incident in the computer lab is sure to ____ my thoughts in the next few days.", "Opt_1": "retreat", "Opt_2": "contact", "Opt_3": "occupy", "Opt_4": "detect", "Answer": "occupy", "Opt_1_def": "to go back", "Opt_2_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)", "Opt_3_def": "to up space or time", "Opt_4_def": "to see, find or notice"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If you decide to apply, you will need to ____ a full application including: cover sheet, goals and plan letter, and project statement.", "Opt_1": "risk", "Opt_2": "compile", "Opt_3": "exploit", "Opt_4": "advance", "Answer": "compile", "Opt_1_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure", "Opt_2_def": "to put together (often in a list", "Opt_3_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)", "Opt_4_def": "to go or move forward; to get better"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "If you are unable to attend a class for any reason, and would prefer to work directly from the student guide, please ____ the Training Coordinator.", "Opt_1": "circulate", "Opt_2": "contact", "Opt_3": "propose", "Opt_4": "earn", "Answer": "contact", "Opt_1_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)", "Opt_2_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)", "Opt_3_def": "to suggest", "Opt_4_def": "to get money or another reward (usually by working for it)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "She finally was able to ____ her true ability with an excellent score in the end of year test.", "Opt_1": "comply", "Opt_2": "contradict", "Opt_3": "reveal", "Opt_4": "protect", "Answer": "reveal", "Opt_1_def": "to do what someone asks or orders", "Opt_2_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong", "Opt_3_def": "to show or uncover", "Opt_4_def": "to keep something out of danger"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Including future irrelevant costs generally will not lead to a poor choice; it will only ____ the analysis.", "Opt_1": "complicate", "Opt_2": "estimate", "Opt_3": "integrate", "Opt_4": "fade", "Answer": "complicate", "Opt_1_def": "to make things more complex or difficult", "Opt_2_def": "to make an intelligent guess", "Opt_3_def": "to fit into a new situation", "Opt_4_def": "to disappear slowly"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government did not proceed with the recommendations ____ the disability program and decided to review changes to the program.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Hopkins argues that the district court committed three ____ errors in determining his sentence.", "Opt_1": "discrete", "Opt_2": "scarce", "Opt_3": "odd", "Opt_4": "logical", "Answer": "discrete", "Opt_1_def": "separate", "Opt_2_def": "rare, not abundant", "Opt_3_def": "strange, unusual", "Opt_4_def": "making sense"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is a ____ that Japanese girls are quiet. You should hear them on the bus on a school trip!", "Opt_1": "stereotype", "Opt_2": "status", "Opt_3": "condition", "Opt_4": "sum", "Answer": "stereotype", "Opt_1_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)", "Opt_2_def": "position, standing", "Opt_3_def": "state", "Opt_4_def": "an amount of money, total"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "During this course you will review your knowledge of German, by focusing on the four language skills, ____ speaking, listening, reading and writing.", "Opt_1": "conversely", "Opt_2": "namely", "Opt_3": "therefore", "Opt_4": "predominantly", "Answer": "namely", "Opt_1_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand", "Opt_2_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_3_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_4_def": "mostly"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Although nuclear power does not pollute the air, many people are ____ it because they fear an accident or terrorist attack on a nuclear power station.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "In most school parents are asked to ____ to their child participating in sex education lessons.", "Opt_1": "neglect", "Opt_2": "utilize", "Opt_3": "consent", "Opt_4": "attach", "Answer": "consent", "Opt_1_def": "to not think about or care for", "Opt_2_def": "to use", "Opt_3_def": "to agree", "Opt_4_def": "to put together with"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "While I don't ____ this as absolutely the ultimate method that everyone should use, it is important that a standardized technique be adopted.", "Opt_1": "spread", "Opt_2": "present", "Opt_3": "claim", "Opt_4": "refute", "Answer": "present", "Opt_1_def": "to move (over a wider area)", "Opt_2_def": "to give or show; to make a presentation", "Opt_3_def": "to state to be true", "Opt_4_def": "to prove to be untrue; to deny"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "This is the single most important ____ a district judge can perform in the administration of his duties.", "Opt_1": "incident", "Opt_2": "deed", "Opt_3": "contrast", "Opt_4": "challenge", "Answer": "deed", "Opt_1_def": "happening; event", "Opt_2_def": "an action", "Opt_3_def": "difference", "Opt_4_def": "difficult situation; problem"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "This ____ is subject to formal revision before publication in the university journal.", "Opt_1": "conflict", "Opt_2": "trend", "Opt_3": "opinion", "Opt_4": "minimum", "Answer": "opinion", "Opt_1_def": "problem, struggle or battle", "Opt_2_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "view; what you think about someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "the smallest amount; the least"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The Commission was unable to estimate the cost of complying with new requirements ____ data recording.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "This is an important finding that has implications for the ____ and treatment of children with PTSD.", "Opt_1": "boundary", "Opt_2": "result", "Opt_3": "diagnosis", "Opt_4": "liberty", "Answer": "diagnosis", "Opt_1_def": "limit, extent", "Opt_2_def": "outcome, effect", "Opt_3_def": "assessment of a situation (particularly of a problem)", "Opt_4_def": "freedom"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The VFWF reserves the right to seek additional funds if the amount of the ____ is insufficient to fully meet the needs.", "Opt_1": "object", "Opt_2": "principle", "Opt_3": "entity", "Opt_4": "grant", "Answer": "grant", "Opt_1_def": "thing", "Opt_2_def": "rule", "Opt_3_def": "thing; body; organization", "Opt_4_def": "a sum of money given to a person or organization"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Contact between infected and uninfected people can ____ disease.", "Opt_1": "transmit", "Opt_2": "conduct", "Opt_3": "inform", "Opt_4": "explore", "Answer": "transmit", "Opt_1_def": "to send or convey", "Opt_2_def": "to do or perform; to behave", "Opt_3_def": "to say, give information", "Opt_4_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "If it doesn't print clearly after several cleanings, you will need to ____ the print cartridge.", "Opt_1": "migrate", "Opt_2": "engage", "Opt_3": "purchase", "Opt_4": "replace", "Answer": "replace", "Opt_1_def": "to go to another place", "Opt_2_def": "to participate in; to focus attention on", "Opt_3_def": "to buy", "Opt_4_def": "to put in or take the place of .."}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government failed to recognize the ____ of the public's unhappiness with the new law.", "Opt_1": "dimension", "Opt_2": "series", "Opt_3": "battle", "Opt_4": "priority", "Answer": "dimension", "Opt_1_def": "importance; amount", "Opt_2_def": "a number of things, one after the other", "Opt_3_def": "fight, part of a war", "Opt_4_def": "first and most important task"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The author had failed to ____ his report, so it was impossible to check the truth of his claims.", "Opt_1": "affect", "Opt_2": "annotate", "Opt_3": "generate", "Opt_4": "depend", "Answer": "annotate", "Opt_1_def": "to have an influence on", "Opt_2_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing", "Opt_3_def": "to make or produce", "Opt_4_def": "be influenced (by)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Over the course of her ____ in the program she has come a great distance from her primary focus as an agent for FEMA.", "Opt_1": "journey", "Opt_2": "transition", "Opt_3": "scale", "Opt_4": "object", "Answer": "journey", "Opt_1_def": "a long trip to a different place", "Opt_2_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_3_def": "extent", "Opt_4_def": "thing"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "If your parents want too take you out of school during ____ time, they must have a legitimate reason.", "Opt_1": "rank", "Opt_2": "effect", "Opt_3": "term", "Opt_4": "attack", "Answer": "term", "Opt_1_def": "position (in a list or hierarchy)", "Opt_2_def": "result", "Opt_3_def": "a word or expression", "Opt_4_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Volleyball players must ____ in order, and every player must do this (i.e. a team may NOT have a designated setter/hitter/etc. who does not ____ out).", "Opt_1": "rotate", "Opt_2": "suffer", "Opt_3": "refute", "Opt_4": "increase", "Answer": "rotate", "Opt_1_def": "to turn or move (around)", "Opt_2_def": "to experience something bad or painful", "Opt_3_def": "to prove to be untrue; to deny", "Opt_4_def": "to get bigger"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The factory worker was awarded \ufffd\ufffd30,000 ____ for losing his arm in an accident.", "Opt_1": "compensation", "Opt_2": "evidence", "Opt_3": "gap", "Opt_4": "truth", "Answer": "compensation", "Opt_1_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_2_def": "proof, signs", "Opt_3_def": "space, opening or time between", "Opt_4_def": "actual reason or fact"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Most older cultures seem to accept volcanoes as a natural part of life and ____ their habits accordingly.", "Opt_1": "adjust", "Opt_2": "contain", "Opt_3": "attempt", "Opt_4": "identify", "Answer": "adjust", "Opt_1_def": "to change (often in order to make something work properly)", "Opt_2_def": "to have in it; to hold inside", "Opt_3_def": "to try", "Opt_4_def": "to know or say who or what something is"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "A nursing or household robot must be ____ in order to reach a variety of working sites within the house.", "Opt_1": "key", "Opt_2": "logical", "Opt_3": "mobile", "Opt_4": "faint", "Answer": "mobile", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "making sense", "Opt_3_def": "moving; able to move", "Opt_4_def": "not strong"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "You have learned this lesson that water and other liquids ____ sound better than air.", "Opt_1": "acquire", "Opt_2": "transmit", "Opt_3": "invest", "Opt_4": "derive", "Answer": "transmit", "Opt_1_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_2_def": "to send or convey", "Opt_3_def": "to put money into something", "Opt_4_def": "to come from or get from"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Politicians ____ that they can't know everything, so they surround themselves with people who can advise them.", "Opt_1": "realize", "Opt_2": "ban", "Opt_3": "sustain", "Opt_4": "perceive", "Answer": "realize", "Opt_1_def": "to come to know or understand", "Opt_2_def": "to prohibit or forbid", "Opt_3_def": "to keep going; to maintain", "Opt_4_def": "to see; to become aware of with one of the senses; to think"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "I think the students enjoy the fact that they have the ____ to try different things, says Harris. You can ask them to expand and see which direction they take.", "Opt_1": "liberty", "Opt_2": "attack", "Opt_3": "fault", "Opt_4": "demand", "Answer": "liberty", "Opt_1_def": "freedom", "Opt_2_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage", "Opt_3_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem", "Opt_4_def": "a need or desire for"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Most people employ an ____ when they want to buy or sell a house.", "Opt_1": "access", "Opt_2": "agent", "Opt_3": "belief", "Opt_4": "expense", "Answer": "agent", "Opt_1_def": "the right to enter or use", "Opt_2_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone", "Opt_3_def": "what you think; what you believe in", "Opt_4_def": "cost"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "My overall impression is that this plan describes a very ambitious attempt to ____ an important issue in a scientifically credible manner.", "Opt_1": "comprehend", "Opt_2": "precede", "Opt_3": "extend", "Opt_4": "address", "Answer": "address", "Opt_1_def": "to understand", "Opt_2_def": "to go or be before someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to make longer in time or space", "Opt_4_def": "to give attention to (an issue)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Each College or School should ____ the teaching of basic technology skills at the earliest level possible.", "Opt_1": "commit", "Opt_2": "improve", "Opt_3": "integrate", "Opt_4": "recur", "Answer": "integrate", "Opt_1_def": "to do (often an offense)", "Opt_2_def": "to get better", "Opt_3_def": "to fit into a new situation", "Opt_4_def": "to happen again"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "All this progress was a ____ of the advance of technology and also of advances in government and other social organizations in capitalist society.", "Opt_1": "opportunity", "Opt_2": "gap", "Opt_3": "consequence", "Opt_4": "background", "Answer": "consequence", "Opt_1_def": "chance", "Opt_2_def": "space, opening or time between", "Opt_3_def": "result", "Opt_4_def": "family experiences; circumstances"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Although two weeks are dedicated to its development at the end of the semester you should not ____ that this is enough time for the entire project.", "Opt_1": "conclude", "Opt_2": "respect", "Opt_3": "tend", "Opt_4": "view", "Answer": "conclude", "Opt_1_def": "to finish; to make a judgment", "Opt_2_def": "to think positively about someone; to tolerate or avoid interfering with something", "Opt_3_def": "to often behave in a certain way", "Opt_4_def": "to have an opinion"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The ____ is to find the right mixture of materials that will result in the creation of clear electrical signals.", "Opt_1": "industry", "Opt_2": "objective", "Opt_3": "finance", "Opt_4": "shift", "Answer": "objective", "Opt_1_def": "area of business ( often manufacturing )", "Opt_2_def": "aim or goal", "Opt_3_def": "to do with money and payment", "Opt_4_def": "change"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "A small proportion of the government were ____ the Prime Minister's plan, but they were outvoted.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "People with mental disabilities are so marginalized that even human rights activists have failed to ____ for them.", "Opt_1": "require", "Opt_2": "claim", "Opt_3": "reserve", "Opt_4": "advocate", "Answer": "advocate", "Opt_1_def": "to need", "Opt_2_def": "to state to be true", "Opt_3_def": "to keep", "Opt_4_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "There is a sharp contrast between Japan's fairly rigid ____ of national and private universities with the United States, which has a wider variety of institutions.", "Opt_1": "hierarchy", "Opt_2": "coincidence", "Opt_3": "debate", "Opt_4": "environment", "Answer": "hierarchy", "Opt_1_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)", "Opt_2_def": "an uncommon happening of two things", "Opt_3_def": "formal discussion", "Opt_4_def": "the world around us"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "She is unlikely to rise above the ____ of teacher helper; she is not very hard-working, and too often absent.", "Opt_1": "rank", "Opt_2": "speed", "Opt_3": "lecture", "Opt_4": "contrary", "Answer": "rank", "Opt_1_def": "position (in a list or hierarchy)", "Opt_2_def": "how quickly something moves or changes", "Opt_3_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "opposite"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The priests of this institution did not give their answers by inspiration, but occupied themselves chiefly with the ____ of dreams", "Opt_1": "interpretation", "Opt_2": "consequence", "Opt_3": "background", "Opt_4": "committee", "Answer": "interpretation", "Opt_1_def": "explanation; assessment", "Opt_2_def": "result", "Opt_3_def": "family experiences; circumstances", "Opt_4_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Do not write on the board with ____ ink. It cannot be erased.", "Opt_1": "apparent", "Opt_2": "original", "Opt_3": "permanent", "Opt_4": "discrete", "Answer": "permanent", "Opt_1_def": "clear; obvious", "Opt_2_def": "the first of its kind", "Opt_3_def": "lasting for ever or for a very long time", "Opt_4_def": "separate"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Rarely do any of the numbers in any of the four columns ____ by more than five.", "Opt_1": "destroy", "Opt_2": "attract", "Opt_3": "deviate", "Opt_4": "measure", "Answer": "deviate", "Opt_1_def": "to break or damage completely", "Opt_2_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like", "Opt_3_def": "to be different", "Opt_4_def": "to find out how much there is of something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The ____ cannot guarantee the accuracy of the information or the appropriateness of any material that a student finds.", "Opt_1": "tradition", "Opt_2": "concept", "Opt_3": "privilege", "Opt_4": "district", "Answer": "district", "Opt_1_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things", "Opt_2_def": "idea; understanding", "Opt_3_def": "a right (to do something)", "Opt_4_def": "region of a city"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "She had a flash of ____ that she was going to fail her exams unless she started working.", "Opt_1": "entity", "Opt_2": "obstacle", "Opt_3": "reply", "Opt_4": "insight", "Answer": "insight", "Opt_1_def": "thing; body; organization", "Opt_2_def": "barrier; problem", "Opt_3_def": "an answer", "Opt_4_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Library and information science students must be taught how to ____ the resources that will allow them to anticipate the future and avoid becoming irrelevant as information professionals.", "Opt_1": "impress", "Opt_2": "exceed", "Opt_3": "accelerate", "Opt_4": "exploit", "Answer": "exploit", "Opt_1_def": "to create a favourable reaction", "Opt_2_def": "to be more than or better than", "Opt_3_def": "to get or make faster", "Opt_4_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The VFWF reserves the right to seek additional funds if the amount of the ____ is insufficient to fully meet the needs.", "Opt_1": "account", "Opt_2": "grant", "Opt_3": "hypothesis", "Opt_4": "topic", "Answer": "grant", "Opt_1_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening", "Opt_2_def": "a sum of money given to a person or organization", "Opt_3_def": "idea or prediction", "Opt_4_def": "area of interest or discussion"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "So far scientists have been unable to ____ in their efforts to find a cure for cancer.", "Opt_1": "illuminate", "Opt_2": "announce", "Opt_3": "succeed", "Opt_4": "interrupt", "Answer": "succeed", "Opt_1_def": "to show clearly; to light up", "Opt_2_def": "to state (often in an official way)", "Opt_3_def": "to do well", "Opt_4_def": "to stop something from happening"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The paper was unable to attract sufficient ____ and ceased publication after a few months.", "Opt_1": "support", "Opt_2": "detriment", "Opt_3": "choice", "Opt_4": "strategy", "Answer": "support", "Opt_1_def": "help", "Opt_2_def": "disadvantage", "Opt_3_def": "decision, selection", "Opt_4_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Most scientists are more interested in the ____ of winning the Nobel Prize than the money they get for doing so.", "Opt_1": "criterion", "Opt_2": "prestige", "Opt_3": "code", "Opt_4": "boundary", "Answer": "prestige", "Opt_1_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something", "Opt_2_def": "fame and respect", "Opt_3_def": "a set of rules", "Opt_4_def": "limit, extent"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The school is planning to bring in an external tax expert to analyze its ____ methods.", "Opt_1": "source", "Opt_2": "finance", "Opt_3": "strategy", "Opt_4": "surface", "Answer": "finance", "Opt_1_def": "where something begins, where you can find something", "Opt_2_def": "to do with money and payment", "Opt_3_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal", "Opt_4_def": "the outside layer of an object"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "These notes are intended as a ____ introduction to some of the main ideas and methods of calculus.", "Opt_1": "economic", "Opt_2": "brief", "Opt_3": "external", "Opt_4": "explicit", "Answer": "brief", "Opt_1_def": "financial; to do with money", "Opt_2_def": "short", "Opt_3_def": "outside", "Opt_4_def": "clearly and openly expressed"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "One factor was political: because we had decided to ____ the project at first to the six northernmost counties in our region.", "Opt_1": "confine", "Opt_2": "encounter", "Opt_3": "facilitate", "Opt_4": "express", "Answer": "confine", "Opt_1_def": "to limit", "Opt_2_def": "to meet or experience", "Opt_3_def": "to make something easier", "Opt_4_def": "to say or mean"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Part of the job of an ESL teacher in an international school is to ____ the need to make work comprehensible to non-native speakers.", "Opt_1": "advocate", "Opt_2": "deduce", "Opt_3": "strive", "Opt_4": "absorb", "Answer": "advocate", "Opt_1_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to come to a conclusion about someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to work or try hard", "Opt_4_def": "to take in; to take up"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The last ____ of the twentieth century started in 1990 and ended on 31 December 1999.", "Opt_1": "source", "Opt_2": "decade", "Opt_3": "ignorance", "Opt_4": "motive", "Answer": "decade", "Opt_1_def": "where something begins, where you can find something", "Opt_2_def": "a period of ten years", "Opt_3_def": "lack of knowledge", "Opt_4_def": "reason"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "You will ____ a lengthy, very technical email, which in short, states that your unsubscribe request did not succeed.", "Opt_1": "strain", "Opt_2": "confine", "Opt_3": "approve", "Opt_4": "receive", "Answer": "receive", "Opt_1_def": "to put under stress or make difficult", "Opt_2_def": "to limit", "Opt_3_def": "to agree to", "Opt_4_def": "to get"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "We should avoid the error of assuming that we will ever be able to ____ the causes of his behaviour.", "Opt_1": "offend", "Opt_2": "conserve", "Opt_3": "conduct", "Opt_4": "comprehend", "Answer": "comprehend", "Opt_1_def": "to go against; to upset", "Opt_2_def": "to preserve; to not use", "Opt_3_def": "to do or perform; to behave", "Opt_4_def": "to understand"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The study finds they are more likely than their non-Latino white neighbors to ____ another stroke in the first two years after living through one.", "Opt_1": "introduce", "Opt_2": "commit", "Opt_3": "suffer", "Opt_4": "announce", "Answer": "suffer", "Opt_1_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time", "Opt_2_def": "to do (often an offense)", "Opt_3_def": "to experience something bad or painful", "Opt_4_def": "to state (often in an official way)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "This form is to be used by students who seek to ____ or drop a course during the first two weeks of the trimester.", "Opt_1": "add", "Opt_2": "derive", "Opt_3": "arrange", "Opt_4": "presume", "Answer": "add", "Opt_1_def": "to include; to give or say extra", "Opt_2_def": "to come from or get from", "Opt_3_def": "to plan to happen; to group together", "Opt_4_def": "to believe, assume"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "However, the Indian ____ is passing through a difficult phase in its history.", "Opt_1": "bias", "Opt_2": "assignment", "Opt_3": "society", "Opt_4": "comparison", "Answer": "society", "Opt_1_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice", "Opt_2_def": "a task; the giving of a task", "Opt_3_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country", "Opt_4_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The course is aimed to develop appropriate skills and will ____ attempt to identify contexts where a traditional lecture might be required.", "Opt_1": "rather", "Opt_2": "respectively", "Opt_3": "thereby", "Opt_4": "therefore", "Answer": "therefore", "Opt_1_def": "instead", "Opt_2_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other", "Opt_3_def": "by doing this", "Opt_4_def": "so, as a result"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Job applicants often find that their personal attributes match what a company values; when this occurs, you should ____ these attributes in your CV.", "Opt_1": "highlight", "Opt_2": "monitor", "Opt_3": "intervene", "Opt_4": "retreat", "Answer": "highlight", "Opt_1_def": "to show (the important features of something)", "Opt_2_def": "to watch ( someone's or something's behaviour )", "Opt_3_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)", "Opt_4_def": "to go back"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The school plans to ____ the sports field so that games can be played after dark.", "Opt_1": "owe", "Opt_2": "illuminate", "Opt_3": "appreciate", "Opt_4": "associate", "Answer": "illuminate", "Opt_1_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)", "Opt_2_def": "to show clearly; to light up", "Opt_3_def": "to understand (the value of someone or something)", "Opt_4_def": "to link to; to make a connection to"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Knowing when to seek treatment for ____ health disorders is important for parents and families.", "Opt_1": "superior", "Opt_2": "automatic", "Opt_3": "mental", "Opt_4": "elaborate", "Answer": "mental", "Opt_1_def": "better", "Opt_2_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually", "Opt_3_def": "of the brain or mind", "Opt_4_def": "detailed; complex"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "This interesting site offers the student of neuroscience access to an ____ amount of information on the discipline.", "Opt_1": "immense", "Opt_2": "reliable", "Opt_3": "pure", "Opt_4": "ambiguous", "Answer": "immense", "Opt_1_def": "very large", "Opt_2_def": "can be trusted, does not let you down \r\n", "Opt_3_def": "complete, 100%", "Opt_4_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "She has ____ problems with her spelling, but the content of her writing is actually very good.", "Opt_1": "suitable", "Opt_2": "harsh", "Opt_3": "severe", "Opt_4": "adjacent", "Answer": "severe", "Opt_1_def": "good for a particular job or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "hard, unfair", "Opt_3_def": "serious, harsh", "Opt_4_def": "next to"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It is the president who will need to encourage the strategic thinking and action ____ to attract and retain employees of quality.", "Opt_1": "imaginary", "Opt_2": "immediate", "Opt_3": "wise", "Opt_4": "necessary", "Answer": "necessary", "Opt_1_def": "not real; from the imagination", "Opt_2_def": "first (without delay)", "Opt_3_def": "intelligent; sensible", "Opt_4_def": "needed; very important"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Some students ____ that they can simultaneously watch TV and do their homework.", "Opt_1": "claim", "Opt_2": "adhere", "Opt_3": "insert", "Opt_4": "multiply", "Answer": "claim", "Opt_1_def": "to state to be true", "Opt_2_def": "to keep to; to follow", "Opt_3_def": "to put in", "Opt_4_def": "to increase greatly"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Some scientists claim that we cannot infer ____ warming on the basis of a just few years of hot weather.", "Opt_1": "global", "Opt_2": "utter", "Opt_3": "fortunate", "Opt_4": "supplementary", "Answer": "global", "Opt_1_def": "world", "Opt_2_def": "complete, total", "Opt_3_def": "lucky", "Opt_4_def": "extra; additional"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Dairy farmers have led the latest in a long ____ of protests by agricultural associations, despite the record high prices for farm products.", "Opt_1": "staff", "Opt_2": "interpretation", "Opt_3": "license", "Opt_4": "series", "Answer": "series", "Opt_1_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)", "Opt_2_def": "explanation; assessment", "Opt_3_def": "permission to do something (often an official document)", "Opt_4_def": "a number of things, one after the other"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "His lungs were filled in an ____ with a great volume of driven air which he could not expel.", "Opt_1": "instant", "Opt_2": "obsolete", "Opt_3": "passive", "Opt_4": "official", "Answer": "instant", "Opt_1_def": "immediate", "Opt_2_def": "not used or needed any more; out of date", "Opt_3_def": "not active; unresponsive", "Opt_4_def": "approved by an authority"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If you ____ against the school's computer use policy, you will not be permitted to use the computer labs.", "Opt_1": "ensure", "Opt_2": "impose", "Opt_3": "settle", "Opt_4": "offend", "Answer": "offend", "Opt_1_def": "to make sure (of)", "Opt_2_def": "to force; to require to happen", "Opt_3_def": "to solve a problem or dispute", "Opt_4_def": "to go against; to upset"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "There is land ____ the ice in Antarctica, but water ____ it at the North Pole.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "beneath", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "below", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "During its congress, Committee failed to ____ even one woman to a leading position.", "Opt_1": "introduce", "Opt_2": "consult", "Opt_3": "provide", "Opt_4": "elect", "Answer": "elect", "Opt_1_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time", "Opt_2_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)", "Opt_3_def": "to give", "Opt_4_def": "to choose by voting"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The ____ service in Germany is much better than that in England.", "Opt_1": "train", "Opt_2": "fear", "Opt_3": "suffer", "Opt_4": "represent", "Answer": "train", "Opt_1_def": "to teach someone how to do a job", "Opt_2_def": "to be concerned or frightened about", "Opt_3_def": "to experience something bad or painful", "Opt_4_def": "to be; to show or indicate"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The course is aimed to develop appropriate skills and will therefore ____ to identify contexts where a traditional lecture might be required.", "Opt_1": "realize", "Opt_2": "precede", "Opt_3": "confirm", "Opt_4": "attempt", "Answer": "attempt", "Opt_1_def": "to come to know or understand", "Opt_2_def": "to go or be before someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to agree that something is correct", "Opt_4_def": "to try"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The global ____ agreements have failed to include meaningful, enforceable labour or environmental standards.", "Opt_1": "trade", "Opt_2": "connect", "Opt_3": "omit", "Opt_4": "judge", "Answer": "trade", "Opt_1_def": "to exchange products or services", "Opt_2_def": "to bring or put together", "Opt_3_def": "to leave something out or not do something", "Opt_4_def": "to give an opinion about someone or something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The income of a soccer player in one week is many times higher than what most people ____ in a whole year.", "Opt_1": "separate", "Opt_2": "advise", "Opt_3": "reward", "Opt_4": "earn", "Answer": "earn", "Opt_1_def": "to pull or put apart", "Opt_2_def": "to say what someone should do; to give advice", "Opt_3_def": "to give something (e.g. a prize) for good work or behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "to get money or another reward (usually by working for it)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government is planning to ____ all new mothers with a book advising them how to take care of their baby.", "Opt_1": "cooperate", "Opt_2": "convince", "Opt_3": "provide", "Opt_4": "owe", "Answer": "provide", "Opt_1_def": "to work (well) with another person", "Opt_2_def": "to (try and) get someone to believe something", "Opt_3_def": "to give", "Opt_4_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Collecting information with no particular plan or purpose and then hoping to ____ it into a research project is not likely to succeed.", "Opt_1": "transform", "Opt_2": "control", "Opt_3": "neglect", "Opt_4": "align", "Answer": "transform", "Opt_1_def": "to change (often completely)", "Opt_2_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone", "Opt_3_def": "to not think about or care for", "Opt_4_def": "to bring into line with; to make similar"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "At no point in our deliberations are numbers employed in a way that would trigger an ____ decision to offer or deny admission.", "Opt_1": "official", "Opt_2": "automatic", "Opt_3": "considerable", "Opt_4": "apart", "Answer": "automatic", "Opt_1_def": "approved by an authority", "Opt_2_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually", "Opt_3_def": "very big; very much", "Opt_4_def": "not together, separate"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It operated below 60%, was generally poorly designed and therefore not ____ considering.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Is this a ____ picture by Picasso or is it a fake?", "Opt_1": "precise", "Opt_2": "subsequent", "Opt_3": "passive", "Opt_4": "genuine", "Answer": "genuine", "Opt_1_def": "exact", "Opt_2_def": "next, following", "Opt_3_def": "not active; unresponsive", "Opt_4_def": "real and authentic"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government needs to decide on a ____ response to the continuing violent demonstrations.", "Opt_1": "sole", "Opt_2": "particular", "Opt_3": "optional", "Opt_4": "sane", "Answer": "sane", "Opt_1_def": "only", "Opt_2_def": "specific", "Opt_3_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want", "Opt_4_def": "reasonable; not mad"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The prime minister is today expected to ____ the date of the next election.", "Opt_1": "announce", "Opt_2": "integrate", "Opt_3": "prosper", "Opt_4": "devote", "Answer": "announce", "Opt_1_def": "to state (often in an official way)", "Opt_2_def": "to fit into a new situation", "Opt_3_def": "to do well; to become rich", "Opt_4_def": "to give (time) to"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The time has come, however, to quit spending time and money supporting ____ technologies and to concentrate on delivering better service.", "Opt_1": "obsolete", "Opt_2": "adjacent", "Opt_3": "eligible", "Opt_4": "perpetual", "Answer": "obsolete", "Opt_1_def": "not used or needed any more; out of date", "Opt_2_def": "next to", "Opt_3_def": "being entitled or qualified to do something", "Opt_4_def": "continuing for ever; never disappearing"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "When traveling off-road, the car sensors must be able to detect negative obstacles such as holes and ditches as well as ____ ones such as trees or other cars.", "Opt_1": "practical", "Opt_2": "chief", "Opt_3": "positive", "Opt_4": "enormous", "Answer": "positive", "Opt_1_def": "useful; possible", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_4_def": "very big"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "You will ____ the course unless you start working harder.", "Opt_1": "fail", "Opt_2": "prevent", "Opt_3": "occur", "Opt_4": "abandon", "Answer": "fail", "Opt_1_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly", "Opt_2_def": "to stop from doing or happening", "Opt_3_def": "to happen; take place", "Opt_4_def": "to leave or give up"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It is often necessary to revise a mathematical model several times in the course of an ____ operations research study.", "Opt_1": "necessary", "Opt_2": "certain", "Opt_3": "identical", "Opt_4": "urban", "Answer": "urban", "Opt_1_def": "needed; very important", "Opt_2_def": "sure", "Opt_3_def": "exactly the same", "Opt_4_def": "of the town or city"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "He was not willing to retreat from previous ____ commitments.", "Opt_1": "frequent", "Opt_2": "legitimate", "Opt_3": "loose", "Opt_4": "legal", "Answer": "legal", "Opt_1_def": "often", "Opt_2_def": "correct; allowed", "Opt_3_def": "not firm or finished", "Opt_4_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Children in Experiment 2 did not ____ any evidence of recognizing the familiarized words in the passages.", "Opt_1": "exhibit", "Opt_2": "sector", "Opt_3": "justice", "Opt_4": "experiment", "Answer": "exhibit", "Opt_1_def": "to show", "Opt_2_def": "part; area", "Opt_3_def": "fairness in law", "Opt_4_def": "test"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "He mentioned what seemed like a huge sum. It was indeed a huge amount for a ____ that had only a skeleton staff and strained budget.", "Opt_1": "skill", "Opt_2": "programme", "Opt_3": "industry", "Opt_4": "privilege", "Answer": "programme", "Opt_1_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)", "Opt_2_def": "a course of lessons; a project", "Opt_3_def": "area of business ( often manufacturing )", "Opt_4_def": "a right (to do something)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Throughout the day, with a brief interval for lunch, he stared at the history project which was ____ the next morning.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "beneath", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "below", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The company's efforts to increase business over the past year failed to ____ the shareholders.", "Opt_1": "import", "Opt_2": "impress", "Opt_3": "presume", "Opt_4": "add", "Answer": "impress", "Opt_1_def": "to bring in (to a country)", "Opt_2_def": "to create a favourable reaction", "Opt_3_def": "to believe, assume", "Opt_4_def": "to include; to give or say extra"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "We were not able to demonstrate statistically ____ differences in performance or quality.", "Opt_1": "ultimate", "Opt_2": "independent", "Opt_3": "automatic", "Opt_4": "significant", "Answer": "significant", "Opt_1_def": "final or most important", "Opt_2_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else", "Opt_3_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually", "Opt_4_def": "important, large"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "We ____ outside counsel to work on particular matters when considerations such as cost and highly specialized subject matter make it appropriate to do so.", "Opt_1": "produce", "Opt_2": "join", "Opt_3": "attempt", "Opt_4": "engage", "Answer": "engage", "Opt_1_def": "to make or create", "Opt_2_def": "to become a member (of an organization; to get together with others", "Opt_3_def": "to try", "Opt_4_def": "to participate in; to focus attention on"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The private ____ offers many opportunities for students with a history or liberal arts background.", "Opt_1": "bias", "Opt_2": "contrast", "Opt_3": "sector", "Opt_4": "level", "Answer": "sector", "Opt_1_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice", "Opt_2_def": "difference", "Opt_3_def": "part; area", "Opt_4_def": "standard; layer; amount"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Children who are moved more frequently are more likely to have ____ problems than children in more stable placements.", "Opt_1": "ambiguous", "Opt_2": "cautious", "Opt_3": "subsequent", "Opt_4": "dense", "Answer": "subsequent", "Opt_1_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation", "Opt_2_def": "careful", "Opt_3_def": "next, following", "Opt_4_def": "thick; full; detailed"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Normally, disciplinary action begins with a ____ warning for the first offense.", "Opt_1": "verbal", "Opt_2": "ordinary", "Opt_3": "cautious", "Opt_4": "obsolete", "Answer": "verbal", "Opt_1_def": "to do with words and language (especially the spoken language)", "Opt_2_def": "usual, typical, every day", "Opt_3_def": "careful", "Opt_4_def": "not used or needed any more; out of date"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Beethoven was not an ideal parent and enormous ____ developed between the two, contributing to his son's attempted suicide in 1826.", "Opt_1": "friction", "Opt_2": "asset", "Opt_3": "environment", "Opt_4": "field", "Answer": "friction", "Opt_1_def": "problems or arguments between two people or groups", "Opt_2_def": "advantage", "Opt_3_def": "the world around us", "Opt_4_def": "area of interest or study"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Sufficient progress has been made with regard to drinking water to place within reach the target of halving the proportion of the population without ____ to safe drinking water between 1990 and 2015.", "Opt_1": "programme", "Opt_2": "record", "Opt_3": "objection", "Opt_4": "access", "Answer": "access", "Opt_1_def": "a course of lessons; a project", "Opt_2_def": "evidence; documentation", "Opt_3_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval", "Opt_4_def": "the right to enter or use"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The main ____ of these wars is the social unrest, and the increasing economic and social divergence between the groups of the community.", "Opt_1": "cause", "Opt_2": "consequence", "Opt_3": "instinct", "Opt_4": "materials", "Answer": "consequence", "Opt_1_def": "the reason why something happens", "Opt_2_def": "result", "Opt_3_def": "natural feeling or reaction", "Opt_4_def": "the things you need to do something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Even more extraordinary, every child ____ one was more than willing to state his or her name to the stranger.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Once Grace Albee arrived in New York City in 1933, she was able to ____ herself to full-time printmaking and her art began to command serious national attention.", "Opt_1": "recognize", "Opt_2": "derive", "Opt_3": "dedicate", "Opt_4": "block", "Answer": "dedicate", "Opt_1_def": "to know or understand (who someone is or what something is)", "Opt_2_def": "to come from or get from", "Opt_3_def": "to devote (time and attention)", "Opt_4_def": "to not allow; to stop or prevent"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The study did not discover any significant relationship between the type of music and the ____ of stress.", "Opt_1": "compensation", "Opt_2": "disaster", "Opt_3": "penalty", "Opt_4": "amount", "Answer": "amount", "Opt_1_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_2_def": "a huge problem or failure", "Opt_3_def": "negative consequence; punishment", "Opt_4_def": "how much there is of something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Doctors recognize the difficulty of giving up smoking. That's why they ____ never starting.", "Opt_1": "accumulate", "Opt_2": "recommend", "Opt_3": "achieve", "Opt_4": "restrict", "Answer": "recommend", "Opt_1_def": "to grow; to gather together", "Opt_2_def": "to suggest something to someone because it is good", "Opt_3_def": "to gain or get something (often academic success)", "Opt_4_def": "to limit"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The continued presence of a huge military force in the Gulf area provides the necessary ____ of pressure to ensure implementation of obligations.", "Opt_1": "doubt", "Opt_2": "command", "Opt_3": "element", "Opt_4": "opportunity", "Answer": "element", "Opt_1_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)", "Opt_2_def": "control", "Opt_3_def": "aspect, part", "Opt_4_def": "chance"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "A geography graduate produces a piece of geographic research and analyzes, synthesizes, and evaluates the ____ information.", "Opt_1": "suitable", "Opt_2": "sane", "Opt_3": "relevant", "Opt_4": "minor", "Answer": "relevant", "Opt_1_def": "good for a particular job or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "reasonable; not mad", "Opt_3_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration", "Opt_4_def": "small, not important"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government cannot afford to be ____ about the numbers of young people who fail to find any kind of employment.", "Opt_1": "passive", "Opt_2": "loose", "Opt_3": "broad", "Opt_4": "immense", "Answer": "passive", "Opt_1_def": "not active; unresponsive", "Opt_2_def": "not firm or finished", "Opt_3_def": "wide, extensive", "Opt_4_def": "very large"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If the adult victim acknowledges having experienced abuse, it is important to assess the ____ for future violence, as well as the danger involved.", "Opt_1": "extract", "Opt_2": "potential", "Opt_3": "layer", "Opt_4": "dispute", "Answer": "potential", "Opt_1_def": "to remove; to take out and use", "Opt_2_def": "good possibility", "Opt_3_def": "level", "Opt_4_def": "argument; conflict"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "He did not manage to develop a particularly good ____ in his own life until he was able to stop worrying about what others thought of him.", "Opt_1": "trait", "Opt_2": "penalty", "Opt_3": "balance", "Opt_4": "fault", "Answer": "balance", "Opt_1_def": "characteristic; aspect", "Opt_2_def": "negative consequence; punishment", "Opt_3_def": "equalness", "Opt_4_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Most people have a ____ notion of their financial goals even if they have never written them down.", "Opt_1": "actual", "Opt_2": "vague", "Opt_3": "economic", "Opt_4": "profound", "Answer": "vague", "Opt_1_def": "real", "Opt_2_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_3_def": "financial; to do with money", "Opt_4_def": "deep; great; serious"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Give me a ____ explanation of how the accident happened.", "Opt_1": "cautious", "Opt_2": "enormous", "Opt_3": "brief", "Opt_4": "particular", "Answer": "brief", "Opt_1_def": "careful", "Opt_2_def": "very big", "Opt_3_def": "short", "Opt_4_def": "specific"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "You are recommended to ____ quickly throughout the classroom to make sure that everyone understands the task, then return to help students who are having difficulty.", "Opt_1": "circulate", "Opt_2": "append", "Opt_3": "deduce", "Opt_4": "focus", "Answer": "circulate", "Opt_1_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)", "Opt_2_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)", "Opt_3_def": "to come to a conclusion about someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to direct attention (on an issue)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "You are making very ____ progress in learning English! You only started learning a year ago, and you can already speak quite fluently.", "Opt_1": "rapid", "Opt_2": "actual", "Opt_3": "credible", "Opt_4": "moderate", "Answer": "rapid", "Opt_1_def": "quick", "Opt_2_def": "real", "Opt_3_def": "believable", "Opt_4_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "All political parties must ____ in their proposals to stamp out racism.", "Opt_1": "ensure", "Opt_2": "unite", "Opt_3": "adopt", "Opt_4": "migrate", "Answer": "unite", "Opt_1_def": "to make sure (of)", "Opt_2_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_3_def": "to take in; to start", "Opt_4_def": "to go to another place"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "\"Helpless in the face of terrorism\" - that's not a ____ that University of Cincinnati geography", "Opt_1": "duty", "Opt_2": "sum", "Opt_3": "phrase", "Opt_4": "reluctance", "Answer": "phrase", "Opt_1_def": "responsibility, or job that you are required to do", "Opt_2_def": "an amount of money, total", "Opt_3_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure.", "Opt_4_def": "unwillingness; hesitation"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If your parents want too take you out of school during term time, they must have a ____ reason.", "Opt_1": "positive", "Opt_2": "perpetual", "Opt_3": "numerous", "Opt_4": "legitimate", "Answer": "legitimate", "Opt_1_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_2_def": "continuing for ever; never disappearing", "Opt_3_def": "very many", "Opt_4_def": "correct; allowed"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The technology to ____ carbon monoxide into liquid fuel has been around a long time.", "Opt_1": "constitute", "Opt_2": "abuse", "Opt_3": "convert", "Opt_4": "diminish", "Answer": "convert", "Opt_1_def": "to be; to make up", "Opt_2_def": "to treat someone or something badly", "Opt_3_def": "to change from one thing to another", "Opt_4_def": "to get smaller or less important"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Please note that section 5 is the most important, and ____ it should constitute the majority of your journal entry.", "Opt_1": "indirectly", "Opt_2": "perhaps", "Opt_3": "hence", "Opt_4": "predominantly", "Answer": "hence", "Opt_1_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate", "Opt_2_def": "maybe, possibly", "Opt_3_def": "so, therefore", "Opt_4_def": "mostly"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The media and the public should not ____ the music industry for the jobs that parents are not fulfilling.", "Opt_1": "label", "Opt_2": "migrate", "Opt_3": "blame", "Opt_4": "respect", "Answer": "blame", "Opt_1_def": "to give a name to someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to go to another place", "Opt_3_def": "to accuse", "Opt_4_def": "to think positively about someone; to tolerate or avoid interfering with something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Global warming and polar melting threaten to raise water levels and ____ flood low-lying cities.", "Opt_1": "thus", "Opt_2": "therefore", "Opt_3": "overly", "Opt_4": "occasionally", "Answer": "thus", "Opt_1_def": "so", "Opt_2_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_3_def": "too", "Opt_4_def": "sometimes"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Attendance will not constitute a specific percentage of your ____ grade, but if you miss more than two classes you will definitely fail this course.", "Opt_1": "final", "Opt_2": "physical", "Opt_3": "apparent", "Opt_4": "aware", "Answer": "final", "Opt_1_def": "last", "Opt_2_def": "of the body", "Opt_3_def": "clear; obvious", "Opt_4_def": "knowing"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "There was a ____ in language teaching about 40 years ago when the spoken language replaced writing and grammar as the main focus of teaching.", "Opt_1": "dispute", "Opt_2": "condition", "Opt_3": "institution", "Opt_4": "revolution", "Answer": "revolution", "Opt_1_def": "argument; conflict", "Opt_2_def": "state", "Opt_3_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom", "Opt_4_def": "a time of great change"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Sitting too long in front of a computer may ____ headaches or back problems.", "Opt_1": "retire", "Opt_2": "displace", "Opt_3": "attract", "Opt_4": "induce", "Answer": "induce", "Opt_1_def": "to stop working", "Opt_2_def": "to push out or take the place of something or someone", "Opt_3_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like", "Opt_4_def": "to make happen; to force"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The publishing company brought a ____ of its books to display to teachers.", "Opt_1": "point", "Opt_2": "degree", "Opt_3": "sample", "Opt_4": "dimension", "Answer": "sample", "Opt_1_def": "purpose; reason; value", "Opt_2_def": "amount", "Opt_3_def": "example; a smaller number of a larger collection", "Opt_4_def": "importance; amount"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "In about 5 billion years, the sun will ____ its fuel supply, and will puff up into a bloated star called a red giant.", "Opt_1": "exhaust", "Opt_2": "suppress", "Opt_3": "occupy", "Opt_4": "communicate", "Answer": "exhaust", "Opt_1_def": "to use up", "Opt_2_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen", "Opt_3_def": "to up space or time", "Opt_4_def": "to convey information"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "At no ____ in our deliberations are numbers employed in a way that would trigger an automatic decision to offer or deny admission.", "Opt_1": "point", "Opt_2": "contract", "Opt_3": "element", "Opt_4": "facilities", "Answer": "point", "Opt_1_def": "purpose; reason; value", "Opt_2_def": "a written agreement, binding in law", "Opt_3_def": "aspect, part", "Opt_4_def": "buildings and other places that can be used by people"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The profession of social work is based on the values of service, social and economic justice, dignity and ____ of the person, importance of human relationships, and integrity and competence in practice.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "There is a widespread belief that scaling up HIV ____ counseling and testing (VCT) programs in Africa will have large prevention benefits.", "Opt_1": "spontaneous", "Opt_2": "voluntary", "Opt_3": "broad", "Opt_4": "valid", "Answer": "voluntary", "Opt_1_def": "happening without warning or planning", "Opt_2_def": "done freely; from personal choice", "Opt_3_def": "wide, extensive", "Opt_4_def": "correct"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Traveling really gives students a better ____ of the world.", "Opt_1": "category", "Opt_2": "course", "Opt_3": "society", "Opt_4": "perspective", "Answer": "perspective", "Opt_1_def": "group of similar items", "Opt_2_def": "a subject or period of study", "Opt_3_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country", "Opt_4_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If you are accepted you will need to arrange to have an ____ copy of your scores sent to the Program address below.", "Opt_1": "brief", "Opt_2": "official", "Opt_3": "widespread", "Opt_4": "proper", "Answer": "official", "Opt_1_def": "short", "Opt_2_def": "approved by an authority", "Opt_3_def": "common", "Opt_4_def": "correct, appropriate"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "There is no mechanism in the master plan to ____ whether or not we are doing what we are supposed to do.", "Opt_1": "prevent", "Opt_2": "solve", "Opt_3": "assess", "Opt_4": "investigate", "Answer": "assess", "Opt_1_def": "to stop from doing or happening", "Opt_2_def": "to find an answer", "Opt_3_def": "to judge or test", "Opt_4_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Consequently, the percentages will not sum to 100% because many students were ____ on the questions in the survey.", "Opt_1": "odd", "Opt_2": "vast", "Opt_3": "neutral", "Opt_4": "available", "Answer": "neutral", "Opt_1_def": "strange, unusual", "Opt_2_def": "very large", "Opt_3_def": "neither for nor against; neither positive nor negative", "Opt_4_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "When a ____ of wood is gently put into still water, it will descend by the force of gravity, until it has displaced a quantity of water, equal to its own.", "Opt_1": "mention", "Opt_2": "assemble", "Opt_3": "block", "Opt_4": "fail", "Answer": "block", "Opt_1_def": "to say; state", "Opt_2_def": "to get, put or bring together", "Opt_3_def": "to not allow; to stop or prevent", "Opt_4_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The school wanted to ____ students from families outside the usual sphere of business and finance.", "Opt_1": "attract", "Opt_2": "assimilate", "Opt_3": "insert", "Opt_4": "prevent", "Answer": "attract", "Opt_1_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like", "Opt_2_def": "to take in", "Opt_3_def": "to put in", "Opt_4_def": "to stop from doing or happening"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government predicts that oil prices will not ____ as much this year as last year.", "Opt_1": "prospect", "Opt_2": "privilege", "Opt_3": "speed", "Opt_4": "vary", "Answer": "vary", "Opt_1_def": "chance, likelihood", "Opt_2_def": "a right (to do something)", "Opt_3_def": "how quickly something moves or changes", "Opt_4_def": "to change or be different"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The government announced that it was pleased with the ____ fall in unemployment during its term in office.", "Opt_1": "independent", "Opt_2": "abstract", "Opt_3": "flexible", "Opt_4": "steady", "Answer": "steady", "Opt_1_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else", "Opt_2_def": "not specific or concrete", "Opt_3_def": "can be changed or bent", "Opt_4_def": "gradual; without interruptions; firm"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The ____ in Iraq continues to occupy the government's attention.", "Opt_1": "statement", "Opt_2": "dispute", "Opt_3": "disaster", "Opt_4": "situation", "Answer": "situation", "Opt_1_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)", "Opt_2_def": "argument; conflict", "Opt_3_def": "a huge problem or failure", "Opt_4_def": "circumstances"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The teacher did not completely ____ the students' suggestion, but she first needed to discuss it with the principal.", "Opt_1": "accumulate", "Opt_2": "dismiss", "Opt_3": "assist", "Opt_4": "undergo", "Answer": "dismiss", "Opt_1_def": "to grow; to gather together", "Opt_2_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant", "Opt_3_def": "to help", "Opt_4_def": "to receive or experience"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Sometimes it is necessary to ____ force in order to achieve peace in a troubled region.", "Opt_1": "exert", "Opt_2": "assert", "Opt_3": "compete", "Opt_4": "allege", "Answer": "exert", "Opt_1_def": "to use", "Opt_2_def": "to claim, to say strongly", "Opt_3_def": "to try and win against someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to claim or state"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Teachers can ____ that students get a minimum of 8 hours sleep per night, but they cannot dictate it.", "Opt_1": "lessen", "Opt_2": "respect", "Opt_3": "assist", "Opt_4": "suggest", "Answer": "suggest", "Opt_1_def": "to reduce", "Opt_2_def": "to think positively about someone; to tolerate or avoid interfering with something", "Opt_3_def": "to help", "Opt_4_def": "to say an idea; to recommend"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "She claimed that the disproportionate number of non-native speakers in the ____ did not distort the results.", "Opt_1": "survey", "Opt_2": "struggle", "Opt_3": "exhibit", "Opt_4": "interpretation", "Answer": "survey", "Opt_1_def": "questionnaire; information gained by questioning people or data", "Opt_2_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome", "Opt_3_def": "to show", "Opt_4_def": "explanation; assessment"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "He said the debate now should ____ events of the past and the focus should be on what the UN, the US and Iraq could do to achieve the results.", "Opt_1": "decrease", "Opt_2": "remove", "Opt_3": "exclude", "Opt_4": "prevent", "Answer": "exclude", "Opt_1_def": "to get smaller, to go down", "Opt_2_def": "to take away", "Opt_3_def": "to leave out; opposite of include", "Opt_4_def": "to stop from doing or happening"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Studies have shown that students ____ jobs that they like to jobs that pay well.", "Opt_1": "permit", "Opt_2": "introduce", "Opt_3": "contradict", "Opt_4": "prefer", "Answer": "prefer", "Opt_1_def": "to allow", "Opt_2_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time", "Opt_3_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong", "Opt_4_def": "to like better"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The faculty member cannot ____ a reasonable request for extension of the project due date.", "Opt_1": "associate", "Opt_2": "create", "Opt_3": "accompany", "Opt_4": "refuse", "Answer": "refuse", "Opt_1_def": "to link to; to make a connection to", "Opt_2_def": "to make; to use your imagination to make something new", "Opt_3_def": "to go with someone or something; to exist together", "Opt_4_def": "to not do something that someone wants you to do"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Recent government IT initiatives focus narrowly on a specific technical problem, like enabling ____ data communication or Web-based transactions.", "Opt_1": "smooth", "Opt_2": "brief", "Opt_3": "automatic", "Opt_4": "mobile", "Answer": "mobile", "Opt_1_def": "easy, unproblematic", "Opt_2_def": "short", "Opt_3_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually", "Opt_4_def": "moving; able to move"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The government is thinking about introducing courses to ____ young people how to be good parents.", "Opt_1": "train", "Opt_2": "confront", "Opt_3": "attract", "Opt_4": "ban", "Answer": "train", "Opt_1_def": "to teach someone how to do a job", "Opt_2_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)", "Opt_3_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like", "Opt_4_def": "to prohibit or forbid"}]]